<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="Bollywood-Classic-RU">
    <display-name>Bollywood Classic</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/Bollywood-Classic-RU.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417004230 +0500" stop="20260417033252 +0500">
    <title>Brahmachari</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Abandoned as a child, Brahmachari lives in a mortgaged house with twelve young orphans. He saves a woman from dying and she changes his life forever. But first she has to deal with her own affairs.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417033252 +0500" stop="20260417053409 +0500">
    <title>Ittefaq 1969</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dilip, who loves his passion more than his wife, threatens to kill her if she harms his paintings. Later, when his wife is found murdered, he is accused of the crime and sent to a psychiatric ward.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417053409 +0500" stop="20260417084256 +0500">
    <title>Hamraaz</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kumar, a stage actor, falls in love with Meena and gets married to her. Things take a turn when one day she is found murdered and he becomes the prime suspect.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417084256 +0500" stop="20260417115325 +0500">
    <title>Kudrat 1981</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Chandramukhi visits Shimla and learns that she is a reincarnation of Paro, a girl who was raped and murdered. Plagued by her dark past, she attempts to bring the culprits to justice.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417115325 +0500" stop="20260417141725 +0500">
    <title>Yaraana</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>JB, a borderline psychopath, is attracted to Lalita, a beautiful young woman. He forces her to marry him but she runs away on her wedding day by feigning unconsciousness.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417141725 +0500" stop="20260417170813 +0500">
    <title>Dhool Ka Phool</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After Mahesh abandons Meena and their baby, she is compelled to desert the child to fend for himself. However, he gets adopted by a kind Muslim man and grows up to soon cross paths with his past.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417170813 +0500" stop="20260417201719 +0500">
    <title>Ustadon Ke Ustad</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vishwanath and Jaikishan are two thieves and good friends. When they try to lead an honest life for the sake of their women, Pukhraj turns them against each other and the two become sworn enemies.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417201719 +0500" stop="20260417232407 +0500">
    <title>Tyagi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Village-based Shankar makes his living as a farmer, living with his dad, and two brothers. He borrows money to fund his brothers education in the city. But once in the city they meet with the underworld and begin to carry on illegal activities.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417232407 +0500" stop="20260418025546 +0500">
    <title>Sagar Sangam</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Upon growing to be a criminal, Gopi's conviction sends him to Devipur where he uncovers the truth about his traumatic childhood and sets off to seek revenge.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260418025546 +0500" stop="20260418054701 +0500">
    <title>Aakhri Kasam</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jagga, a labourer, loses both his wife and son after an attack by an evil zamindar. He abducts one of the zamindar's sons, raises him as a good person and pits him against his father to get revenge.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260418054701 +0500" stop="20260418081500 +0500">
    <title>Babu</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Babu, a young man, falls in love with Kammo. When a thug rapes her, he murders him out of revenge, which leads to his arrest. After his release, he starts looking after Kammo and her child, Pinky. However, Pinky grows up to be a snob.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260418081500 +0500" stop="20260418111657 +0500">
    <title>Saagar</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Raja, a fisherman is secretly in love with Mona. When wealthy Ravi comes to live with his grandmother, Kamladevi, he sees Mona and falls in love with her.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260418111657 +0500" stop="20260418140235 +0500">
    <title>Aadmi 1993</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vijay, a factory supervisor, is falsely accused and arrested for killing his family. Just when he is at his lowest point, an inspector offers to help him in return for capturing the son of a gangster.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260418140235 +0500" stop="20260418170206 +0500">
    <title>Aa Gale Lag Jaa 1994</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Roshni, a wealthy heiress, wants to marry Suraj, a poor man, but her mother disapproves as his father is an ex-prisoner. Meanwhile, a series of murders take place and the suspicion falls on Suraj.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260418170206 +0500" stop="20260418200717 +0500">
    <title>Kal Ki Awaz</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>When a bank chairman's son is abducted and held for ransom, DSP Ali intervenes but cannot save the child. Later, his world is turned upside down when his daughter is kidnapped.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260418200717 +0500" stop="20260418230727 +0500">
    <title>Justice Chaudhury</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Justice Chaudhury is forced to go against his principles when criminal Shanker Singh's brother Jai Singh harasses his speech-impaired daughter Lakshmi.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260418230727 +0500" stop="20260419021646 +0500">
    <title>Yakeen 1969</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Rajesh, a scientist, works with the Indian Government on a confidential research project. He is forced to deal with miscreants who wish to steal his research.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>