<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="Bollywood-Classic-RU">
    <display-name>Bollywood Classic</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/Bollywood-Classic-RU.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260416073704 +0500" stop="20260416100504 +0500">
    <title>Babu</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Babu, a young man, falls in love with Kammo. When a thug rapes her, he murders him out of revenge, which leads to his arrest. After his release, he starts looking after Kammo and her child, Pinky. However, Pinky grows up to be a snob.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260416100504 +0500" stop="20260416124817 +0500">
    <title>Adalat</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A farmer is aving 3 city boys from a tiger's theeth. In return they invite him to the city, where he find out that one of them rape his daughter.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260416124817 +0500" stop="20260416155346 +0500">
    <title>Mazdoor</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A laborer-turned-businessman faces challenges after the marriage of his children.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260416155346 +0500" stop="20260416183941 +0500">
    <title>Dil Tera Aashiq</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Thakur Ranvir Singh Chaudhary cuts off his ties with his sister after she marries a man below their status, but after her death the responsibility of looking after her children falls on him.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260416183941 +0500" stop="20260416215103 +0500">
    <title>Khud-Daar</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Hari is forced to marry Seema, who dislikes his stepbrothers, Govind and Rajesh. When he goes to Mumbai, she displaces them to become beggars. However, destiny reunites them with Hari in a courtroom.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260416215103 +0500" stop="20260417004230 +0500">
    <title>Tum Haseen Main Jawaan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Sunil, a promiscuous navy officer, falls in love with Anuradha and introduces her to his family. However, an admirer of Anuradha tries to deceive Sunil by informing him that she is a single mother.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417004230 +0500" stop="20260417033252 +0500">
    <title>Brahmachari</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Abandoned as a child, Brahmachari lives in a mortgaged house with twelve young orphans. He saves a woman from dying and she changes his life forever. But first she has to deal with her own affairs.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417033252 +0500" stop="20260417053409 +0500">
    <title>Ittefaq 1969</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dilip, who loves his passion more than his wife, threatens to kill her if she harms his paintings. Later, when his wife is found murdered, he is accused of the crime and sent to a psychiatric ward.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417053409 +0500" stop="20260417084256 +0500">
    <title>Hamraaz</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kumar, a stage actor, falls in love with Meena and gets married to her. Things take a turn when one day she is found murdered and he becomes the prime suspect.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417084256 +0500" stop="20260417115325 +0500">
    <title>Kudrat 1981</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Chandramukhi visits Shimla and learns that she is a reincarnation of Paro, a girl who was raped and murdered. Plagued by her dark past, she attempts to bring the culprits to justice.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417115325 +0500" stop="20260417141725 +0500">
    <title>Yaraana</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>JB, a borderline psychopath, is attracted to Lalita, a beautiful young woman. He forces her to marry him but she runs away on her wedding day by feigning unconsciousness.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417141725 +0500" stop="20260417170813 +0500">
    <title>Dhool Ka Phool</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After Mahesh abandons Meena and their baby, she is compelled to desert the child to fend for himself. However, he gets adopted by a kind Muslim man and grows up to soon cross paths with his past.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417170813 +0500" stop="20260417201719 +0500">
    <title>Ustadon Ke Ustad</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Vishwanath and Jaikishan are two thieves and good friends. When they try to lead an honest life for the sake of their women, Pukhraj turns them against each other and the two become sworn enemies.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417201719 +0500" stop="20260417232407 +0500">
    <title>Tyagi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Village-based Shankar makes his living as a farmer, living with his dad, and two brothers. He borrows money to fund his brothers education in the city. But once in the city they meet with the underworld and begin to carry on illegal activities.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-Classic-RU" start="20260417232407 +0500" stop="20260418025546 +0500">
    <title>Sagar Sangam</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Upon growing to be a criminal, Gopi's conviction sends him to Devipur where he uncovers the truth about his traumatic childhood and sets off to seek revenge.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>