<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="Bollywood-HD-RU">
    <display-name>Bollywood HD</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/Bollywood-HD-RU.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260417002615 +0500" stop="20260417025334 +0500">
    <title>EMI: Liya Hai To Chukana Padega</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Sattar Bhai runs a collection agency called Good Luck Recovery in Mumbai's Bhendi Bazar area. Famous for his notoriety, he uses unconventional methods to make four defaulters repay their debts.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260417025334 +0500" stop="20260417054450 +0500">
    <title>Ghar Jamai</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dwarka, a millionaire, is impressed by Anil, a principled man, and wants him to marry Mona, his daughter. However, after their marriage, he compels him to move into his house.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260417054450 +0500" stop="20260417081556 +0500">
    <title>Ek Thi Daayan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Bobo, a famous magician, plans to marry his girlfriend Tamara. Tragedy strikes when he gets scary hallucinations about his dead sister. Left with no other option, he seeks a psychiatrist's help.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260417081556 +0500" stop="20260417102127 +0500">
    <title>Ragini MMS 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A sleazy film director's decision to shoot his latest erotic horror movie in a notorious haunted house angers the vengeful spirit of its past inhabitant.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260417102127 +0500" stop="20260417133156 +0500">
    <title>Undertrial</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Sagar Hussain, a factory worker, is falsely accused of and imprisoned for raping his own daughters. Later, when his lawyer digs deeper, the truth reveals itself to be much worse than imagined.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260417133156 +0500" stop="20260417155719 +0500">
    <title>Train to Pakistan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The people of Mano Majra, a village on the Indo-Pak border, live in harmony. However, things change when a train arrives from Pakistan containing the dead bodies of the people coming to India.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260417155719 +0500" stop="20260417180514 +0500">
    <title>Agnee Prem</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>When two childhood friends are separated from each other, they promise to meet each year at a temple on a hill. However, they meet 10 years later when they are grown-ups.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260417180514 +0500" stop="20260417203453 +0500">
    <title>Dil Hai Betaab</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Meena and Raja, who are in love with each other, decide to marry.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260417203453 +0500" stop="20260417232358 +0500">
    <title>Mohabbat Ki Arzoo</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A motor mechanic posing as a rich man falls in love with a girl from a wealthy family pretending to be poor. The lovers rebel against their family members and society to remain together.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260417232358 +0500" stop="20260418020330 +0500">
    <title>Kucch To Hai</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A group of friends accidentally throw professor Bakshi off a cliff after seeing a corpse in his house. Years later, during a reunion, they are stalked by a mysterious killer.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260418020330 +0500" stop="20260418044901 +0500">
    <title>Dushman Duniya Ka</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Mahesh, an honest man, is shocked to learn that his son, Lucky, has been using recreational drugs. Lucky promises to kick the habit but circumstances push him towards the world of drugs once again.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260418044901 +0500" stop="20260418075931 +0500">
    <title>Undertrial</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Sagar Hussain, a factory worker, is falsely accused of and imprisoned for raping his own daughters. Later, when his lawyer digs deeper, the truth reveals itself to be much worse than imagined.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260418075931 +0500" stop="20260418103001 +0500">
    <title>Zameer: The Fire Within</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Pooja gets married to Suraj but feels guilty for separating him from Supriya, his former fiancee. When Suraj learns the truth he abandons her, oblivious to the fact that she is pregnant.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260418103001 +0500" stop="20260418132451 +0500">
    <title>Mohabbat 1997</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Gaurav and Rohit, two best friends, fall in love with Shweta. After a traumatic accident, Rohit dies and Shweta gets engaged to Gaurav, who seems to be hiding a deadly secret.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260418132451 +0500" stop="20260418160826 +0500">
    <title>Karobaar: The Business of Love</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Friends Rajiv and Amar go their separate ways after Seema decides to be with Amar rather than Rajiv. Years later, prosecution lawyer Amar is delighted to see Rajiv in court and accused of murder.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260418160826 +0500" stop="20260418181800 +0500">
    <title>Bandit Queen</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Phoolan Devi, who belongs to a lower caste, faces sexual abuse and discrimination in society. A turn of events leads to her becoming the revered leader of a gang.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260418181800 +0500" stop="20260418210644 +0500">
    <title>Nishchaiy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>2 brothers, Ravi and Rohan separated due to unforeseen circumstances created by Ravi's employer. Years later Ravi, who is released from prison and Rohan, a successful lawyer clash with each other unaware of the fact that they are real brothers.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260418210644 +0500" stop="20260418230920 +0500">
    <title>Shor in the City</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Various residents and career-criminals face challenges in crime-laden Mumbai.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="Bollywood-HD-RU" start="20260418230920 +0500" stop="20260419021216 +0500">
    <title>Hindustan Ki Kasam</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>When two twin brothers get separated at birth, one grows up as a Hindu in India while the other as a Muslim in Pakistan. Later, they meet at opposite sides on the battlefield.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>