<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="CGTN-China-Travel-CN">
    <display-name>CGTN China Travel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/CGTN-China-Travel-CN.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420081903 +0500" stop="20260420085203 +0500">
    <title>Echoes of Green</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Echoes of Green takes viewers deep into Anji’s bamboo forests and mountain villages, where a new generation of Chinese youth is redefining how to live with nature. Through stories of outdoor sports, forest cafés, tea rituals, and family farms, the series shows how ecological ideals have become everyday choices and creative lifestyles. It is not just about landscapes, but about people — young dreamers proving that prosperity and nature can grow side by side, and that culture gives life to sustainability.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420085203 +0500" stop="20260420090000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420090000 +0500" stop="20260420093711 +0500">
    <title>Life as a Miao Silversmith</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, Eva May steps into Maliao Village — a century-old silversmith village nestled in Leishan, Guizhou Province. Over the course of a week, she dives into the craft and daily lives of Miao men who carry on the silversmithing legacy. She works side by side with local silversmiths day in and day out, delving into the culture and techniques behind Miao silverware. She even joins master silversmiths for a live-stream event, before engaging in discussions with university professors about how traditional craftsmanship can fuel rural revitalization. On top of that, she witnesses the breathtaking sight of \"maidens adorned in silver and flowers\" at the grand Miao New Year celebrations, visits Xijiang Qianhu Miaozhai — the world’s largest Miao village — and learns to forge a small yet meaningful piece of Miao silver ornament.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420093711 +0500" stop="20260420094629 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420094629 +0500" stop="20260420102057 +0500">
    <title>New Year with the Miao</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, it’s Miao New Year, and that means multitudes of merrymaking! Fishing, drinking, bullfighting… Join the host Min-Zhui Lee, among the magnificent mountains of Leishan, where it’s all happening for the ethnic Miao.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420102057 +0500" stop="20260420103001 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420103001 +0500" stop="20260420110502 +0500">
    <title>Valentine's with the Snake King</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Every year on Qixi Festival (Chinese Valentine's Day), the town of Zhanghu in Nanping, Fujian Province hosts a folk custom event: the Snake King Parade. Local residents carry the statue of the Snake King from the temple, along with specially prepared pythons, and parade through the streets and alleys. Wherever the procession passes, residents and shopkeepers greet them with firecrackers and burn incense to pray, hoping to receive the unique blessing of the Snake King. This distinctive folk activity is rarely seen elsewhere across China. Taking this event as its highlight, the episode leads audiences on a deep dive into the towns and villages of northern Fujian, delivering a highly engaging and visually appealing viewing experience.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420110502 +0500" stop="20260420111311 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420111311 +0500" stop="20260420114746 +0500">
    <title>An Encounter with China’s Endangered Monkeys</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we head to Baima Snow Mountain Nature Reserve in Diqing Tibetan Autonomous Prefecture, Yunnan Province, to learn about and participate in the conservation work for the rare and precious national treasure: the Yunnan snub-nosed monkey. The presenter ventures into the forest, experiences the daily life of local forest rangers, and witnesses the harmonious relationship between humans and monkeys. We interview \"the Monkey Father\"—Long Yongcheng, chief scientist of The Nature Conservancy (TNC) and leader of China's Primate Expert Group—who shares stories about the two decades of efforts dedicated to protecting the Yunnan snub-nosed monkey. We also go to the mountains to conduct research alongside young volunteers. Through these activities, we recognize the importance of environmental education for young people in promoting natural ecological balance and harmonious development.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420114746 +0500" stop="20260420115630 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420115630 +0500" stop="20260420123200 +0500">
    <title>World Heritages in China: A Journey on Water from Wuxi to Yixing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Water has always been the heartbeat of human civilization, nurturing the cities it weaves through. From the first drops that carved out its waterways to the thriving metropolis we see today, Wuxi’s story is inseparable from the grand canal. This is the story of a city born of water. In this episode, we uncover how the waters have shaped Wuxi’s identity.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420123200 +0500" stop="20260420124137 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420124137 +0500" stop="20260420132007 +0500">
    <title>Ding Porcelain Firing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In ancient times, skilled craftsmen combined clay with fire and, using nothing more than their hands and wisdom, created the history of porcelain.\n\nA thousand years ago, at the time of the Northern Song Dynasty, a type of porcelain was produced that stood out for its exquisite quality, elegant coloring and beautiful patterns. This was Ding porcelain, and it became a favorite at the imperial court. However, within 200 years, amid the chaos of constant warfare, the art of making it was lost. The dazzling white light of the Ding kilns had faded, seemingly forever. \n\nAnd yet, 800 years later, that light has been reignited.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420132007 +0500" stop="20260420132935 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420132935 +0500" stop="20260420140505 +0500">
    <title>Quyang Stone Carving</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Quyang is known as a hometown of Chinese carving. Quyang's stone carving works are popular around different parts of China, thus also exported to over 100 countries and regions worldwide. The style of Quyang stone carving both carries the mysterious and rough spirit of the Wei Dynasty and the natural and graceful forms of the Tang and Song dynasties. It reflects the life experiences and live philosophies of local artisans. Each statue's showcases unique oriental aesthetics.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420140505 +0500" stop="20260420141903 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420141903 +0500" stop="20260420145203 +0500">
    <title>Echoes of Green</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Echoes of Green takes viewers deep into Anji’s bamboo forests and mountain villages, where a new generation of Chinese youth is redefining how to live with nature. Through stories of outdoor sports, forest cafés, tea rituals, and family farms, the series shows how ecological ideals have become everyday choices and creative lifestyles. It is not just about landscapes, but about people — young dreamers proving that prosperity and nature can grow side by side, and that culture gives life to sustainability.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420145203 +0500" stop="20260420150000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420150000 +0500" stop="20260420153711 +0500">
    <title>Life as a Miao Silversmith</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, Eva May steps into Maliao Village — a century-old silversmith village nestled in Leishan, Guizhou Province. Over the course of a week, she dives into the craft and daily lives of Miao men who carry on the silversmithing legacy. She works side by side with local silversmiths day in and day out, delving into the culture and techniques behind Miao silverware. She even joins master silversmiths for a live-stream event, before engaging in discussions with university professors about how traditional craftsmanship can fuel rural revitalization. On top of that, she witnesses the breathtaking sight of \"maidens adorned in silver and flowers\" at the grand Miao New Year celebrations, visits Xijiang Qianhu Miaozhai — the world’s largest Miao village — and learns to forge a small yet meaningful piece of Miao silver ornament.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420153711 +0500" stop="20260420154629 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420154629 +0500" stop="20260420162057 +0500">
    <title>New Year with the Miao</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, it’s Miao New Year, and that means multitudes of merrymaking! Fishing, drinking, bullfighting… Join the host Min-Zhui Lee, among the magnificent mountains of Leishan, where it’s all happening for the ethnic Miao.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420162057 +0500" stop="20260420163001 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420163001 +0500" stop="20260420170502 +0500">
    <title>Valentine's with the Snake King</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Every year on Qixi Festival (Chinese Valentine's Day), the town of Zhanghu in Nanping, Fujian Province hosts a folk custom event: the Snake King Parade. Local residents carry the statue of the Snake King from the temple, along with specially prepared pythons, and parade through the streets and alleys. Wherever the procession passes, residents and shopkeepers greet them with firecrackers and burn incense to pray, hoping to receive the unique blessing of the Snake King. This distinctive folk activity is rarely seen elsewhere across China. Taking this event as its highlight, the episode leads audiences on a deep dive into the towns and villages of northern Fujian, delivering a highly engaging and visually appealing viewing experience.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420170502 +0500" stop="20260420171311 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420171311 +0500" stop="20260420174746 +0500">
    <title>An Encounter with China’s Endangered Monkeys</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we head to Baima Snow Mountain Nature Reserve in Diqing Tibetan Autonomous Prefecture, Yunnan Province, to learn about and participate in the conservation work for the rare and precious national treasure: the Yunnan snub-nosed monkey. The presenter ventures into the forest, experiences the daily life of local forest rangers, and witnesses the harmonious relationship between humans and monkeys. We interview \"the Monkey Father\"—Long Yongcheng, chief scientist of The Nature Conservancy (TNC) and leader of China's Primate Expert Group—who shares stories about the two decades of efforts dedicated to protecting the Yunnan snub-nosed monkey. We also go to the mountains to conduct research alongside young volunteers. Through these activities, we recognize the importance of environmental education for young people in promoting natural ecological balance and harmonious development.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420174746 +0500" stop="20260420175630 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420175630 +0500" stop="20260420183200 +0500">
    <title>World Heritages in China: A Journey on Water from Wuxi to Yixing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Water has always been the heartbeat of human civilization, nurturing the cities it weaves through. From the first drops that carved out its waterways to the thriving metropolis we see today, Wuxi’s story is inseparable from the grand canal. This is the story of a city born of water. In this episode, we uncover how the waters have shaped Wuxi’s identity.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420183200 +0500" stop="20260420184137 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420184137 +0500" stop="20260420192007 +0500">
    <title>Ding Porcelain Firing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In ancient times, skilled craftsmen combined clay with fire and, using nothing more than their hands and wisdom, created the history of porcelain.\n\nA thousand years ago, at the time of the Northern Song Dynasty, a type of porcelain was produced that stood out for its exquisite quality, elegant coloring and beautiful patterns. This was Ding porcelain, and it became a favorite at the imperial court. However, within 200 years, amid the chaos of constant warfare, the art of making it was lost. The dazzling white light of the Ding kilns had faded, seemingly forever. \n\nAnd yet, 800 years later, that light has been reignited.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420192007 +0500" stop="20260420192935 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420192935 +0500" stop="20260420200505 +0500">
    <title>Quyang Stone Carving</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Quyang is known as a hometown of Chinese carving. Quyang's stone carving works are popular around different parts of China, thus also exported to over 100 countries and regions worldwide. The style of Quyang stone carving both carries the mysterious and rough spirit of the Wei Dynasty and the natural and graceful forms of the Tang and Song dynasties. It reflects the life experiences and live philosophies of local artisans. Each statue's showcases unique oriental aesthetics.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420200505 +0500" stop="20260420201903 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420201903 +0500" stop="20260420205203 +0500">
    <title>Echoes of Green</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Echoes of Green takes viewers deep into Anji’s bamboo forests and mountain villages, where a new generation of Chinese youth is redefining how to live with nature. Through stories of outdoor sports, forest cafés, tea rituals, and family farms, the series shows how ecological ideals have become everyday choices and creative lifestyles. It is not just about landscapes, but about people — young dreamers proving that prosperity and nature can grow side by side, and that culture gives life to sustainability.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420205203 +0500" stop="20260420210000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420210000 +0500" stop="20260420213755 +0500">
    <title>The Pulse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>“The Pulse” features musicians performing amidst Guizhou’s stunning natural scenery, bringing to life a harmonious blend of music and landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420213755 +0500" stop="20260420221226 +0500">
    <title>The Pulse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>“The Pulse” features musicians performing amidst Guizhou’s stunning natural scenery, bringing to life a harmonious blend of music and landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420221226 +0500" stop="20260420221844 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420221844 +0500" stop="20260420222748 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420222748 +0500" stop="20260420230124 +0500">
    <title>The Great Wall Homestay</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode of Travelogue, Tianran He's heading to the mountains on Beijing’s northern outskirts, to meet some people his age who have swapped city life for the chance to run guesthouses beside the Great Wall of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420230124 +0500" stop="20260420230933 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420230933 +0500" stop="20260420234210 +0500">
    <title>A Village Homestay in Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode of Travelogue, our presenter Tianran He’s heading out of Beijing proper, to the city’s Miyun District. There he’ll meet some people running guesthouses who gave up their day jobs, in order to achieve the dream of a place of their own in the country.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420234210 +0500" stop="20260420235054 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260420235054 +0500" stop="20260421002924 +0500">
    <title>An Echo of Antiquity: The Enduring Charm of Kunqu</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kunqu Opera, the \"ancestor of a hundred operas,\" condenses its 600-year essence. From its melodious and captivating vocals to its elegant and delicate movements, we will explore the unique charm of this ancient performing art and the profound cultural heritage behind it.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421002924 +0500" stop="20260421003356 +0500">
    <title>From bean to cup: The rise of China’s specialty coffee</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Pu’er — a city named after tea — is now at the center of another brewing story: China’s fast-rising coffee industry. From mountain farms to urban cafés, a new generation of growers and coffee professionals is bringing China’s specialty coffee onto the global stage. What makes Yunnan’s coffee region unique? How are farmers, industry professionals, and consumers shaping a new coffee ecosystem in China? Join us as we explore how China’s coffee culture is evolving — from origin to cup.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421003356 +0500" stop="20260421004333 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421004333 +0500" stop="20260421011903 +0500">
    <title>A Vibe of the Village: The Beat of Xiangxi Drums</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Experience the vibrant power of Xiangxi Drum Dance. This program delves into the heart of Tujia and Miao cultures, showcasing the rhythmic beats and spirited performances that have echoed through West Hunan's mountains for centuries. Discover the stories, traditions, and raw energy of this captivating folk art.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421011903 +0500" stop="20260421012831 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421012831 +0500" stop="20260421020341 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: Wing Chun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martial arts lover Kleber Battaglia is on a mission: To seek out China's kungfu masters, and learn their secrets. From explosive Wing Chun to fluid Taiji Quan, slippery Snake Style to elegant White Crane, he'll learn hidden moves and ancient techniques for defeating powerful opponents. But ?there’s more to kungfu than combat: From culture and philosophy, to wellness and insights from the natural world, Kleber will discover that contained within every kick, strike and throw, is the condensed wisdom of the ancient masters. This is Kungfu-wise.\nKleber travels to Foshan, the birthplace of Wing Chun. A practitioner of this style, he seeks out masters of two different lineages: Ip Man and Snake Style. First he visits the Ip Man lineage, based on the legendary kungfu master whose life story spawned hundreds of martial arts movies, with Bruce Lee counting among his students. With Ip Man Wing Chun, Kleber learns how to create powerful short strikes perfectly suited to fighting in Foshan’s narrow alleys. With Snake Style, he experiences unique training methods that give its practitioners superhuman flexibility, allowing them to stick to their opponents, and even fight on boats in canals.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421020341 +0500" stop="20260421021909 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421021909 +0500" stop="20260421025309 +0500">
    <title>Wudang Martial Arts and Taichi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Join host Yegor on a journey into the heart of China’s Wudang Mountains—the spiritual cradle of Taoism and the birthplace of Wudang martial arts. Through in-depth conversations with renowned masters such as Zhong Xueyong, Cai Chongguang, Jake Pinnick, and Liu Xiang, this episode explores the philosophy, techniques, and living spirit of Wudang Quan and Taichi.\nFrom the internal cultivation of qi to the harmony between body and mind, Wudang martial arts are more than just physical training—they are a way of life rooted in the Tao. Alongside martial techniques, the program also delves into traditional Chinese music, calligraphy, and medicine, revealing how these disciplines come together in the pursuit of balance, self-awareness, and longevity.\nThis is not just a story of punches and postures, but of tradition, transformation, and the timeless search for harmony between humans and the universe.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421025309 +0500" stop="20260421030000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421030000 +0500" stop="20260421033755 +0500">
    <title>The Pulse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>“The Pulse” features musicians performing amidst Guizhou’s stunning natural scenery, bringing to life a harmonious blend of music and landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421033755 +0500" stop="20260421041226 +0500">
    <title>The Pulse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>“The Pulse” features musicians performing amidst Guizhou’s stunning natural scenery, bringing to life a harmonious blend of music and landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421041226 +0500" stop="20260421041844 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421041844 +0500" stop="20260421042748 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421042748 +0500" stop="20260421050124 +0500">
    <title>The Great Wall Homestay</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode of Travelogue, Tianran He's heading to the mountains on Beijing’s northern outskirts, to meet some people his age who have swapped city life for the chance to run guesthouses beside the Great Wall of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421050124 +0500" stop="20260421050933 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421050933 +0500" stop="20260421054210 +0500">
    <title>A Village Homestay in Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode of Travelogue, our presenter Tianran He’s heading out of Beijing proper, to the city’s Miyun District. There he’ll meet some people running guesthouses who gave up their day jobs, in order to achieve the dream of a place of their own in the country.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421054210 +0500" stop="20260421055054 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421055054 +0500" stop="20260421062924 +0500">
    <title>An Echo of Antiquity: The Enduring Charm of Kunqu</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kunqu Opera, the \"ancestor of a hundred operas,\" condenses its 600-year essence. From its melodious and captivating vocals to its elegant and delicate movements, we will explore the unique charm of this ancient performing art and the profound cultural heritage behind it.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421062924 +0500" stop="20260421063356 +0500">
    <title>From bean to cup: The rise of China’s specialty coffee</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Pu’er — a city named after tea — is now at the center of another brewing story: China’s fast-rising coffee industry. From mountain farms to urban cafés, a new generation of growers and coffee professionals is bringing China’s specialty coffee onto the global stage. What makes Yunnan’s coffee region unique? How are farmers, industry professionals, and consumers shaping a new coffee ecosystem in China? Join us as we explore how China’s coffee culture is evolving — from origin to cup.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421063356 +0500" stop="20260421064333 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421064333 +0500" stop="20260421071903 +0500">
    <title>A Vibe of the Village: The Beat of Xiangxi Drums</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Experience the vibrant power of Xiangxi Drum Dance. This program delves into the heart of Tujia and Miao cultures, showcasing the rhythmic beats and spirited performances that have echoed through West Hunan's mountains for centuries. Discover the stories, traditions, and raw energy of this captivating folk art.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421071903 +0500" stop="20260421072831 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421072831 +0500" stop="20260421080341 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: Wing Chun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martial arts lover Kleber Battaglia is on a mission: To seek out China's kungfu masters, and learn their secrets. From explosive Wing Chun to fluid Taiji Quan, slippery Snake Style to elegant White Crane, he'll learn hidden moves and ancient techniques for defeating powerful opponents. But ?there’s more to kungfu than combat: From culture and philosophy, to wellness and insights from the natural world, Kleber will discover that contained within every kick, strike and throw, is the condensed wisdom of the ancient masters. This is Kungfu-wise.\nKleber travels to Foshan, the birthplace of Wing Chun. A practitioner of this style, he seeks out masters of two different lineages: Ip Man and Snake Style. First he visits the Ip Man lineage, based on the legendary kungfu master whose life story spawned hundreds of martial arts movies, with Bruce Lee counting among his students. With Ip Man Wing Chun, Kleber learns how to create powerful short strikes perfectly suited to fighting in Foshan’s narrow alleys. With Snake Style, he experiences unique training methods that give its practitioners superhuman flexibility, allowing them to stick to their opponents, and even fight on boats in canals.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421080341 +0500" stop="20260421081909 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421081909 +0500" stop="20260421085309 +0500">
    <title>Wudang Martial Arts and Taichi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Join host Yegor on a journey into the heart of China’s Wudang Mountains—the spiritual cradle of Taoism and the birthplace of Wudang martial arts. Through in-depth conversations with renowned masters such as Zhong Xueyong, Cai Chongguang, Jake Pinnick, and Liu Xiang, this episode explores the philosophy, techniques, and living spirit of Wudang Quan and Taichi.\nFrom the internal cultivation of qi to the harmony between body and mind, Wudang martial arts are more than just physical training—they are a way of life rooted in the Tao. Alongside martial techniques, the program also delves into traditional Chinese music, calligraphy, and medicine, revealing how these disciplines come together in the pursuit of balance, self-awareness, and longevity.\nThis is not just a story of punches and postures, but of tradition, transformation, and the timeless search for harmony between humans and the universe.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421085309 +0500" stop="20260421090000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421090000 +0500" stop="20260421093755 +0500">
    <title>The Pulse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>“The Pulse” features musicians performing amidst Guizhou’s stunning natural scenery, bringing to life a harmonious blend of music and landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421093755 +0500" stop="20260421101226 +0500">
    <title>The Pulse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>“The Pulse” features musicians performing amidst Guizhou’s stunning natural scenery, bringing to life a harmonious blend of music and landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421101226 +0500" stop="20260421101844 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421101844 +0500" stop="20260421102748 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421102748 +0500" stop="20260421110124 +0500">
    <title>The Great Wall Homestay</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode of Travelogue, Tianran He's heading to the mountains on Beijing’s northern outskirts, to meet some people his age who have swapped city life for the chance to run guesthouses beside the Great Wall of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421110124 +0500" stop="20260421110933 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421110933 +0500" stop="20260421114210 +0500">
    <title>A Village Homestay in Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode of Travelogue, our presenter Tianran He’s heading out of Beijing proper, to the city’s Miyun District. There he’ll meet some people running guesthouses who gave up their day jobs, in order to achieve the dream of a place of their own in the country.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421114210 +0500" stop="20260421115054 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421115054 +0500" stop="20260421122924 +0500">
    <title>An Echo of Antiquity: The Enduring Charm of Kunqu</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kunqu Opera, the \"ancestor of a hundred operas,\" condenses its 600-year essence. From its melodious and captivating vocals to its elegant and delicate movements, we will explore the unique charm of this ancient performing art and the profound cultural heritage behind it.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421122924 +0500" stop="20260421123356 +0500">
    <title>From bean to cup: The rise of China’s specialty coffee</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Pu’er — a city named after tea — is now at the center of another brewing story: China’s fast-rising coffee industry. From mountain farms to urban cafés, a new generation of growers and coffee professionals is bringing China’s specialty coffee onto the global stage. What makes Yunnan’s coffee region unique? How are farmers, industry professionals, and consumers shaping a new coffee ecosystem in China? Join us as we explore how China’s coffee culture is evolving — from origin to cup.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421123356 +0500" stop="20260421124333 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421124333 +0500" stop="20260421131903 +0500">
    <title>A Vibe of the Village: The Beat of Xiangxi Drums</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Experience the vibrant power of Xiangxi Drum Dance. This program delves into the heart of Tujia and Miao cultures, showcasing the rhythmic beats and spirited performances that have echoed through West Hunan's mountains for centuries. Discover the stories, traditions, and raw energy of this captivating folk art.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421131903 +0500" stop="20260421132831 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421132831 +0500" stop="20260421140341 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: Wing Chun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martial arts lover Kleber Battaglia is on a mission: To seek out China's kungfu masters, and learn their secrets. From explosive Wing Chun to fluid Taiji Quan, slippery Snake Style to elegant White Crane, he'll learn hidden moves and ancient techniques for defeating powerful opponents. But ?there’s more to kungfu than combat: From culture and philosophy, to wellness and insights from the natural world, Kleber will discover that contained within every kick, strike and throw, is the condensed wisdom of the ancient masters. This is Kungfu-wise.\nKleber travels to Foshan, the birthplace of Wing Chun. A practitioner of this style, he seeks out masters of two different lineages: Ip Man and Snake Style. First he visits the Ip Man lineage, based on the legendary kungfu master whose life story spawned hundreds of martial arts movies, with Bruce Lee counting among his students. With Ip Man Wing Chun, Kleber learns how to create powerful short strikes perfectly suited to fighting in Foshan’s narrow alleys. With Snake Style, he experiences unique training methods that give its practitioners superhuman flexibility, allowing them to stick to their opponents, and even fight on boats in canals.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421140341 +0500" stop="20260421141909 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421141909 +0500" stop="20260421145309 +0500">
    <title>Wudang Martial Arts and Taichi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Join host Yegor on a journey into the heart of China’s Wudang Mountains—the spiritual cradle of Taoism and the birthplace of Wudang martial arts. Through in-depth conversations with renowned masters such as Zhong Xueyong, Cai Chongguang, Jake Pinnick, and Liu Xiang, this episode explores the philosophy, techniques, and living spirit of Wudang Quan and Taichi.\nFrom the internal cultivation of qi to the harmony between body and mind, Wudang martial arts are more than just physical training—they are a way of life rooted in the Tao. Alongside martial techniques, the program also delves into traditional Chinese music, calligraphy, and medicine, revealing how these disciplines come together in the pursuit of balance, self-awareness, and longevity.\nThis is not just a story of punches and postures, but of tradition, transformation, and the timeless search for harmony between humans and the universe.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421145309 +0500" stop="20260421150000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421150000 +0500" stop="20260421153755 +0500">
    <title>The Pulse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>“The Pulse” features musicians performing amidst Guizhou’s stunning natural scenery, bringing to life a harmonious blend of music and landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421153755 +0500" stop="20260421161226 +0500">
    <title>The Pulse</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>“The Pulse” features musicians performing amidst Guizhou’s stunning natural scenery, bringing to life a harmonious blend of music and landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421161226 +0500" stop="20260421161844 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421161844 +0500" stop="20260421162748 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421162748 +0500" stop="20260421170124 +0500">
    <title>The Great Wall Homestay</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode of Travelogue, Tianran He's heading to the mountains on Beijing’s northern outskirts, to meet some people his age who have swapped city life for the chance to run guesthouses beside the Great Wall of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421170124 +0500" stop="20260421170933 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421170933 +0500" stop="20260421174210 +0500">
    <title>A Village Homestay in Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode of Travelogue, our presenter Tianran He’s heading out of Beijing proper, to the city’s Miyun District. There he’ll meet some people running guesthouses who gave up their day jobs, in order to achieve the dream of a place of their own in the country.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421174210 +0500" stop="20260421175054 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421175054 +0500" stop="20260421182924 +0500">
    <title>An Echo of Antiquity: The Enduring Charm of Kunqu</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kunqu Opera, the \"ancestor of a hundred operas,\" condenses its 600-year essence. From its melodious and captivating vocals to its elegant and delicate movements, we will explore the unique charm of this ancient performing art and the profound cultural heritage behind it.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421182924 +0500" stop="20260421183356 +0500">
    <title>From bean to cup: The rise of China’s specialty coffee</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Pu’er — a city named after tea — is now at the center of another brewing story: China’s fast-rising coffee industry. From mountain farms to urban cafés, a new generation of growers and coffee professionals is bringing China’s specialty coffee onto the global stage. What makes Yunnan’s coffee region unique? How are farmers, industry professionals, and consumers shaping a new coffee ecosystem in China? Join us as we explore how China’s coffee culture is evolving — from origin to cup.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421183356 +0500" stop="20260421184333 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421184333 +0500" stop="20260421191903 +0500">
    <title>A Vibe of the Village: The Beat of Xiangxi Drums</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Experience the vibrant power of Xiangxi Drum Dance. This program delves into the heart of Tujia and Miao cultures, showcasing the rhythmic beats and spirited performances that have echoed through West Hunan's mountains for centuries. Discover the stories, traditions, and raw energy of this captivating folk art.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421191903 +0500" stop="20260421192831 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421192831 +0500" stop="20260421200341 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: Wing Chun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Martial arts lover Kleber Battaglia is on a mission: To seek out China's kungfu masters, and learn their secrets. From explosive Wing Chun to fluid Taiji Quan, slippery Snake Style to elegant White Crane, he'll learn hidden moves and ancient techniques for defeating powerful opponents. But ?there’s more to kungfu than combat: From culture and philosophy, to wellness and insights from the natural world, Kleber will discover that contained within every kick, strike and throw, is the condensed wisdom of the ancient masters. This is Kungfu-wise.\nKleber travels to Foshan, the birthplace of Wing Chun. A practitioner of this style, he seeks out masters of two different lineages: Ip Man and Snake Style. First he visits the Ip Man lineage, based on the legendary kungfu master whose life story spawned hundreds of martial arts movies, with Bruce Lee counting among his students. With Ip Man Wing Chun, Kleber learns how to create powerful short strikes perfectly suited to fighting in Foshan’s narrow alleys. With Snake Style, he experiences unique training methods that give its practitioners superhuman flexibility, allowing them to stick to their opponents, and even fight on boats in canals.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421200341 +0500" stop="20260421201909 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421201909 +0500" stop="20260421205309 +0500">
    <title>Wudang Martial Arts and Taichi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Join host Yegor on a journey into the heart of China’s Wudang Mountains—the spiritual cradle of Taoism and the birthplace of Wudang martial arts. Through in-depth conversations with renowned masters such as Zhong Xueyong, Cai Chongguang, Jake Pinnick, and Liu Xiang, this episode explores the philosophy, techniques, and living spirit of Wudang Quan and Taichi.\nFrom the internal cultivation of qi to the harmony between body and mind, Wudang martial arts are more than just physical training—they are a way of life rooted in the Tao. Alongside martial techniques, the program also delves into traditional Chinese music, calligraphy, and medicine, revealing how these disciplines come together in the pursuit of balance, self-awareness, and longevity.\nThis is not just a story of punches and postures, but of tradition, transformation, and the timeless search for harmony between humans and the universe.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421205309 +0500" stop="20260421210000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421210000 +0500" stop="20260421213755 +0500">
    <title>Women of the Xiangjiang River Ep.1</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Xiangjiang River runs 800 kilometers through the whole of Hunan Province. Hailed as the mother river of Hunan, it serves as a vital waterway connecting the Yangtze and Pearl River systems. Its source is located in Yongzhou, a land of abundant water resources, rich natural treasures and outstanding people. In this episode, we focus on three young women from Yongzhou: Pan Haiying, a dance teacher; Huang Cuilan, an inheritor of brocade weaving; and Hu Xin, a custodian of Nüshu culture. We document snippets of their daily lives and work, to reflect the profound cultural heritage along the Xiangjiang River and the value pursuits of the women living on its banks.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421213755 +0500" stop="20260421214543 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421214543 +0500" stop="20260421222237 +0500">
    <title>Women of the Xiangjiang River Ep.2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we continue our journey along the Xiangjiang River in Hunan Province, to meet more outstanding women from the cities of Hengyang and Zhuzhou. By documenting snippets of the daily lives and work of a paper-cutting artist, the director of the Hengyang Huagu Opera Troupe, and an inheritor of Liling porcelain craftsmanship, we gain vivid insights into the distinctive cultural traditions of this region.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421222237 +0500" stop="20260421223011 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421223011 +0500" stop="20260421230643 +0500">
    <title>Women of the Xiangjiang River Ep.3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we continue our journey along the Xiangjiang River in Hunan Province, traveling to the cities of Zhuzhou and Xiangtan to meet another group of extraordinary women. By capturing snippets of the lives and work of an electric locomotive designer, a flight instructor, a painter, and a poverty alleviation volunteer, we showcase the unique cultural and humanistic charm of this region.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421230643 +0500" stop="20260421231322 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421231322 +0500" stop="20260421234855 +0500">
    <title>Women of the Xiangjiang River Ep.4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we arrive in Changsha — the economic and cultural hub of Hunan Province, and a core city in the Yangtze River Middle Reaches Economic Zone. Our lens turns to the \"Xiangjiang Ladies\" who work in Changsha’s high-tech and equipment manufacturing sectors. Their daily lives and professional endeavors reflect the city’s innovative vitality, while their after-work gatherings also showcase the dazzling night views along both banks of the Xiangjiang River, highlighting Changsha’s distinct charm as a vibrant capital of leisure and entertainment.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421234855 +0500" stop="20260421235609 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260421235609 +0500" stop="20260422003508 +0500">
    <title>Indigo Dreams: A Hue of Dali Tie-dye</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dali Tie-dye is the unique textile art of the Bai people, renowned for its exquisite hand-tying and traditional indigo dyeing techniques that create brilliant, one-of-a-kind patterns. Explore the cultural heritage and enduring beauty of this ancient craft from Yunnan.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422003508 +0500" stop="20260422004315 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422004315 +0500" stop="20260422005747 +0500">
    <title>Awakening Lion-1</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Xingshi, or literally “awakened lion,” is a name for the southern style of the lion dance. Historically, it evolved from a court dance in the Tang Dynasty almost 1,200 years ago. With the southward migration of the population from the central plains, lion dance culture was introduced to the south. In the Ming Dynasty around 400 years ago, xingshi appeared in Guangdong and was then widely spread throughout southern China and even overseas. Lion dance has become a very important part of Chinese culture.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422005747 +0500" stop="20260422011145 +0500">
    <title>Awakening Lion-2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Xingshi, or literally “awakened lion,” is a name for the southern style of the lion dance. Historically, it evolved from a court dance in the Tang Dynasty almost 1,200 years ago. With the southward migration of the population from the central plains, lion dance culture was introduced to the south. In the Ming Dynasty around 400 years ago, xingshi appeared in Guangdong and was then widely spread throughout southern China and even overseas. Lion dance has become a very important part of Chinese culture.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422011145 +0500" stop="20260422011915 +0500">
    <title>Awakening Lion-3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Xingshi, or literally “awakened lion,” is a name for the southern style of the lion dance. Historically, it evolved from a court dance in the Tang Dynasty almost 1,200 years ago. With the southward migration of the population from the central plains, lion dance culture was introduced to the south. In the Ming Dynasty around 400 years ago, xingshi appeared in Guangdong and was then widely spread throughout southern China and even overseas. Lion dance has become a very important part of Chinese culture.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422011915 +0500" stop="20260422012843 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422012843 +0500" stop="20260422020413 +0500">
    <title>Rhythms of the Forest: A Sound of Li Instruments</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Li bamboo and wood instruments offer a journey into the unique sounds of Hainan's Li ethnic group. Explore the ancient craftsmanship and musical heritage, from the resonant tones of bamboo flutes to the percussive rhythms of wooden drums. Experience the natural melodies that tell the stories of the Li people.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422020413 +0500" stop="20260422021941 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422021941 +0500" stop="20260422025241 +0500">
    <title>Forged in Legend: A Glimpse of Longquan Blades</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Longquan swords, legendary blades from China, embody centuries of masterful craftsmanship. Forged with unique folding techniques and a distinctive star-patterned finish, these swords are renowned for their sharpness, resilience, and artistic value. Discover the rich history and cultural significance of these revered symbols of Chinese heritage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422025241 +0500" stop="20260422030000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422030000 +0500" stop="20260422033755 +0500">
    <title>Women of the Xiangjiang River Ep.1</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Xiangjiang River runs 800 kilometers through the whole of Hunan Province. Hailed as the mother river of Hunan, it serves as a vital waterway connecting the Yangtze and Pearl River systems. Its source is located in Yongzhou, a land of abundant water resources, rich natural treasures and outstanding people. In this episode, we focus on three young women from Yongzhou: Pan Haiying, a dance teacher; Huang Cuilan, an inheritor of brocade weaving; and Hu Xin, a custodian of Nüshu culture. We document snippets of their daily lives and work, to reflect the profound cultural heritage along the Xiangjiang River and the value pursuits of the women living on its banks.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422033755 +0500" stop="20260422034543 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422034543 +0500" stop="20260422042237 +0500">
    <title>Women of the Xiangjiang River Ep.2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we continue our journey along the Xiangjiang River in Hunan Province, to meet more outstanding women from the cities of Hengyang and Zhuzhou. By documenting snippets of the daily lives and work of a paper-cutting artist, the director of the Hengyang Huagu Opera Troupe, and an inheritor of Liling porcelain craftsmanship, we gain vivid insights into the distinctive cultural traditions of this region.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260422042237 +0500" stop="20260422043011 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>