<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="CGTN-China-Travel-CN">
    <display-name>CGTN China Travel</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/CGTN-China-Travel-CN.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416072845 +0500" stop="20260416080545 +0500">
    <title>Crossroads of Cultures: The Legacy of Silk Roads</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Quanzhou, situated on the southeastern coast of China, once served as a maritime hub of the East and Southeast Asia trade network during the 10th to 14th centuries, gaining prominence for its exceptional trading port.\nWith 22 distinctive heritage sites listed on the UNESCO World Heritage List, this city stands as a testament to the legendary history of the Silk Roads.\nIn this program, we invite four individuals living in Quanzhou to showcase their daily lives, capturing their journeys through the city's world heritage sites.\nThrough their perspectives, we present a dynamic portrayal of a city rich in heritage. From the maritime splendor of Quanzhou's history to the serene echoes of its ancient city, from the historical treasures of the Luoyang Bridge to the vibrancy of the modern urban landscape, we journey alongside our guests through time and space, exploring Quanzhou's diverse charm and unique allure. Join us as we immerse ourselves in a city that bridges history and cultures, and embraces innovation.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416080545 +0500" stop="20260416082013 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416082013 +0500" stop="20260416085143 +0500">
    <title>The Elegance of Luoyang</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Luoyang, as the eastern starting point of the Silk Road, is a city with a rich history and a tradition of cultural inclusivity. As such, it enjoys a prominent position in the heritage of the whole world.\nIn this episode, we’ll visit White Horse Temple to learn about its fascinating international background. At Longmen Grottoes, which were designated as a UNESCO World Heritage Site in the year 2000, we’ll appreciate how the unique ancient splendor is being revived by 3D technology. At the city’s annual Peony Festival, we’ll explore the significance of China’s national flower and national dress.\nInvited to a Luoyang Water Banquet, we’ll learn something about the city’s culinary traditions. And finally, a master of tang sancai, or tri-color pottery, will discuss the legacy of this ancient craft and its place in the modern era.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416085143 +0500" stop="20260416090000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416090000 +0500" stop="20260416093840 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: Hung Ga and Choy Li Fut</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In Foshan, China, Kleber meets with two masters of southern Chinese martial arts. He learns from a Hung Ga master that while this kungfu style is often associated with brute force, it’s actually a combination of hard and soft techniques that can also be used in traditional Chinese massage. Next, Kleber meets a master of Choy Li Fut, a kungfu style that utilizes everyday items such as towels, fans and even abacuses, and discovers the link between martial arts and lion dance.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416093840 +0500" stop="20260416094758 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416094758 +0500" stop="20260416102338 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: Taiji Quan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kleber travels to Chenjiagou in central China, the birthplace of Chen-style Taiji Quan. Also known as tai chi, the martial art is iconic for its slow movements and purported health benefits, but Kleber quickly discovers it’s the real deal: From being thrown around by teenagers to learning about the martial art’s Yin-Yang philosophy, Kleber experiences for himself how this kungfu style allows small to defeat big, and soft to beat strong.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416102338 +0500" stop="20260416103242 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416103242 +0500" stop="20260416110522 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: Five Ancestors Fist</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In Quanzhou, southeast China, Kleber seeks out masters of the Five Ancestors Fist, a combination of five local kungfu styles. He meets the abbot of a Southern Shaolin Temple, and takes part in the extraordinary training regime used by Shaolin monks to hone their bodies and minds. He experiences the intricacies of Quanzhou’s traditional puppetry, and learns how Five Ancestors Fist incorporated military tactics that allowed its practitioners to band together and fight off pirates.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416110522 +0500" stop="20260416111331 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416111331 +0500" stop="20260416114557 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: White Crane</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In Yongchun, China, Kleber explores the origins of White Crane kungfu and its effect on the martial arts world. He learns how its blocks and strikes were inspired by animal movements, and how acupuncture points can be used to deadly effect. After training his grip and finger strength with wooden sticks, he travels to Beijing for an introduction to Goju-ryu karate, and discovers striking similarities with White Crane.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416114557 +0500" stop="20260416115441 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416115441 +0500" stop="20260416123340 +0500">
    <title>Grand Song of the Dong — Natural Oriental Harmony</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Grand Song of the Dong is a polyphonic folk singing tradition of the Dong ethnic group. Performers from several villages gather together to sing, unaccompanied.\nThe songs, which describe the history, beliefs, customs, and emotions of the Dong people, are an important part of their cultural identity and contribute significantly to their social cohesion.\nGenerally sung in the Dong language, which has no written form, they are passed on orally from one generation to the next. Classified into various genres—including narrative and love songs, drinking and funeral songs—they are often accompanied by clapping, stomping, and dancing.\nSung on occasions such as festivals, weddings, and funerals, the Grand Song, as a valuable part of the Dong ethnic group’s cultural heritage, reflects their wisdom and creativity, as well as their harmony with nature.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416123340 +0500" stop="20260416124317 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416124317 +0500" stop="20260416131917 +0500">
    <title>Exploring Ethnic Attire: Dong Elegance</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dong clothing weaves together tradition, craftsmanship, and the unique identity of the Dong ethnic group. In this episode, we’ll unravel the stories behind the intricate designs, vibrant colors, and deep cultural significance of Dong attire. From ceremonial garments to everyday wear, each piece is imbued with the essence of a rich heritage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416131917 +0500" stop="20260416132845 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416132845 +0500" stop="20260416140545 +0500">
    <title>Crossroads of Cultures: The Legacy of Silk Roads</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Quanzhou, situated on the southeastern coast of China, once served as a maritime hub of the East and Southeast Asia trade network during the 10th to 14th centuries, gaining prominence for its exceptional trading port.\nWith 22 distinctive heritage sites listed on the UNESCO World Heritage List, this city stands as a testament to the legendary history of the Silk Roads.\nIn this program, we invite four individuals living in Quanzhou to showcase their daily lives, capturing their journeys through the city's world heritage sites.\nThrough their perspectives, we present a dynamic portrayal of a city rich in heritage. From the maritime splendor of Quanzhou's history to the serene echoes of its ancient city, from the historical treasures of the Luoyang Bridge to the vibrancy of the modern urban landscape, we journey alongside our guests through time and space, exploring Quanzhou's diverse charm and unique allure. Join us as we immerse ourselves in a city that bridges history and cultures, and embraces innovation.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416140545 +0500" stop="20260416142013 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416142013 +0500" stop="20260416145143 +0500">
    <title>The Elegance of Luoyang</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Luoyang, as the eastern starting point of the Silk Road, is a city with a rich history and a tradition of cultural inclusivity. As such, it enjoys a prominent position in the heritage of the whole world.\nIn this episode, we’ll visit White Horse Temple to learn about its fascinating international background. At Longmen Grottoes, which were designated as a UNESCO World Heritage Site in the year 2000, we’ll appreciate how the unique ancient splendor is being revived by 3D technology. At the city’s annual Peony Festival, we’ll explore the significance of China’s national flower and national dress.\nInvited to a Luoyang Water Banquet, we’ll learn something about the city’s culinary traditions. And finally, a master of tang sancai, or tri-color pottery, will discuss the legacy of this ancient craft and its place in the modern era.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416145143 +0500" stop="20260416150000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416150000 +0500" stop="20260416153840 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: Hung Ga and Choy Li Fut</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In Foshan, China, Kleber meets with two masters of southern Chinese martial arts. He learns from a Hung Ga master that while this kungfu style is often associated with brute force, it’s actually a combination of hard and soft techniques that can also be used in traditional Chinese massage. Next, Kleber meets a master of Choy Li Fut, a kungfu style that utilizes everyday items such as towels, fans and even abacuses, and discovers the link between martial arts and lion dance.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416153840 +0500" stop="20260416154758 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416154758 +0500" stop="20260416162338 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: Taiji Quan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Kleber travels to Chenjiagou in central China, the birthplace of Chen-style Taiji Quan. Also known as tai chi, the martial art is iconic for its slow movements and purported health benefits, but Kleber quickly discovers it’s the real deal: From being thrown around by teenagers to learning about the martial art’s Yin-Yang philosophy, Kleber experiences for himself how this kungfu style allows small to defeat big, and soft to beat strong.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416162338 +0500" stop="20260416163242 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416163242 +0500" stop="20260416170522 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: Five Ancestors Fist</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In Quanzhou, southeast China, Kleber seeks out masters of the Five Ancestors Fist, a combination of five local kungfu styles. He meets the abbot of a Southern Shaolin Temple, and takes part in the extraordinary training regime used by Shaolin monks to hone their bodies and minds. He experiences the intricacies of Quanzhou’s traditional puppetry, and learns how Five Ancestors Fist incorporated military tactics that allowed its practitioners to band together and fight off pirates.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416170522 +0500" stop="20260416171331 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416171331 +0500" stop="20260416174557 +0500">
    <title>Kungfu-wise: White Crane</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In Yongchun, China, Kleber explores the origins of White Crane kungfu and its effect on the martial arts world. He learns how its blocks and strikes were inspired by animal movements, and how acupuncture points can be used to deadly effect. After training his grip and finger strength with wooden sticks, he travels to Beijing for an introduction to Goju-ryu karate, and discovers striking similarities with White Crane.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416174557 +0500" stop="20260416175441 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416175441 +0500" stop="20260416183340 +0500">
    <title>Grand Song of the Dong — Natural Oriental Harmony</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The Grand Song of the Dong is a polyphonic folk singing tradition of the Dong ethnic group. Performers from several villages gather together to sing, unaccompanied.\nThe songs, which describe the history, beliefs, customs, and emotions of the Dong people, are an important part of their cultural identity and contribute significantly to their social cohesion.\nGenerally sung in the Dong language, which has no written form, they are passed on orally from one generation to the next. Classified into various genres—including narrative and love songs, drinking and funeral songs—they are often accompanied by clapping, stomping, and dancing.\nSung on occasions such as festivals, weddings, and funerals, the Grand Song, as a valuable part of the Dong ethnic group’s cultural heritage, reflects their wisdom and creativity, as well as their harmony with nature.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416183340 +0500" stop="20260416184317 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416184317 +0500" stop="20260416191917 +0500">
    <title>Exploring Ethnic Attire: Dong Elegance</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dong clothing weaves together tradition, craftsmanship, and the unique identity of the Dong ethnic group. In this episode, we’ll unravel the stories behind the intricate designs, vibrant colors, and deep cultural significance of Dong attire. From ceremonial garments to everyday wear, each piece is imbued with the essence of a rich heritage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416191917 +0500" stop="20260416192845 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416192845 +0500" stop="20260416200545 +0500">
    <title>Crossroads of Cultures: The Legacy of Silk Roads</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Quanzhou, situated on the southeastern coast of China, once served as a maritime hub of the East and Southeast Asia trade network during the 10th to 14th centuries, gaining prominence for its exceptional trading port.\nWith 22 distinctive heritage sites listed on the UNESCO World Heritage List, this city stands as a testament to the legendary history of the Silk Roads.\nIn this program, we invite four individuals living in Quanzhou to showcase their daily lives, capturing their journeys through the city's world heritage sites.\nThrough their perspectives, we present a dynamic portrayal of a city rich in heritage. From the maritime splendor of Quanzhou's history to the serene echoes of its ancient city, from the historical treasures of the Luoyang Bridge to the vibrancy of the modern urban landscape, we journey alongside our guests through time and space, exploring Quanzhou's diverse charm and unique allure. Join us as we immerse ourselves in a city that bridges history and cultures, and embraces innovation.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416200545 +0500" stop="20260416202013 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416202013 +0500" stop="20260416205143 +0500">
    <title>The Elegance of Luoyang</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Luoyang, as the eastern starting point of the Silk Road, is a city with a rich history and a tradition of cultural inclusivity. As such, it enjoys a prominent position in the heritage of the whole world.\nIn this episode, we’ll visit White Horse Temple to learn about its fascinating international background. At Longmen Grottoes, which were designated as a UNESCO World Heritage Site in the year 2000, we’ll appreciate how the unique ancient splendor is being revived by 3D technology. At the city’s annual Peony Festival, we’ll explore the significance of China’s national flower and national dress.\nInvited to a Luoyang Water Banquet, we’ll learn something about the city’s culinary traditions. And finally, a master of tang sancai, or tri-color pottery, will discuss the legacy of this ancient craft and its place in the modern era.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416205143 +0500" stop="20260416210000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416210000 +0500" stop="20260416213601 +0500">
    <title>Navigating the Hills of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>This episode explores the transportation ingenuity of Chongqing, the Fog City. Surrounded by mountains and rivers, this megacity solves topographic challenges with the Yangtze River Cableway, Asia's second-longest escalator, and a train passing through a building. From the dock culture at the confluence of two rivers to a logistics hub linking China and Europe, witness its transformation from an inland town to an economic center via the Go West policy.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416213601 +0500" stop="20260416214519 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416214519 +0500" stop="20260416222121 +0500">
    <title>Tasting the Lifestyle of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>This episode uncovers Chongqing's lifestyle, where hot pot is more than food but a city symbol intertwined with climate and history. Tracing its roots at a hot pot museum and experiencing mountain restaurants, we see its evolution from dockworkers' fare to a trendy lifestyle. Exploring graffiti streets, old teahouses and Hongyadong, we find Chongqing balances vibrancy and leisure amid modern development.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416222121 +0500" stop="20260416222925 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416222925 +0500" stop="20260416230703 +0500">
    <title>Discovering the Ancient Grottoes of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The third episode of the Chongqing Series, Humanistic Chongqing, focuses on the Dazu Stone Carvings in Chongqing. In 1999, the Dazu Stone Carvings were inscribed on the World Cultural Heritage List. As an outstanding representative of China's late grotto carving art, they integrate the essence of Confucianism, Buddhism and Taoism in their content, fully embodying the beauty of cultural integration. This episode comprehensively showcases the profound historical and cultural heritage of Dazu and its vibrant contemporary folk customs, exploring the thematic connotations, artistic characteristics and historical origins of the Dazu Stone Carvings, as well as their far-reaching influence on the local people for generations.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416230703 +0500" stop="20260416231412 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416231412 +0500" stop="20260416234857 +0500">
    <title>Three Gorges of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, through the new fashion of five-star cruise tour on the Three Gorges, with comfortable and convenient high-end experiences, we take the audience to travel along the river, multi-dimensionally show the most spectacular and beautiful landscape gallery along the Yangtze River, feel the unique charm of canyons, rapids and cultural relics on both banks, and convey the new charm of Yangtze River cultural tourism.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416234857 +0500" stop="20260416235741 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260416235741 +0500" stop="20260417003311 +0500">
    <title>Ningxia: Echoes of the Yellow River</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ningxia: Echoes of the Yellow River is a documentary focusing on the World Heritage sites and cultural–ecological conservation in the Ningxia Hui Autonomous Region. Through the lens of Ningxia’s heritage stories, the film highlights China’s commitment to World Heritage preservation, ecological restoration, and cultural continuity — presenting to global audiences a land where history and modernity intertwine, and where desert and oasis coexist.\nBy following the guardians of the Western Xia Imperial Tombs, desert restorers in the Tengger Desert, Great Wall rangers at Sanguankou, traditional sheepskin raft craftsmen, and managers of the Yellow River irrigation system in Qingtongxia, the program reveals Ningxia’s distinctive contributions to cultural heritage, natural ecology, and intangible traditions — and the enduring human spirit behind them.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417003311 +0500" stop="20260417004148 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417004148 +0500" stop="20260417011948 +0500">
    <title>The sound of casting</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>For centuries, the fires of craftsmanship have never faded in Pingyao. In this UNESCO World Heritage city once famed for trade, three ancient metalworking traditions — sword casting, gold and silver crafting, and iron forging — continue to thrive. This episode steps into the workshops where artisans shape metal with fire and devotion. Each blade’s edge, each ornament’s gleam, and each curve of wrought iron tells a story of resilience and artistry — revealing how the spirit of Pingyao’s craftsmanship still glows in the heart of time.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417011948 +0500" stop="20260417012916 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417012916 +0500" stop="20260417020625 +0500">
    <title>China's Ancient “Wall Street”: Pingyao</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we head to Pingyao – the ancient \"Wall Street\" of China and a historic banking hub. Enclosed by ancient city walls and seemingly frozen in time, this entire city, together with two nearby ancient temples, offers a one-of-a-kind adventure at this UNESCO World Heritage Site.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417020625 +0500" stop="20260417022153 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417022153 +0500" stop="20260417025232 +0500">
    <title>World Heritages in Handan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Handan, a renowned historical and cultural city in China, boasts abundant cultural and tourism resources, including the Handan Museum and Congtai Park in Congtai District, as well as the Xiangtangshan Grottoes, Guangfu Ancient City, Cizhou Kiln, etc. Handan also has a long-standing connection with the Beijing-Hangzhou Grand Canal, a world cultural heritage. As a great project created in ancient China, the Grand Canal has not only exerted a profound impact on cities along the route in terms of transportation, economy and culture, but also served as an important driving force for Handan's development.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417025232 +0500" stop="20260417030000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417030000 +0500" stop="20260417033601 +0500">
    <title>Navigating the Hills of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>This episode explores the transportation ingenuity of Chongqing, the Fog City. Surrounded by mountains and rivers, this megacity solves topographic challenges with the Yangtze River Cableway, Asia's second-longest escalator, and a train passing through a building. From the dock culture at the confluence of two rivers to a logistics hub linking China and Europe, witness its transformation from an inland town to an economic center via the Go West policy.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417033601 +0500" stop="20260417034519 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417034519 +0500" stop="20260417042121 +0500">
    <title>Tasting the Lifestyle of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>This episode uncovers Chongqing's lifestyle, where hot pot is more than food but a city symbol intertwined with climate and history. Tracing its roots at a hot pot museum and experiencing mountain restaurants, we see its evolution from dockworkers' fare to a trendy lifestyle. Exploring graffiti streets, old teahouses and Hongyadong, we find Chongqing balances vibrancy and leisure amid modern development.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417042121 +0500" stop="20260417042925 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417042925 +0500" stop="20260417050403 +0500">
    <title>Discovering the Ancient Grottoes of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The third episode of the Chongqing Series, Humanistic Chongqing, focuses on the Dazu Stone Carvings in Chongqing. In 1999, the Dazu Stone Carvings were inscribed on the World Cultural Heritage List. As an outstanding representative of China's late grotto carving art, they integrate the essence of Confucianism, Buddhism and Taoism in their content, fully embodying the beauty of cultural integration. This episode comprehensively showcases the profound historical and cultural heritage of Dazu and its vibrant contemporary folk customs, exploring the thematic connotations, artistic characteristics and historical origins of the Dazu Stone Carvings, as well as their far-reaching influence on the local people for generations.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417050403 +0500" stop="20260417051412 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417051412 +0500" stop="20260417054857 +0500">
    <title>Three Gorges of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, through the new fashion of five-star cruise tour on the Three Gorges, with comfortable and convenient high-end experiences, we take the audience to travel along the river, multi-dimensionally show the most spectacular and beautiful landscape gallery along the Yangtze River, feel the unique charm of canyons, rapids and cultural relics on both banks, and convey the new charm of Yangtze River cultural tourism.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417054857 +0500" stop="20260417055741 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417055741 +0500" stop="20260417063311 +0500">
    <title>Ningxia: Echoes of the Yellow River</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ningxia: Echoes of the Yellow River is a documentary focusing on the World Heritage sites and cultural–ecological conservation in the Ningxia Hui Autonomous Region. Through the lens of Ningxia’s heritage stories, the film highlights China’s commitment to World Heritage preservation, ecological restoration, and cultural continuity — presenting to global audiences a land where history and modernity intertwine, and where desert and oasis coexist.\nBy following the guardians of the Western Xia Imperial Tombs, desert restorers in the Tengger Desert, Great Wall rangers at Sanguankou, traditional sheepskin raft craftsmen, and managers of the Yellow River irrigation system in Qingtongxia, the program reveals Ningxia’s distinctive contributions to cultural heritage, natural ecology, and intangible traditions — and the enduring human spirit behind them.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417063311 +0500" stop="20260417064148 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417064148 +0500" stop="20260417071948 +0500">
    <title>The sound of casting</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>For centuries, the fires of craftsmanship have never faded in Pingyao. In this UNESCO World Heritage city once famed for trade, three ancient metalworking traditions — sword casting, gold and silver crafting, and iron forging — continue to thrive. This episode steps into the workshops where artisans shape metal with fire and devotion. Each blade’s edge, each ornament’s gleam, and each curve of wrought iron tells a story of resilience and artistry — revealing how the spirit of Pingyao’s craftsmanship still glows in the heart of time.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417071948 +0500" stop="20260417072916 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417072916 +0500" stop="20260417080625 +0500">
    <title>China's Ancient “Wall Street”: Pingyao</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we head to Pingyao – the ancient \"Wall Street\" of China and a historic banking hub. Enclosed by ancient city walls and seemingly frozen in time, this entire city, together with two nearby ancient temples, offers a one-of-a-kind adventure at this UNESCO World Heritage Site.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417080625 +0500" stop="20260417082153 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417082153 +0500" stop="20260417085232 +0500">
    <title>World Heritages in Handan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Handan, a renowned historical and cultural city in China, boasts abundant cultural and tourism resources, including the Handan Museum and Congtai Park in Congtai District, as well as the Xiangtangshan Grottoes, Guangfu Ancient City, Cizhou Kiln, etc. Handan also has a long-standing connection with the Beijing-Hangzhou Grand Canal, a world cultural heritage. As a great project created in ancient China, the Grand Canal has not only exerted a profound impact on cities along the route in terms of transportation, economy and culture, but also served as an important driving force for Handan's development.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417085232 +0500" stop="20260417090000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417090000 +0500" stop="20260417093601 +0500">
    <title>Navigating the Hills of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>This episode explores the transportation ingenuity of Chongqing, the Fog City. Surrounded by mountains and rivers, this megacity solves topographic challenges with the Yangtze River Cableway, Asia's second-longest escalator, and a train passing through a building. From the dock culture at the confluence of two rivers to a logistics hub linking China and Europe, witness its transformation from an inland town to an economic center via the Go West policy.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417093601 +0500" stop="20260417094519 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417094519 +0500" stop="20260417102121 +0500">
    <title>Tasting the Lifestyle of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>This episode uncovers Chongqing's lifestyle, where hot pot is more than food but a city symbol intertwined with climate and history. Tracing its roots at a hot pot museum and experiencing mountain restaurants, we see its evolution from dockworkers' fare to a trendy lifestyle. Exploring graffiti streets, old teahouses and Hongyadong, we find Chongqing balances vibrancy and leisure amid modern development.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417102121 +0500" stop="20260417102925 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417102925 +0500" stop="20260417110703 +0500">
    <title>Discovering the Ancient Grottoes of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The third episode of the Chongqing Series, Humanistic Chongqing, focuses on the Dazu Stone Carvings in Chongqing. In 1999, the Dazu Stone Carvings were inscribed on the World Cultural Heritage List. As an outstanding representative of China's late grotto carving art, they integrate the essence of Confucianism, Buddhism and Taoism in their content, fully embodying the beauty of cultural integration. This episode comprehensively showcases the profound historical and cultural heritage of Dazu and its vibrant contemporary folk customs, exploring the thematic connotations, artistic characteristics and historical origins of the Dazu Stone Carvings, as well as their far-reaching influence on the local people for generations.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417110703 +0500" stop="20260417111412 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417111412 +0500" stop="20260417114857 +0500">
    <title>Three Gorges of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, through the new fashion of five-star cruise tour on the Three Gorges, with comfortable and convenient high-end experiences, we take the audience to travel along the river, multi-dimensionally show the most spectacular and beautiful landscape gallery along the Yangtze River, feel the unique charm of canyons, rapids and cultural relics on both banks, and convey the new charm of Yangtze River cultural tourism.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417114857 +0500" stop="20260417115741 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417115741 +0500" stop="20260417123311 +0500">
    <title>Ningxia: Echoes of the Yellow River</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ningxia: Echoes of the Yellow River is a documentary focusing on the World Heritage sites and cultural–ecological conservation in the Ningxia Hui Autonomous Region. Through the lens of Ningxia’s heritage stories, the film highlights China’s commitment to World Heritage preservation, ecological restoration, and cultural continuity — presenting to global audiences a land where history and modernity intertwine, and where desert and oasis coexist.\nBy following the guardians of the Western Xia Imperial Tombs, desert restorers in the Tengger Desert, Great Wall rangers at Sanguankou, traditional sheepskin raft craftsmen, and managers of the Yellow River irrigation system in Qingtongxia, the program reveals Ningxia’s distinctive contributions to cultural heritage, natural ecology, and intangible traditions — and the enduring human spirit behind them.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417123311 +0500" stop="20260417124148 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417124148 +0500" stop="20260417131948 +0500">
    <title>The sound of casting</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>For centuries, the fires of craftsmanship have never faded in Pingyao. In this UNESCO World Heritage city once famed for trade, three ancient metalworking traditions — sword casting, gold and silver crafting, and iron forging — continue to thrive. This episode steps into the workshops where artisans shape metal with fire and devotion. Each blade’s edge, each ornament’s gleam, and each curve of wrought iron tells a story of resilience and artistry — revealing how the spirit of Pingyao’s craftsmanship still glows in the heart of time.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417131948 +0500" stop="20260417132916 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417132916 +0500" stop="20260417140625 +0500">
    <title>China's Ancient “Wall Street”: Pingyao</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we head to Pingyao – the ancient \"Wall Street\" of China and a historic banking hub. Enclosed by ancient city walls and seemingly frozen in time, this entire city, together with two nearby ancient temples, offers a one-of-a-kind adventure at this UNESCO World Heritage Site.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417140625 +0500" stop="20260417142153 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417142153 +0500" stop="20260417145232 +0500">
    <title>World Heritages in Handan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Handan, a renowned historical and cultural city in China, boasts abundant cultural and tourism resources, including the Handan Museum and Congtai Park in Congtai District, as well as the Xiangtangshan Grottoes, Guangfu Ancient City, Cizhou Kiln, etc. Handan also has a long-standing connection with the Beijing-Hangzhou Grand Canal, a world cultural heritage. As a great project created in ancient China, the Grand Canal has not only exerted a profound impact on cities along the route in terms of transportation, economy and culture, but also served as an important driving force for Handan's development.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417145232 +0500" stop="20260417150000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417150000 +0500" stop="20260417153601 +0500">
    <title>Navigating the Hills of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>This episode explores the transportation ingenuity of Chongqing, the Fog City. Surrounded by mountains and rivers, this megacity solves topographic challenges with the Yangtze River Cableway, Asia's second-longest escalator, and a train passing through a building. From the dock culture at the confluence of two rivers to a logistics hub linking China and Europe, witness its transformation from an inland town to an economic center via the Go West policy.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417153601 +0500" stop="20260417154519 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417154519 +0500" stop="20260417162121 +0500">
    <title>Tasting the Lifestyle of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>This episode uncovers Chongqing's lifestyle, where hot pot is more than food but a city symbol intertwined with climate and history. Tracing its roots at a hot pot museum and experiencing mountain restaurants, we see its evolution from dockworkers' fare to a trendy lifestyle. Exploring graffiti streets, old teahouses and Hongyadong, we find Chongqing balances vibrancy and leisure amid modern development.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417162121 +0500" stop="20260417162925 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417162925 +0500" stop="20260417170703 +0500">
    <title>Discovering the Ancient Grottoes of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The third episode of the Chongqing Series, Humanistic Chongqing, focuses on the Dazu Stone Carvings in Chongqing. In 1999, the Dazu Stone Carvings were inscribed on the World Cultural Heritage List. As an outstanding representative of China's late grotto carving art, they integrate the essence of Confucianism, Buddhism and Taoism in their content, fully embodying the beauty of cultural integration. This episode comprehensively showcases the profound historical and cultural heritage of Dazu and its vibrant contemporary folk customs, exploring the thematic connotations, artistic characteristics and historical origins of the Dazu Stone Carvings, as well as their far-reaching influence on the local people for generations.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417170703 +0500" stop="20260417171412 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417171412 +0500" stop="20260417174857 +0500">
    <title>Three Gorges of Chongqing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, through the new fashion of five-star cruise tour on the Three Gorges, with comfortable and convenient high-end experiences, we take the audience to travel along the river, multi-dimensionally show the most spectacular and beautiful landscape gallery along the Yangtze River, feel the unique charm of canyons, rapids and cultural relics on both banks, and convey the new charm of Yangtze River cultural tourism.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417174857 +0500" stop="20260417175741 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417175741 +0500" stop="20260417183311 +0500">
    <title>Ningxia: Echoes of the Yellow River</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ningxia: Echoes of the Yellow River is a documentary focusing on the World Heritage sites and cultural–ecological conservation in the Ningxia Hui Autonomous Region. Through the lens of Ningxia’s heritage stories, the film highlights China’s commitment to World Heritage preservation, ecological restoration, and cultural continuity — presenting to global audiences a land where history and modernity intertwine, and where desert and oasis coexist.\nBy following the guardians of the Western Xia Imperial Tombs, desert restorers in the Tengger Desert, Great Wall rangers at Sanguankou, traditional sheepskin raft craftsmen, and managers of the Yellow River irrigation system in Qingtongxia, the program reveals Ningxia’s distinctive contributions to cultural heritage, natural ecology, and intangible traditions — and the enduring human spirit behind them.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417183311 +0500" stop="20260417184148 +0500">
    <title>LIVING THE NEW WAVE  China's livestream shopping boom redefines e-commerce</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Now, we’re taking you inside one of China’s most dynamic phenomena—the livestream shopping revolution. From the misty tea mountains of Guizhou to Beijing’s glittering jewelry studios, millions tune in daily not just to purchase, but to connect. How did this fusion of entertainment and e-commerce become such a powerful cultural force? And what does it tell us about the future of shopping worldwide? Our reporter Lucy Lyv is here with us.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417184148 +0500" stop="20260417191948 +0500">
    <title>The sound of casting</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>For centuries, the fires of craftsmanship have never faded in Pingyao. In this UNESCO World Heritage city once famed for trade, three ancient metalworking traditions — sword casting, gold and silver crafting, and iron forging — continue to thrive. This episode steps into the workshops where artisans shape metal with fire and devotion. Each blade’s edge, each ornament’s gleam, and each curve of wrought iron tells a story of resilience and artistry — revealing how the spirit of Pingyao’s craftsmanship still glows in the heart of time.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417191948 +0500" stop="20260417192916 +0500">
    <title>INVESTING IN JOY: Inside China's new emotional economy</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Today's young Chinese generation are driving a new \"emotional economy,\" spending not just on necessities but on feelings. From trendy toys that offer joy and community, to serene scents that provide a moment of peace – they are investing in personal well-being, reshaping the consumer landscape.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417192916 +0500" stop="20260417200625 +0500">
    <title>China's Ancient “Wall Street”: Pingyao</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we head to Pingyao – the ancient \"Wall Street\" of China and a historic banking hub. Enclosed by ancient city walls and seemingly frozen in time, this entire city, together with two nearby ancient temples, offers a one-of-a-kind adventure at this UNESCO World Heritage Site.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417200625 +0500" stop="20260417202153 +0500">
    <title>The Inner Horizon: China's extreme sports revolution</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>They say in China, the most exciting frontiers aren't always on a map. A new cultural wave is sweeping the nation, turning vertical rock faces, open skies, and dense forests into new playgrounds. What was once the domain of a handful of adventurers is now a booming lifestyle for millions of young Chinese. I recently ventured out to explore why extreme sports are becoming the new national pastime, and what this reveals about the changing spirit of China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417202153 +0500" stop="20260417205232 +0500">
    <title>World Heritages in Handan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Handan, a renowned historical and cultural city in China, boasts abundant cultural and tourism resources, including the Handan Museum and Congtai Park in Congtai District, as well as the Xiangtangshan Grottoes, Guangfu Ancient City, Cizhou Kiln, etc. Handan also has a long-standing connection with the Beijing-Hangzhou Grand Canal, a world cultural heritage. As a great project created in ancient China, the Grand Canal has not only exerted a profound impact on cities along the route in terms of transportation, economy and culture, but also served as an important driving force for Handan's development.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417205232 +0500" stop="20260417210000 +0500">
    <title>The beat of the city: Inside China's booming Livehouse scene</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>From the intimate jazz vibes of Beijing's Blue Note to the electric energy of a Guangzhou livehouse — we dive into China's booming nightlife scene. Discover how these venues are more than just places for a night out — they're cultural hubs where young audiences connect, artists innovate, and the city's heart beats to a brand new rhythm.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417210000 +0500" stop="20260417213740 +0500">
    <title>Fun Guide to China: Hainan 1</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As Hainan moves towards implementing its special customs operation, CGTN’s Travelogue is launching a brand-new series, “Fun Guide to China”. Set in Hainan, the pilot episode journeys through its cities, mountains, coastlines and rainforests, capturing the vibrant atmosphere of life in the Free Trade Port.From the world’s largest stand-alone duty-free mall – a true shopper’s paradise, to the laid-back charm of an “Old Dad Tea” restaurant, host Tianran He explores the evolving cityscape of Haikou. On the northeast coast in Wenchang, he joins a local photographer to witness the launch of a Chinese space rocket, before diving into interactive space museums that bring the cosmos within reach. The journey then heads west to Danzhou, where campervans and “mermaids” share the same stage, before reaching Wanning on the east coast, where Tianran catches waves at one of China’s most famous surfing hotspots.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417213740 +0500" stop="20260417214558 +0500">
    <title>Dive into the world of foreign talent in China's movie industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>We go behind the scenes of China's fast-evolving film industry with foreign actors making their mark here. From script study to on-set cultural moments, they share how they learn, interpret, and help bring Chinese stories to life. Their journeys highlight not only China's growing appeal and openness but also the vibrant, two-way cultural exchange unfolding on the global stage.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417214558 +0500" stop="20260417222037 +0500">
    <title>Fun Guide to China: Hainan 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode host Tianran He continues his adventure across Hainan. This time, the road trip begins in Dongfang, where Tianran tucks into roast suckling pig by day and, by night, attends grassroots basketball games that rival NBA games in atmosphere. In the mountains of Wuzhishan, Tianran explores a lush jungle with forest rangers, before stepping back in time to 1988 for a retro-chic disco night. In Lingshui, the journey moves offshore as Tianran enjoys a seafood feast on a floating fishing platform, then heads back to shore to visit a contemporary art museum by the pier. After reaching Sanya in the south, he joins scuba divers on a mission to restore coral reefs, before winding down on a yacht with friends and laughter. Finally, Tianran travels to Baisha for the “La’aomen” harvest festival, where the local ethnic Li people sing, dance and celebrate their most important crop: “Mountain Orchid Rice”.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417222037 +0500" stop="20260417222941 +0500">
    <title>Personalized tours draw more global travelers to Beijing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>As China’s visa-free policy continues to attract visitors from around the world, more international tourists are choosing customized experiences in Beijing. Local guides fluent in multiple languages are helping them discover the city in their own way. Reporter Li Qiong joined oneone of the capital’s most popular guides to see how personalized tours are reshaping travel in China.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417222941 +0500" stop="20260417230457 +0500">
    <title>My Little Cricket Fighter</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we explore a time-honored form of entertainment in China that has existed for thousands of years – cricket fighting. Music, Chinese chess, calligraphy and painting, and raising flowers, birds, fish and insects are known as the Eight Traditional Pastimes of the Chinese people. Raising insects may be the last on the list, but it is a pastime unique to China. Though these small creatures are tiny, the culture surrounding them has been nurtured by the Chinese people over thousands of years, embodying the unique cultural psychology, folk customs and aesthetic values of the Chinese nation.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417230457 +0500" stop="20260417231206 +0500">
    <title>From plush toys to holograms: The growing world of AI companionship</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Artificial intelligence is evolving—from answering our questions to keeping us company. From robotic pets in our neighborhoods to holographic characters that sense our mood, AI companionship is stepping out of science fiction and into everyday life. What does this mean for human relationships and the future of connection itself? Reporter Zhang Hong explores the rise of these new companions.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417231206 +0500" stop="20260417234516 +0500">
    <title>Inner Mongolia’s Frozen Wonderland</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In this episode, we feature the Winter Nadam Fair and winter sports in Hulunbuir, Inner Mongolia. By late December, the Hulunbuir Grassland is blanketed in ice and snow. Even in the bitter cold of around 30 degrees below zero, the grassland is alive with a festive bustle.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417234516 +0500" stop="20260417235400 +0500">
    <title>Young Chinese dare to express their culture</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A fresh chapter in cultural storytelling is being written by young Chinese around the world. Young Chinese are amplifying tradition through trend, donning hanfu not only in historical lanes but in everyday life, and weaving those visuals into the fabric of social media. Our reporter Ioana Gomoi meets the creators who are turning heritage into a trendy cultural inspiration.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="CGTN-China-Travel-CN" start="20260417235400 +0500" stop="20260418002900 +0500">
    <title>Yangliuqing New Year Painting Art</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>On May 20, 2006, Yangliuqing New Year Paintings were named as part of China’s national intangible cultural heritage. The New Year painting tradition can be traced back many centuries, to the Ming Dynasty and beyond, reaching the height of its popularity in the Qing Dynasty. There are no restrictions on the themes of the paintings, and there is no blessing they cannot convey. Yangliuqing New Year Paintings are loved all over the country for their beautiful details and vivid colors—but most of all, for the good wishes they impart to anyone who sees them.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>