<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO-PL">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419005000 +0500" stop="20260419024500 +0500">
    <title>Vinci 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Cuma receives an offer to participate in a new heist.At first he refuses, but changes his mind when he learns that his old rival, Chudy, is planning a spectacular robbery in Krakow without his participation.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Juliusz Machulski</director>
      <actor>Robert Cumiński Cuma - Robert Więckiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Julian Wolniewicz Szerszeń - Borys Szyc</actor>
      <actor>Magda - Kamilla Baar</actor>
      <actor>komisarz Łukasz Wilk - Marcin Dorociński</actor>
      <actor>paser Chudy - Mirosław Haniszewski</actor>
      <actor>Marcin Kudra - Łukasz Simlat</actor>
      <actor>Jan Bednarek Werbus - Jacek Król</actor>
      <actor>Kazu Tanaka - Masakazu Miyanaga</actor>
      <actor>kurator Zjawińska - Ilona Ostrowska</actor>
      <actor>Helmut - Krzysztof Stelmaszyk</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419024500 +0500" stop="20260419044500 +0500">
    <title>Road House</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Elwood Dalton (Jake Gyllenhaal), a former mixed martial arts fighter, is hired by the owner of a bar in Florida to restore order.The woman's trouble is shady clients who often start fights.The new bodyguard uses his experience in the ring and quickly gets rid of the problem.The psychopathic Knox (Conor McGregor), who is also versed in martial arts, turns out to be a much more difficult opponent.A bloody confrontation ensues.A remake of the 1989 film with a memorable performance by Patrick Swayze.The new version stars Jake Gyllenhaal, who underwent an impressive transformation for the role.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Doug Liman</director>
      <actor>Dalton - Jake Gyllenhaal</actor>
      <actor>Ellie - Daniela Melchior</actor>
      <actor>Knox - Conor McGregor</actor>
      <actor>Ben Brandt - Billy Magnussen</actor>
      <actor>Frankie - Jessica Williams</actor>
      <actor>Laura - B.K. Cannon</actor>
      <actor>Sheriff Black - Joaquim de Almeida</actor>
      <actor>Billy - Lukas Gage</actor>
      <actor>Reef - Dominique Columbus</actor>
      <actor>Moe - Arturo Castro</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Action Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419044500 +0500" stop="20260419071500 +0500">
    <title>The Last Duel</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>France, 14th century.Marquerite de Carrouges (Jodie Comer) accuses Jacques le Gris (Adam Driver) of rape.The man was once friends with her husband, Jean (Matt Damon), from a respectable family.They shed blood together in battles, but later their paths diverged.They were divided by a fight for money and influence.Favored by Count Pierre d'Alencon (Ben Affleck), the less connected, but ambitious and educated Jacques won further honors.However, it was Jean who married a beautiful, proud and intelligent woman who also caught the attention of his companion.Now the knight must defend her and his honor.He challenges le Gris, who denies the allegations, to a duel.Not only pride and justice are at stake - if de Carrouges dies, his wife will also die.The spectacular story with stylish photos by Dariusz Wolski is based on facts.The last court duel took place in France in 1386.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ridley Scott</director>
      <actor>Sir Jean de Carrouges - Matt Damon</actor>
      <actor>Jacques Le Gris - Adam Driver</actor>
      <actor>Marguerite de Carrouges - Jodie Comer</actor>
      <actor>Nicole de Carrouges - Harriet Walter</actor>
      <actor>Pierre d'Alençon - Ben Affleck</actor>
      <actor>King Charles VI - Alex Lawther</actor>
      <actor>Crespin - Marton Csokas</actor>
      <actor>Herald at the Duel - William Houston</actor>
      <actor>Jean de Carrouges III - Oliver Cotton</actor>
      <actor>Carrouges' Priest - Aurélien Lorgnier</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419071500 +0500" stop="20260419090000 +0500">
    <title>W skrócie</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 2019, on the threshold of the pandemic.Single woman Ellen (Laura Tonke) spends New Year's Eve with her friends.No one knows that she is having an affair with Sebastian (Ronald Zehrfeld), Eva's (Antje Traue) husband.Rolf (Nicholas Ofczarek) and Dina (Pegah Ferydoni) make a perfect couple, unlike Mareike (Annette Frier) and Adam (Trystan Pütter).Maya (Katia Fellin) wants children, Natalie (Jasmin Shakeri) cannot decide.Max (Henning Flüsloh) comes into Ellen's life and he would love her if she let him.Years pass.The woman attends various types of celebrations, birthday parties and casual social gatherings.He learns about events in his friends' lives.The sense of community unites and allows everyone to return to everyday life with positive energy.Remake of the Danish film "A Long Story Briefly".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Dietl</director>
      <actor>Ellen - Laura Tonke</actor>
      <actor>Natalie - Jasmin Shakeri</actor>
      <actor>Mareike - Annette Frier</actor>
      <actor>Rolf - Nicholas Ofczarek</actor>
      <actor>Max - Henning Flüsloh</actor>
      <actor>Adam - Trystan Pütter</actor>
      <actor>Maya - Katia Fellin</actor>
      <actor>Sebastian - Ronald Zehrfeld</actor>
      <actor>Dina - Pegah Ferydoni</actor>
      <actor>Becky - Marlene Tanczik</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419090000 +0500" stop="20260419104500 +0500">
    <title>Happy Feet</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Antarctica.Mambo was born in a land famous for penguins with vocal talent.Singing gives them a sense of community and cements relationships.Unfortunately, Mambo does not have this ability.His mother Norma Jean sees nothing wrong with it, but Memphis' father fears for the future of his son who, due to his inability, may never find his soul mate.The penguin has another valuable gift - he can tap dance perfectly.However, this is not enough for his friend Gloria, the best singer in the area and the leader of the Penguin Empire, who banishes Mamba.He thinks that he doesn't fit in with the rest of the herd.While traveling alone, the exile encounters alien penguins.They are delighted with his tap dancing ability and invite him to their land.There, the penguin discovers a very important truth in life, which says that being yourself is the most important thing.An excellent family film, awarded with an Oscar and a Golden Globe.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>George Miller</director>
      <director>Warren Coleman</director>
    </credits><date>2006</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419104500 +0500" stop="20260419111000 +0500">
    <title>Kung Fu Panda Holiday</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Po's favorite holiday is approaching.Every year, the bear and his father hang decorations and cook delicacies for the villagers.This year's holidays turn out to be a big challenge for him, because he has to cope with the duties of the Dragon Warrior and become the host of a party organized only for kung-fu masters.Po finds out how difficult it will be to both fulfill his family obligations and not disappoint Master Shifu... In the Polish language version, they lent their voices to the following characters:Marcin Hycnar (Po), Jan Peszek (Shifu) and Wojciech Paszkowski (Po's father).</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tim Johnson</director>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419111000 +0500" stop="20260419130500 +0500">
    <title>The Idea of You</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Solene (Anne Hathaway) is the owner of an art gallery.One day, a divorced woman accompanies her daughter to a concert and meets her musical idol - the singer of the boy band Hayes Campbell (Nicholas Galitzine), about whom teenagers fantasize.Despite the significant age difference, they both feel that they have a lot in common.They start an affair.Paparazzi make their romantic moments miserable.The revelation of a young musician's relationship with a middle-aged single mother turns out to be a media sensation.An unusual love story with a script based on the novel by Robinne Lee.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Showalter</director>
      <actor>Solene - Anne Hathaway</actor>
      <actor>Hayes - Nicholas Galitzine</actor>
      <actor>Izzy - Ella Rubin</actor>
      <actor>Tracy - Annie Mumolo</actor>
      <actor>Daniel - Reid Scott</actor>
      <actor>Eva - Perry Mattfeld</actor>
      <actor>Zeke - Jordan Aaron Hall</actor>
      <actor>Georgia - Mathilda Gianopoulos</actor>
      <actor>Claire - Meg Millidge</actor>
      <actor>Jeremy - Cheech Manohar</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419130500 +0500" stop="20260419150000 +0500">
    <title>Chłopi</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In Lipce, life goes according to the rhythm of nature.Maciej Boryna, the richest man in the village, decides to take Jagna as his wife.Although the girl prefers colorful clothes and paper cutouts to working in the fields, and there are numerous rumors about her reputation, she cannot resist the temptation.He strikes a deal with Dominikowa, who agrees to marry his daughter to him.Soon there is a grand wedding.However, the bride is not happy.He loves his stepson, Antek, with reciprocity, which quickly becomes clear to his wife Hanka.Boryna's son is not only constantly looking for an opportunity to meet his stepmother, but also, taking pride in his honor, condemns the family to vegetation.Subsequent dramatic events cause the entire community's resentment against Jagna to turn into open hostility.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>DK Welchman</director>
      <director>Hugh Welchman</director>
      <actor>Maciej Boryna - Mirosław Baka</actor>
      <actor>Jagna Paczesiówna - Kamila Urzędowska</actor>
      <actor>Antek Boryna - Robert Gulaczyk</actor>
      <actor>Hanka Borynowa - Sonia Mietielica</actor>
      <actor>Dominikowa - Ewa Kasprzyk</actor>
      <actor>Jasio - Maciej Musiał</actor>
      <actor>Mateusz - Mateusz Rusin</actor>
      <actor>Marysia Pastuszka - Julia Wieniawa-Narkiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Organiscina - Małgorzata Kożuchowska</actor>
      <actor>Mayor Piotr - Andrzej Konopka</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419150000 +0500" stop="20260419165000 +0500">
    <title>Frieda's Case</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 1904. A seamstress accused of a crime becomes the center of a trial that exposes the injustices of the legal system.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Maria Brendle</director>
      <actor>Frieda Keller - Julia Buchmann</actor>
      <actor>Walter Gmür - Stefan Merki</actor>
      <actor>Erna Gmür - Rachel Braunschweig</actor>
      <actor>Gesine - Marlene Tanczik</actor>
      <actor>Arnold Janggen - Max Simonischek</actor>
      <actor>Bertha - Liliane Amuat</actor>
      <actor>Frau Hartmann - Bigna Körner</actor>
      <actor>Landjäger Schönenberger - Aaron Hitz</actor>
      <actor>Arbeiterin - Ramona Saluz</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419165000 +0500" stop="20260419183000 +0500">
    <title>Dražen</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1970s.Teenage Dražen Petrovic (Tonko Stosic) living in Šibenik discovers, thanks to his older brother, Aleksander (Lovre Tanfara), that he has a talent for playing basketball.At first, he trained only with him or alone - in the evenings in the gym.When his abilities are noticed at school, he joins the local team, Šibenka, where he is successful.During this time, he falls in love with Renata (Romina Tonkovic).Over time, a talented young man (Domagoj Nizic) goes to a club in Zagreb and then abroad, among others.to Real Madrid, and finally received an offer to play with the New York Brooklyn Nets team, part of the NBA league.Unfortunately, Dražen's passion for basketball also becomes his curse, and success is associated with problems in his personal life, also in his relationship with Renata.A biographical story about the outstanding Croatian athlete, called the Mozart of basketball, who was the first European to play in the NBA.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Danilo Serbedzija</director>
      <director>Ljubo Zdjelarevic</director>
      <actor>Drazen Petrovic - Tonko Stosic</actor>
      <actor>Drazen Petrovic - Domagoj Nizic</actor>
      <actor>Renata - Romina Tonkovic</actor>
      <actor>Biserka Petrovic - Zrinka Cvitešić</actor>
      <actor>Jole Petrovic - Dragan Micanović</actor>
      <actor>Aleksandar Petrovic - Lovre Tanfara</actor>
      <actor>Warren LeGarie - Valentin Perkovic</actor>
      <actor>Klara - Victoria Hauer</actor>
      <actor>Aleksandar Petrovic - Pavle Matusko</actor>
      <actor>Willis Reed - James Perri</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419183000 +0500" stop="20260419210000 +0500">
    <title>Ford v Ferrari</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The victory in the prestigious race goes to the Ferrari team every year.Henry Ford II intends to dethrone the full-time champion.He thinks about building a car that will leave the competition behind.For this purpose, he asks for help from two specialists.One of them is the temperamental fast driving enthusiast Ken Miles.The second one is Carroll Shelby, who can boast of winning Le Mans, and some time ago, due to health problems, he gave up his driving career and took up car design.They both immediately take up the challenge, even though they know that there is a long way to achieve their goal.They quickly encounter resistance from officials.It turns out that they must immerse themselves in the world of ruthless bureaucracy to take part in the twenty-four-hour race.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>James Mangold</director>
      <actor>Carroll Shelby - Matt Damon</actor>
      <actor>Ken Miles - Christian Bale</actor>
      <actor>Lee Iacocca - Jon Bernthal</actor>
      <actor>Mollie Miles - Caitríona Balfe</actor>
      <actor>Leo Beebe - Josh Lucas</actor>
      <actor>Peter Miles - Noah Jupe</actor>
      <actor>Henry Ford II - Tracy Letts</actor>
      <actor>Enzo Ferrari - Remo Girone</actor>
      <actor>Phil Remington - Ray McKinnon</actor>
      <actor>Roy Lunn - JJ Feild</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419210000 +0500" stop="20260419230000 +0500">
    <title>BlackBerry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1996. Mike and Doug, friends from their youth, run a small technology company.They create a revolutionary product, but they cannot sell it.They attract the attention of Jim, who offers to help them.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Matt Johnson</director>
      <actor>Mike - Jay Baruchel</actor>
      <actor>Jim - Glenn Howerton</actor>
      <actor>Doug - Matt Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Jasmine - Kelly Van der Burg</actor>
      <actor>Young Businessman #1 - Gregory Ambrose Calderone</actor>
      <actor>Shelly - Laura Cilevitz</actor>
      <actor>Rick Brock - Martin Donovan</actor>
      <actor>Callaghan Drummond - James Elliot Miniou</actor>
      <actor>Derek - Fuad Musayev</actor>
      <actor>Ethan - Ethan Eng</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260419230000 +0500" stop="20260420004500 +0500">
    <title>Blue Moon</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year is 1943. The legendary lyricist Lorenz Hart (Ethan Hawke), co-author of such hits as "Blue Moon" and "My Funny Valentine", spends the night from March 31 to April 1 in Sardi's bar.In the company of friends, including his muse Elizabeth Weiland (Margaret Qualley), he struggles with wounded pride and shaken self-confidence.At this time, his former long-time collaborator Richard Rodgers (Andrew Scott) celebrates the premiere of his musical entitled"Oklahoma!", which he wrote with Oscar Hammerstein II (Simon Delaney).Two Oscar nominations.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Richard Linklater</director>
      <actor>Lorenz Hart - Ethan Hawke</actor>
      <actor>Elizabeth Weiland - Margaret Qualley</actor>
      <actor>Eddie - Bobby Cannavale</actor>
      <actor>Richard Rodgers - Andrew Scott</actor>
      <actor>E.B. 'Andy' White - Patrick Kennedy</actor>
      <actor>Morty Rifkin - Jonah Lees</actor>
      <actor>Oscar Hammerstein - Simon Delaney</actor>
      <actor>Sven - Giles Surridge</actor>
      <actor>Stevie Sondheim - Cillian Sullivan</actor>
      <actor>Lawrence Langner - Michael James Ford</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420004500 +0500" stop="20260420024000 +0500">
    <title>Babygirl</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Romy (Nicole Kidman) leads a stable and prosperous life.She manages a modern, dynamically developing company, lives in a comfortable house with her devoted husband Jacob (Antonio Banderas) and two teenage daughters.Her everyday life changes when a young intern, Samuel (Harris Dickinson), appears.Despite the age difference, Romy and Samuel begin a fiery romance.The woman begins to rediscover herself, although this decision may mean the loss of both her professional position and her family.She is faced with the decision of whether to follow her own desires, risking everything she has achieved so far.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Halina Reijn</director>
      <actor>Romy - Nicole Kidman</actor>
      <actor>Samuel - Harris Dickinson</actor>
      <actor>Jacob - Antonio Banderas</actor>
      <actor>Esme - Sophie Wilde</actor>
      <actor>Isabel - Esther McGregor</actor>
      <actor>Nora - Vaughan Reilly</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Missel - Victor Slezak</actor>
      <actor>Hazel - Leslie Silva</actor>
      <actor>Hedda - Gaite Jansen</actor>
      <actor>Brack - Robert Farrior</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420024000 +0500" stop="20260420042000 +0500">
    <title>Manodrome</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ralphie (Jesse Eisenberg) recently lost his job.He barely makes ends meet by moonlighting as an Uber driver, while his partner Sal (Odessa Young) is about to give birth.Ralphie is not prepared for his new role, and his problems make it difficult for him to control his emotions.Seeing his helplessness and growing frustration, his gym friend Jason introduces him to the charismatic Dan (Adrien Brody), the leader of a mysterious group of celibate men who preach patriarchy.Ralphie, in crisis, is drawn into their world.Over time, he develops a dangerous obsession.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>John Trengove</director>
      <actor>Ralphie - Jesse Eisenberg</actor>
      <actor>Dad Dan - Adrien Brody</actor>
      <actor>Sal - Odessa Young</actor>
      <actor>Jason - Philip Ettinger</actor>
      <actor>Ahmet - Sallieu Sesay</actor>
      <actor>Son Brad - Evan Jonigkeit</actor>
      <actor>Son Aaron - Caleb Eberhardt</actor>
      <actor>Dad Leo - Ethan Suplee</actor>
      <actor>Garfield - Lamar Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Sachiel - Gheorghe Muresan</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420042000 +0500" stop="20260420060000 +0500">
    <title>Sanctuary</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Hal Porterfield (Christopher Abbott) orders room service at a posh hotel.Rebecca Marin (Margaret Qualley) shows up at the apartment to interview him for the position of general manager of this chain of facilities.Her questions become more and more personal and lead to a surprising ending.In reality, the woman is a dominatrix who follows the script prepared by Hal.However, the relationship does not follow the script ordered by the client.The woman decides to blackmail the rich man.She claims that she recorded a compromising sex tape with him.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Zachary Wigon</director>
      <actor>Hal - Christopher Abbott</actor>
      <actor>Rebecca - Margaret Qualley</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Hallway - Francisco Castaneda</actor>
      <actor>Woman in the Hallway - Kathie Young</actor>
      <actor>Older Phil Porterfield - Dominic Defilips</actor>
      <actor>Younger Phil Porterfield - Rene Calvo</actor>
      <actor>Hal's Mother - Danita Battle</actor>
      <actor>Young Hal - Christian Casatelli</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420060000 +0500" stop="20260420070500 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420070500 +0500" stop="20260420090000 +0500">
    <title>Assassin's Creed</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Recidivist Callum Lynch sentenced to death is not executed.After a fake execution, he ends up in a secret laboratory.There he meets Rikkin and his daughter Sofia.Scientists have a mysterious device that allows them to access the records of ancestors' actions stored in their genes.The criminal is to connect with the consciousness of Aguilar from Spain, who lived during the Great Inquisition and obtained the Apple of Eden, which provides control over emotions.By using this item, you can supposedly eliminate aggression in people.The daredevil travels to the Middle Ages.He discovers that he is a descendant of a member of the Assassin secret society.Over time, he learns what a big mistake he made when he trusted Sofia and her father.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Justin Kurzel</director>
      <actor>Cal Lynch - Michael Fassbender</actor>
      <actor>Sofia - Marion Cotillard</actor>
      <actor>Rikkin - Jeremy Irons</actor>
      <actor>Joseph Lynch - Brendan Gleeson</actor>
      <actor>Ellen Kaye - Charlotte Rampling</actor>
      <actor>Moussa - Michael K. Williams</actor>
      <actor>McGowan - Denis Ménochet</actor>
      <actor>Maria - Ariane Labed</actor>
      <actor>Sultan Muhammad XII - Khalid Abdalla</actor>
      <actor>Cal's Mother - Essie Davis</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420090000 +0500" stop="20260420105500 +0500">
    <title>Oscar's Eye</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Nine-year-old Oscar cannot speak.Because of this, he is rejected and bullied by his peers.However, he becomes friends with the owner of the workshop, Eric, with whom he shares a common passion - photography.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jay Silverman</director>
      <actor>Eric Conway - Beau Bridges</actor>
      <actor>Evelyn Kennedy - Jessica Parker Kennedy</actor>
      <actor>Frank Flynn - Bruce Davison</actor>
      <actor>Victor Kennedy - Scotty Tovar</actor>
      <actor>Oscar Kennedy - Miguel Gabriel</actor>
      <actor>Dermot Flynn - Ross Partridge</actor>
      <actor>Manny - Jorge Pallo</actor>
      <actor>Tony - Ayinde Howell</actor>
      <actor>Jim - Bob Bledsoe</actor>
      <actor>Conor - Ezekiel Bridges</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420105500 +0500" stop="20260420124500 +0500">
    <title>Wolfgang (extraordinari)</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the sudden death of his mother, nine-year-old Wolfgang (Jordi Catalán), an exceptionally gifted boy with features on the autism spectrum, is forced to live with his father, Carles (Miki Esparbé), whom he has never met before.An orderly nine-year-old who strives for perfection cannot stand his father's chaotic lifestyle.He wants to escape to Paris to study at the Grimald Academy and become the best pianist in the world.When Carles discovers his plan, he must make the most important decision in his life: follow his dream of an acting career or sacrifice his plans and become the father Wolfgang really needs.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Javier Ruiz Caldera</director>
      <actor>Carlos - Miki Esparbé</actor>
      <actor>Matilde - Angels Gonyalons</actor>
      <actor>Paco - Berto Romero</actor>
      <actor>Mia - Anna Castillo</actor>
      <actor>Ingrid - Nausicaa Bonnín</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Ruth Llopis</actor>
      <actor>Juana - Montse Alcoverro</actor>
      <actor>Director Serie - Dafnis Balduz</actor>
      <actor>Directora de Casting - Reichel Delgado</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420124500 +0500" stop="20260420145000 +0500">
    <title>Twilight</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Seventeen-year-old Bella Swan moves in with her father, who is the sheriff of a small town.At her new school, the teenager notices Edward Cullen.The unnaturally pale boy, who has the ability to read people's minds, is an inaccessible loner.Hoping that this will scare Bella away, Edward confesses to her that he is a vampire and that he and his entire family have been feeding on animal blood for centuries.This shocking truth does not discourage a girl in love.She and Cullen become inseparable.Their love, however, is threatened by a primal predatory instinct that is increasingly difficult for the boy to control.The couple is surrounded by wanderers hungry for human blood: Laurent, James and Victoria.The lovers face them.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Catherine Hardwicke</director>
      <actor>Bella Swan - Kristen Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Edward Cullen - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Jacob Black - Taylor Lautner</actor>
      <actor>Charlie Swan - Billy Burke</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Carlisle Cullen - Peter Facinelli</actor>
      <actor>Esme Cullen - Elizabeth Reaser</actor>
      <actor>Rosalie Hale - Nikki Reed</actor>
      <actor>Jasper Hale - Jackson Rathbone</actor>
      <actor>Emmett Cullen - Kellan Lutz</actor>
      <actor>James - Cam Gigandet</actor>
    </credits><date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420145000 +0500" stop="20260420170000 +0500">
    <title>Challengers</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Tennis player Tashi Duncan (Zendaya) has had impressive success on the court in the past.Her career was ended by an injury.Today, the woman is the trainer of Art Donaldson (Mike Faist) - her partner and father of her daughter.The man is one title short of the Grand Slam, but he is struggling with injury and age, which may ruin the pair's ambitions.After a series of defeats, the player plans to take part in the Challenger tournament in New Rochelle, New York, which is to be his warm-up before the US Open and a chance to regain his form.Unexpectedly, in the finale, Art will have to face Patrick Zweig (Josh O'Connor) - his childhood friend and Tashi's ex-boyfriend.The match becomes an opportunity for all three to confront their turbulent past.The film by Italian director Luca Guadagnino, the creator of the Oscar-nominated "Those Days, Those Nights", is a combination of a sports drama and a story about a love triangle.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Luca Guadagnino</director>
      <actor>Tashi - Zendaya</actor>
      <actor>Patrick - Josh O'Connor</actor>
      <actor>Art - Mike Faist</actor>
      <actor>Finn Larsen - Jake Jensen</actor>
      <actor>Spectator - Faith Fay</actor>
      <actor>Lily - A.J. Lister</actor>
      <actor>US Open line Judge - Scottie DiGiacomo</actor>
      <actor>Tennis man - Sid Jarvis</actor>
      <actor>Tennis spectator - Charles Massey</actor>
      <actor>Asian Cook - Keanu Ham</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420170000 +0500" stop="20260420195000 +0500">
    <title>The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>An adventure-filled journey through a magical land begins.A quiet homebody, Bilbo Baggins has spent his entire life in an idyllic hobbit village.To his surprise, the wizard Gandalf offers him a trip to Erebor.The descendants of the dwarves who were deprived of their kingdom by the dragon Smaug, led by Thorin, intend to regain their former power.Gandalf says they need the help of an agile halfling.Bilbo is drawn into a whirlwind of extraordinary events.His team must face the numerous dangers that lurk in Middle-earth.The main role is played by the excellent Martin Freeman.The cast also included Ian McKellen and Richard Armitage.The three-time Oscar-nominated first part of the spectacular film adaptation of the novel "The Hobbit, or There and Back Again" by J.R.R.Tolkien.The action takes place 60 years before the events of "The Lord of the Rings".A real treat for fantasy lovers.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Jackson</director>
      <actor>Gandalf - Ian McKellen</actor>
      <actor>Bilbo - Martin Freeman</actor>
      <actor>Thorin - Richard Armitage</actor>
      <actor>Balin - Ken Stott</actor>
      <actor>Dwalin - Graham McTavish</actor>
      <actor>Bifur - William Kircher</actor>
      <actor>Bofur - James Nesbitt</actor>
      <actor>Bombur - Stephen Hunter</actor>
      <actor>Fili - Dean O'Gorman</actor>
      <actor>Kili - Aidan Turner</actor>
    </credits><date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420195000 +0500" stop="20260420212500 +0500">
    <title>The Fountain</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Three stories about man's pursuit of immortality.16th century.In the forests of South America, Spanish conquistador Tomas Creo (Hugh Jackman), head over heels in love with Queen Isabella I of Castile (Rachel Weisz), is looking for the legendary tree of life for her.The ruler wants to use them to finally solve the problem of the power struggle with a certain high-ranking cardinal.In the 20th century, scientist Tom Creo (Hugh Jackman) tries to find a cure that will save his seriously ill wife Izzi (Rachel Weisz).A man cannot come to terms with the fact that his beloved is dying.He decides to devote himself to finding a way to overcome death.Six centuries later, astronaut Tommy (Hugh Jackman) travels through space in a glass ball.He wants to reach the golden nebula, hoping to bring Izzi back to life.A science-fiction drama by Darren Aronofsky, author of "Requiem for a Dream", "Black Swan" and "The Wrestler".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Darren Aronofsky</director>
      <actor>Tomas - Hugh Jackman</actor>
      <actor>Isabel - Rachel Weisz</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Lillian Guzetti - Ellen Burstyn</actor>
      <actor>Father Avila - Mark Margolis</actor>
      <actor>Grand Inquisitor Silecio - Stephen McHattie</actor>
      <actor>Lord of Xibalba - Fernando Hernandez</actor>
      <actor>Captain Ariel - Cliff Curtis</actor>
      <actor>Antonio - Sean Patrick Thomas</actor>
      <actor>Betty - Donna Murphy</actor>
      <actor>Manny - Ethan Suplee</actor>
    </credits><date>2006</date>
    <category lang="en">Psychological Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420212500 +0500" stop="20260420230000 +0500">
    <title>Tripped Up</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Lizzy (Leah Lewis) has always dreamed of becoming a chef.However, participating in a culinary reality show and later working in a New York restaurant became a source of frustration for her.A cooking enthusiast is one step away from giving up her greatest passion.The last chance to stay in the catering industry is to participate in a culinary festival.Together with her friends, Mary (Ashley Moore), Kai (Ariel Winter) and Taylor (Sasha Fox), she sets off on an adventure.If she fails, she is ready to look for another path in life.Unfortunately, the team has been plagued by bad luck since the beginning of the expedition.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Shruti Ganguly</director>
      <actor>Lizzy - Leah Lewis</actor>
      <actor>Mary - Ashley Moore</actor>
      <actor>Kai - Ariel Winter</actor>
      <actor>Taylor - Sasha Fox</actor>
      <actor>Patty - Vanessa L. Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ashley - Jo Ellen Pellman</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Danny Kornfeld</actor>
      <actor>Jose - Gil Perez-Abraham</actor>
      <actor>Chef Missy - Judy Gold</actor>
      <actor>Lotus - Justin Guarini</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO-PL" start="20260420230000 +0500" stop="20260421000500 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>