<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO2-PL">
    <display-name>HBO2</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO2-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416002000 +0500" stop="20260416020000 +0500">
    <title>I Saw the TV Glow</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year is 1996. Two alienated teenagers, Owen (Justice Smith) and Maddy (Brigette Lundy-Paine), reach an understanding in the school corridor.They share a fascination with the late-night TV series "The Pink Opaque."Its heroines, Tara (Lindsey Jordan) and Isabel (Helena Howard), although they live in different parts of the USA, use their spiritual bond to fight a villain called Mr. Melancholia (Emma Portner).Over time, both Maddy and Owen begin to believe that the world of their favorite production is more real than the reality in which they live.Two years later, Maddy admits to a friend that she is planning to escape.Her disappearance coincides with "The Pink Opaque" being taken off the air.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jane Schoenbrun</director>
      <actor>Owen - Justice Smith</actor>
      <actor>Maddy - Brigette Lundy-Paine</actor>
      <actor>Young Owen - Ian Foreman</actor>
      <actor>Isabel - Helena Howard</actor>
      <actor>Tara - Lindsey Jordan</actor>
      <actor>Brenda - Danielle Deadwyler</actor>
      <actor>Frank - Fred Durst</actor>
      <actor>Dave - Conner O'Malley</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Melancholy - Emma Portner</actor>
      <actor>Polo - Madaline Riley</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Psychological Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416020000 +0500" stop="20260416043500 +0500">
    <title>Battle After Another</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Pat (Leonardo DiCaprio) hides under a changed name as Bob Ferguson with his daughter Willa in a town in the desert.No one knows that in the past, this inconspicuous man was the leader of a group of revolutionaries that committed numerous acts of sabotage: his accomplices freed refugees, robbed banks and blew up government buildings.Sixteen years after the attack on the prison, the leader of the elusive gang is tracked down by his old enemy, Colonel Steven Lockjaw (Sean Penn), who was obsessed with Bob's beloved, Willy's mother.When the girl is kidnapped, her desperate father asks her former mentor (Benicio Del Toro) for help.Together they set off to search for the hostage.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Paul Thomas Anderson</director>
      <actor>Bob Ferguson - Leonardo DiCaprio</actor>
      <actor>Sensei Sergio - Benicio Del Toro</actor>
      <actor>Steven Lockjaw - Sean Penn</actor>
      <actor>Perfidia - Teyana Taylor</actor>
      <actor>Deandra - Regina Hall</actor>
      <actor>Laredo - Wood Harris</actor>
      <actor>Willa - Chase Infiniti</actor>
      <actor>Mae West - Alana Haim</actor>
      <actor>Bill Desmond - D.W. Moffett</actor>
      <actor>Tim Smith - John Hoogenakker</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416043500 +0500" stop="20260416061000 +0500">
    <title>Clerks 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After Randal and Dante's store catches fire, the friends must find another job.They still cannot come to terms with the loss of the premises, but they have no money to rebuild it.They get a job in a fast food restaurant.Soon, Dante decides to leave with his fiancée to another state.Things get complicated when it turns out that the manager of the place is pregnant.Meanwhile, Dante's bachelor party is approaching.Randall plans to organize a party whose main attraction will be a stripper.However, an unfortunate mistake occurs and things get out of control.Sequel to Kevin Smith's debut film.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kevin Smith</director>
      <actor>Dante - Brian O'Halloran</actor>
      <actor>Randal - Jeff Anderson</actor>
      <actor>Becky - Rosario Dawson</actor>
      <actor>Jay - Jason Mewes</actor>
      <actor>Gawking Guy - Ben Affleck</actor>
      <actor>Lance Dowds - Jason Lee</actor>
      <actor>Silent Bob - Kevin Smith</actor>
      <actor>Teen #1 - Jake Richardson</actor>
      <actor>Teen #2 - Ethan Suplee</actor>
      <actor>Emma  - Jennifer Schwalbach Smith</actor>
    </credits><date>2006</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416061000 +0500" stop="20260416080000 +0500">
    <title>Good Guy With A Gun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the violent death of his father, teenage Will (Beck Nolan) and his mother, Tessa Greenwood (Tiffany Bedwell), move to a small town in Illinois.There is a house they inherited from an ancestor, which the woman intends to sell.There, Will meets boys his own age and quickly becomes friends with them.The new friends are fascinated by the weapons each of them has and spend time practicing their shooting skills.Will begins to share their passion, which even worsens his already not good relationship with his mother, complicates the mourning for his father, and even puts the boy's life in danger.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>John Mossman</director>
      <actor>Duke - Dan Waller</actor>
      <actor>Jerry - Ian Barford</actor>
      <actor>Auggie - Morgan Allen</actor>
      <actor>Donelle - Liv Shine</actor>
      <actor>Tom Greenwood - Joe Swanberg</actor>
      <actor>Officer Osborne - John LaFlamboy</actor>
      <actor>Philip - David Pasquesi</actor>
      <actor>Anna - Jennifer Jelsema</actor>
      <actor>Marilyn - Elizabeth Laidlaw</actor>
      <actor>Noreen - Skye Shrum</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416080000 +0500" stop="20260416090000 +0500">
    <title>An Update on Our Family</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The filmmakers discuss the topic of vlogging by families.They tell the story of Myka and James Stauffer, who gave an adopted boy to an orphanage when he was diagnosed with autism.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Rachel Mason</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416090000 +0500" stop="20260416103500 +0500">
    <title>The Inventor</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The brilliant inventor Leonardo da Vinci cannot satisfy his enormous curiosity about the world.In search of inspiration, he leaves Italy and lives at the French court, where he can freely experiment by inventing flying machines, amazing vehicles and examining the human body.He comes up with the idea of ​​creating an ideal city and, together with the adventurous and bold Princess Margaret, tries to convince the ruler of his vision.Together they are also looking for answers about the meaning of life.However, the king expects something down-to-earth from the artist and researcher - he wants a large statue to show the world his power.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jim Capobianco</director>
      <director>Pierre-Luc Granjon</director>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416103500 +0500" stop="20260416115500 +0500">
    <title>The Grinch</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The only companion of the lonely and malicious Grinch is the dog Max. The green creature only leaves the cave in search of food.Meanwhile, the residents of Whosiów are eagerly awaiting a special time of the year, Christmas.Wanting to keep the peace, the Grinch plans to spoil the grand celebrations and kidnap Santa Claus.At the same time, Cindy-Lou and her friends intend to capture a Lappish benefactor to thank him for helping the girl's busy mother.Two opposing intentions will face an inevitable confrontation.Another film adaptation of the adventures of a character created by a children's book writer, Dr.Seuss.Previously, Jim Carrey played the green creature in the 2000 film "The Grinch: No Christmas."In the Polish language version, the characters were voiced by, among others:Jarosław Boberek, Lila Wassermann, Ewa Prus and Karol Kwiatkowski.The carol was performed by Katarzyna Owczarz, Małgorzata Szymańska, Adam Krylik and Krzysztof Pietrzak.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Scott Mosier</director>
      <director>Yarrow Cheney</director>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416115500 +0500" stop="20260416131500 +0500">
    <title>Buffalo Kids</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Tom and Mary arrive in New York to meet Uncle Niall.The relative who was supposed to pick them up doesn't show up at the port.The children, hiding in the train, set off on a journey through the Wild West.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Juan Jesús García Galocha</director>
      <director>Pedro García</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416131500 +0500" stop="20260416144000 +0500">
    <title>A Carpenter Christmas Romance</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Writer Andrea returns to her family farm in Wildwood just before the holidays.She begins an affair with her ex-boyfriend Seth, who was employed in the crew renovating the town after the recent fire.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jake Helgren</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416144000 +0500" stop="20260416155000 +0500">
    <title>Upon Entry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Venezuelan Diego (Alberto Ammann) and Spanish Elena (Bruna Cusí) decide to move to the United States.The couple successfully passed the visa procedure and packed all their belongings.It seems that nothing will stop them from building a new life in the USA soon.At the immigration area at the New York airport, they are asked to talk.Inside the cramped interior, Diego and Elena are subjected to a thorough inspection by border officers.Routine activities turn into a grueling interrogation that lasts several hours.Secrets that they never shared with each other are revealed.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Alejandro Rojas</director>
      <director>Juan Vasquez</director>
      <actor>Diego - Alberto Ammann</actor>
      <actor>Elena - Bruna Cusí</actor>
      <actor>Agent Barrett - Ben Temple</actor>
      <actor>Agent Vásquez - Laura Gómez</actor>
      <actor>Taxista - Laura Bernis</actor>
      <actor>Policia cua - Nuris Blu</actor>
      <actor>Policia sala 1 - David Comrie</actor>
      <actor>Jove - Alicia Durán</actor>
      <actor>Gos policia - Kamyla</actor>
      <actor>Policia finestreta - Colin Morgan</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416155000 +0500" stop="20260416161500 +0500">
    <title>Silicon Valley 6</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The unusual adventures of exceptionally bright new technology specialists living in Silicon Valley in California.They are no strangers to start-ups or running online companies.Programmer Richard Hendricks and his friends dream of a career like Mark Zuckerberg, the creator of Facebook.The men are extremely intelligent, they have great ideas, but at the same time they are young people lost in life and quite unpredictable in interpersonal relationships.Director Mike Judge based the script on his personal experiences when he worked as an engineer at a company near Palo Alto.Viewers will see the Satellite Award nominee Thomas Middleditch ("The Wolf of Wall Street") and Josh Brener ("The Extras") in the main roles.The series "Silicon Valley" received two Golden Globe nominations for best comedy series.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S6E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Mike Judge</director>
      <actor>Nelson 'Big Head' Bighetti - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>Bertram Gilfoyle - Martin Starr</actor>
      <actor>Dinesh Chugtai - Kumail Nanjiani</actor>
      <actor>Donald 'Jared' Dunn - Zach Woods</actor>
      <actor>Gavin Belson - Matt Ross</actor>
      <actor>Jian Yang - Jimmy O. Yang</actor>
      <actor>Laurie Bream - Suzanne Cryer</actor>
      <actor>Hoover - Chris Williams</actor>
      <actor>Spiritual Advisor - Bernard White</actor>
      <actor>Garrett - Sunkrish Bala</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416161500 +0500" stop="20260416163500 +0500">
    <title>Legend of the Boneknapper Dragon</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Gobber is convinced that the legendary dragon Gnatochrup is behind the burning of his house.When none of the neighbors want to believe in the existence of the beast, the old Viking decides to hunt the dragon that is stalking him.He is joined by Hiccup and friends to ensure Gobber's safe return.During the sea journey, they listen to more and more unbelievable stories about the rivalry between a Viking and a monster.Eventually, the travelers crash on Dragon Island, where they learn the truth about Gnatochrup.The animation is a continuation of the film "How to Train Your Dragon".In the Polish language version, the characters were voiced by, among others:Tomasz Traczyński, Mateusz Narloch, Grzegorz Drojewski and Julia Kamińska.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>John Puglisi</director>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416163500 +0500" stop="20260416183000 +0500">
    <title>Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Four high school students, as part of a punishment imposed by the principal, have to clean up the cluttered school basement.The collected items include an old console from the 1990s and the Jumanji game.Intrigued, the teenagers decide to activate the device.In this way, they are drawn into the virtual world.They end up in a dangerous jungle, where, as avatars, they are forced to fight for survival.Spencer becomes a brave adventurer, Fridge turns into a zoologist, Bethany becomes a corpulent paleontology professor who knows his way around maps, and Martha becomes a martial arts expert.On their way, they meet a guide who tells them the purpose of the mission.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jake Kasdan</director>
      <actor>Spencer - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Fridge - Kevin Hart</actor>
      <actor>Bethany - Jack Black</actor>
      <actor>Martha - Karen Gillan</actor>
      <actor>Nigel - Rhys Darby</actor>
      <actor>Van Pelt - Bobby Cannavale</actor>
      <actor>Alex - Nick Jonas</actor>
      <actor>Młody Spencer - Alex Wolff</actor>
      <actor>Młody Fridge - Ser'Darius Blain</actor>
      <actor>Młoda Bethany - Madison Iseman</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416183000 +0500" stop="20260416185000 +0500">
    <title>Secrets of the Furious Five</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After defeating Tai Lung, Po the panda gains the title of Dragon Warrior.Master Shifu assigns the bear another task - to teach kung fu.Enthusiastic bunnies become new adepts of the eastern martial art.In addition to improving his technique, Po must instill in the children the philosophy of kung-fu and character traits such as courage, self-confidence and patience.To achieve the goal, he tells them stories from the past of great warriors - the Crane, the Viper, the Tigress, the Monkey and the Mantis... In the Polish language version, they lent their voices to characters including:Marcin Hycnar (Po) and Jan Peszek (Shifu).</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Raman Hui</director>
    </credits><date>2008</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416185000 +0500" stop="20260416204000 +0500">
    <title>Esperando a Dalí</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Barcelona, ​​1974, a period of intense opposition to Franco's dictatorship.Brothers Fernando (Ivan Massagué), a chef, and Alberto (Pol López), an activist, must hide from the authorities.They find shelter in Cadaqués, a picturesque seaside village that is also the home of the famous artist Salvador Dalí (Gal Soler).In this setting, the brothers meet Lola (Clara Ponsot), who helps them find work.Fernando, influenced by Dalí's works and his infatuation with women, finds a passion for creating unique dishes.The man's ambitions grow, especially when Jules (José Garcia), Lola's eccentric father, dreams of organizing a dinner for Dalí himself.Despite the difficulties, Fernando creates a culinary masterpiece that inspires a revolution in the world of taste, which leads to the creation of the famous Surreal restaurant.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Pujol</director>
      <actor>Jules - José Garcia</actor>
      <actor>Fernando - Ivan Massagué</actor>
      <actor>Lola - Clara Ponsot</actor>
      <actor>Alberto - Pol López</actor>
      <actor>François - Nicolas Cazalé</actor>
      <actor>Luis - Alberto Lozano</actor>
      <actor>Lesya - Varvara Borodina</actor>
      <actor>Tonet - Francesc Ferrer</actor>
      <actor>Gala - Vicky Pena</actor>
      <actor>Teniente Garrido - Paco Tous</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416204000 +0500" stop="20260416223000 +0500">
    <title>The Front Runner</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Senator Gary Hart (Hugh Jackman) is extremely popular, especially among younger voters.In 1988, he decided to run for the presidency of the United States for the second time.He is considered by many to be the favorite.However, unexpectedly, his extramarital relationship with Donna Rice (Sara Paxton) comes to light.The media is publicizing this case, and Hart's career is in question... The director and screenwriter of the film, Jason Reitman, was nominated for the Festival Award at the Toronto International Film Festival.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jason Reitman</director>
      <actor>Gary Hart - Hugh Jackman</actor>
      <actor>Lee Hart - Vera Farmiga</actor>
      <actor>Bill Dixon - J.K. Simmons</actor>
      <actor>Ben Bradlee - Alfred Molina</actor>
      <actor>Irene Kelly - Molly Ephraim</actor>
      <actor>Billy Shore - Mark O'Brien</actor>
      <actor>Kevin Sweeney - Chris Coy</actor>
      <actor>Mike Stratton - Alex Karpovsky</actor>
      <actor>Doug Wilson - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>John Emerson - Tommy Dewey</actor>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260416223000 +0500" stop="20260417002500 +0500">
    <title>Insomnia</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>It's a polar summer in northern Alaska.Police officer Will Dormer (Al Pacino) arrives in the town of Nightmute with his partner Hap Eckhart (Martin Donovan).The men are to find the perpetrator of the murder of a seventeen-year-old girl.Will doesn't feel comfortable up north.The polar summer deepens his insomnia.The trail leads to writer Walter Finch (Robin Williams), who was friends with the victim.While chasing him in the thick fog, Will shoots his partner.Hap dies.In his last words, he accuses Will of doing it to prevent an internal investigation.Dormer covers his tracks by directing suspicions at Finch.A writer who witnessed Hap's murder begins to blackmail Will.Meanwhile, local policewoman Ellie Burr (Hilary Swank) is getting closer to discovering the truth behind Hap's death.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Christopher Nolan</director>
      <actor>detektyw Will Dormer - Al Pacino</actor>
      <actor>detektyw Hap Eckhart - Martin Donovan</actor>
      <actor>Walter Finch - Robin Williams</actor>
      <actor>detektyw Ellie Burr - Hilary Swank</actor>
      <actor>Pilot - Oliver Ole Zemen</actor>
      <actor>Chief Charlie Nyback - Paul Dooley</actor>
      <actor>Fred Duggar - Nicky Katt</actor>
      <actor>Farrell - Larry Holden</actor>
      <actor>Francis - Jay Brazeau</actor>
      <actor>Rich - Lorne Cardinal</actor>
    </credits><date>2002</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417002500 +0500" stop="20260417023500 +0500">
    <title>Mickey 17</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 2050. Mickey Barnes (Robert Pattinson) takes out a loan on usurious terms.Wanting to escape from an aggressive debt collector, together with his friend Timo (Steven Yeun), he joins the crew of a spaceship that is to colonize the ice planet Niflheim.However, when the second of them becomes a shuttle pilot, Mickey - not entirely consciously - becomes the person assigned to the most dangerous tasks.When he dies, in a process called reprinting, a clone of himself is created, which retains his memories.The situation of the version of man number 17 becomes even more complicated when, contrary to expectations, he is not killed during one of the missions, and when he returns to the ship, he finds Mickey 18 there. In these circumstances, the commander of the expedition, Hieronymous Marshall (Mark Ruffalo), decides to eliminate both of them.A surprising, fast-paced and humorous picture by the Oscar-winning writer and director of "Parasite", Bong Joon Ho.The production is an adaptation of the novel by Edward Ashton.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Joon-ho Bong</director>
      <actor>Mickey Barnes - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Gwen Johansen - Toni Collette</actor>
      <actor>Hieronymous Marshall - Mark Ruffalo</actor>
      <actor>Timo - Steven Yeun</actor>
      <actor>Nasha Adjaya - Naomi Ackie</actor>
      <actor>Kai Katz - Anamaria Vartolomei</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Cameron Britton</actor>
      <actor>Shrimp Eyes - Angus Imrie</actor>
      <actor>Preston - Daniel Henshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Fantasy Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417023500 +0500" stop="20260417032000 +0500">
    <title>Heated Rivalry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two ice hockey players, Shane Hollander (Hudson Williams) and Ilya Rozanov (Connor Storrie), are united not only by ambition and the need for competition, but also by a magnetic attraction that neither of them fully understands.What begins as a secret romance between two debutants turns into an extraordinary love journey.Athletes spend eight years chasing fame on the ice rink while trying to deal with their feelings off it.They must decide whether there is room for something as fragile as love in a world of brutal competition.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Jacob Tierney</director>
      <actor>Shane Hollander - Hudson Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ilya Rozanov - Connor Storrie</actor>
      <actor>Scott Hunter - François Arnaud</actor>
      <actor>Yuna Hollander - Christina Chang</actor>
      <actor>Cliff Marleau - Franco Lo Presti</actor>
      <actor>Hayden Pike - Callan Potter</actor>
      <actor>Svetlana - Ksenia Daniela Kharlamova</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #2 - Shaun Starr</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #1 - Conor McKenna</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417032000 +0500" stop="20260417042000 +0500">
    <title>Ród smoka</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The history of House Targaryen.Its leader, Viserys I (Paddy Considine), ruler of the Seven Kingdoms, decides to break with tradition.The king appoints his daughter, Princess Rhaenyra (Milly Alcock and Emma D'Arcy), as heir to the Iron Throne.This step leads to the initiation of a conflict within the family, called the Dance of Dragons.After the ruler's death, the fratricidal fight breaks out with renewed force.Also taking part in it are:Rhaenyra's brother, Aegon (Tom Glynn-Carney), and Alicent Hightower (Emily Carey and Olivia Cooke), the second wife of Viserys I. The events told in the series precede the action of "Game of Thrones" by 200 years.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E9</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Clare Kilner</director>
      <actor>King Viserys Targaryen - Paddy Considine</actor>
      <actor>Prince Daemon Targaryen - Matt Smith</actor>
      <actor>Lord Corlys Velaryon - Steve Toussaint</actor>
      <actor>Princess Rhaenys Velaryon - Eve Best</actor>
      <actor>Otto Hightower - Rhys Ifans</actor>
      <actor>Mysaria - Sonoya Mizuno</actor>
      <actor>Ser Criston Cole - Fabien Frankel</actor>
      <actor>Ser Harwin 'Breakbones' Strong - Ryan Corr</actor>
      <actor>Lord Jason Lannister - Jefferson Hall</actor>
      <actor>Grand Maester Mellos - David Horovitch</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Serial Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417042000 +0500" stop="20260417045500 +0500">
    <title>Peacemaker 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two years have passed since the last events.Chris Smith (John Cena) considers himself a real hero.However, he must earn the recognition of other heroes.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Christopher Smith - John Cena</actor>
      <actor>Leota Adebayo - Danielle Brooks</actor>
      <actor>Adrian Chase - Freddie Stroma</actor>
      <actor>Agent Emilia Harcourt - Jennifer Holland</actor>
      <actor>John Economos - Steve Agee</actor>
      <actor>Eagly - Dee Bradley Baker</actor>
      <actor>Clemson Murn - Chukwudi Iwuji</actor>
      <actor>Auggie Smith - Robert Patrick</actor>
      <actor>Detective Sophie Song - Annie Chang</actor>
      <actor>Detective Larry Fitzgibbon - Lochlyn Munro</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Action-Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417045500 +0500" stop="20260417065500 +0500">
    <title>P.S. I Love You</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the death of her husband Gerry (Gerard Butler), Holly (Hilary Swank) falls into a deep depression.On her 30th birthday, a woman receives a mysterious parcel.The cake comes with a tape with a recorded message from... Gerry.He encourages his beloved to go out and have fun with friends.After this event, new letters regularly arrived to the young widow, each ending with a declaration of love.Gerry knew how much his wife would suffer from losing him.In letters written before her death, he encourages her to take on various challenges.Thanks to her extraordinary sense of connection with the deceased, a woman in despair undergoes specific therapy and tries to start her life anew.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Richard LaGravenese</director>
      <actor>Holly - Hilary Swank</actor>
      <actor>Gerry - Gerard Butler</actor>
      <actor>Denise - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Sharon - Gina Gershon</actor>
      <actor>John - James Marsters</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Kathy Bates</actor>
      <actor>Daniel - Harry Connick Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Ciara - Nellie McKay</actor>
      <actor>William - Jeffrey Dean Morgan</actor>
      <actor>George - Christopher Whalen</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417065500 +0500" stop="20260417090000 +0500">
    <title>Insomnia</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>It's a polar summer in northern Alaska.Police officer Will Dormer (Al Pacino) arrives in the town of Nightmute with his partner Hap Eckhart (Martin Donovan).The men are to find the perpetrator of the murder of a seventeen-year-old girl.Will doesn't feel comfortable up north.The polar summer deepens his insomnia.The trail leads to writer Walter Finch (Robin Williams), who was friends with the victim.While chasing him in the thick fog, Will shoots his partner.Hap dies.In his last words, he accuses Will of doing it to prevent an internal investigation.Dormer covers his tracks by directing suspicions at Finch.A writer who witnessed Hap's murder begins to blackmail Will.Meanwhile, local policewoman Ellie Burr (Hilary Swank) is getting closer to discovering the truth behind Hap's death.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Christopher Nolan</director>
      <actor>detektyw Will Dormer - Al Pacino</actor>
      <actor>detektyw Hap Eckhart - Martin Donovan</actor>
      <actor>Walter Finch - Robin Williams</actor>
      <actor>detektyw Ellie Burr - Hilary Swank</actor>
      <actor>Pilot - Oliver Ole Zemen</actor>
      <actor>Chief Charlie Nyback - Paul Dooley</actor>
      <actor>Fred Duggar - Nicky Katt</actor>
      <actor>Farrell - Larry Holden</actor>
      <actor>Francis - Jay Brazeau</actor>
      <actor>Rich - Lorne Cardinal</actor>
    </credits><date>2002</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417090000 +0500" stop="20260417105000 +0500">
    <title>Esperando a Dalí</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Barcelona, ​​1974, a period of intense opposition to Franco's dictatorship.Brothers Fernando (Ivan Massagué), a chef, and Alberto (Pol López), an activist, must hide from the authorities.They find shelter in Cadaqués, a picturesque seaside village that is also the home of the famous artist Salvador Dalí (Gal Soler).In this setting, the brothers meet Lola (Clara Ponsot), who helps them find work.Fernando, influenced by Dalí's works and his infatuation with women, finds a passion for creating unique dishes.The man's ambitions grow, especially when Jules (José Garcia), Lola's eccentric father, dreams of organizing a dinner for Dalí himself.Despite the difficulties, Fernando creates a culinary masterpiece that inspires a revolution in the world of taste, which leads to the creation of the famous Surreal restaurant.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Pujol</director>
      <actor>Jules - José Garcia</actor>
      <actor>Fernando - Ivan Massagué</actor>
      <actor>Lola - Clara Ponsot</actor>
      <actor>Alberto - Pol López</actor>
      <actor>François - Nicolas Cazalé</actor>
      <actor>Luis - Alberto Lozano</actor>
      <actor>Lesya - Varvara Borodina</actor>
      <actor>Tonet - Francesc Ferrer</actor>
      <actor>Gala - Vicky Pena</actor>
      <actor>Teniente Garrido - Paco Tous</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417105000 +0500" stop="20260417123500 +0500">
    <title>The Front Runner</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Senator Gary Hart (Hugh Jackman) is extremely popular, especially among younger voters.In 1988, he decided to run for the presidency of the United States for the second time.He is considered by many to be the favorite.However, unexpectedly, his extramarital relationship with Donna Rice (Sara Paxton) comes to light.The media is publicizing this case, and Hart's career is in question... The director and screenwriter of the film, Jason Reitman, was nominated for the Festival Award at the Toronto International Film Festival.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jason Reitman</director>
      <actor>Gary Hart - Hugh Jackman</actor>
      <actor>Lee Hart - Vera Farmiga</actor>
      <actor>Bill Dixon - J.K. Simmons</actor>
      <actor>Ben Bradlee - Alfred Molina</actor>
      <actor>Irene Kelly - Molly Ephraim</actor>
      <actor>Billy Shore - Mark O'Brien</actor>
      <actor>Kevin Sweeney - Chris Coy</actor>
      <actor>Mike Stratton - Alex Karpovsky</actor>
      <actor>Doug Wilson - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>John Emerson - Tommy Dewey</actor>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417123500 +0500" stop="20260417145000 +0500">
    <title>Eat Pray Love</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Thirty-something Elizabeth Gilbert (Julia Roberts) living in New York seems to have everything she needs to be happy - a husband, a beautiful house and a good job.Still, she feels unhappy.One day he decides to change his life.He gets a divorce and goes on a long journey to rediscover himself.In Italy, people realize that good food, wine and time spent in the company of friends can give a lot of satisfaction.In India, she learns the power of true prayer, which allows her to find inner peace.In Bali, she discovers the joys of meditation and meets the handsome Felipe (Javier Bardem).Over time, the man becomes the love of her life.The film's script was based on Elizabeth Gilbert's autobiographical novel of the same title.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ryan Murphy</director>
      <actor>Liz Gilbert - Julia Roberts</actor>
      <actor>Felipe - Javier Bardem</actor>
      <actor>Nyomo - I. Gusti Ayu Puspawati</actor>
      <actor>Ketut Liyer - Hadi Subiyanto</actor>
      <actor>Stephen - Billy Crudup</actor>
      <actor>Delia Shiraz - Viola Davis</actor>
      <actor>Andre - A. Jay Radcliff</actor>
      <actor>Andy Shiraz - Mike O'Malley</actor>
      <actor>Bookstore Girl - Ashlie Atkinson</actor>
      <actor>David Piccolo - James Franco</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417145000 +0500" stop="20260417164500 +0500">
    <title>Sound of Metal</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Drummer Ruben (Riz Ahmed) and vocalist Lu go on tour.A passionate musician realizes that he is losing his hearing.The life he loved begins to fall apart and the future is uncertain.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Darius Marder</director>
      <actor>Ruben Stone - Riz Ahmed</actor>
      <actor>Lou - Olivia Cooke</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Paul Raci</actor>
      <actor>Diane - Lauren Ridloff</actor>
      <actor>Richard Berger - Mathieu Amalric</actor>
      <actor>Michael - Domenico Toledo</actor>
      <actor>Jenn - Chelsea Lee</actor>
      <actor>Shaheem - Shaheem Sanchez</actor>
      <actor>Harlan - Chris Perfetti</actor>
      <actor>The Man - Bill Thorpe</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417164500 +0500" stop="20260417171500 +0500">
    <title>Silicon Valley 6</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The unusual adventures of exceptionally bright new technology specialists living in Silicon Valley in California.They are no strangers to start-ups or running online companies.Programmer Richard Hendricks and his friends dream of a career like Mark Zuckerberg, the creator of Facebook.The men are extremely intelligent, they have great ideas, but at the same time they are young people lost in life and quite unpredictable in interpersonal relationships.Director Mike Judge based the script on his personal experiences when he worked as an engineer at a company near Palo Alto.Viewers will see the Satellite Award nominee Thomas Middleditch ("The Wolf of Wall Street") and Josh Brener ("The Extras") in the main roles.The series "Silicon Valley" received two Golden Globe nominations for best comedy series.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S6E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Liza Johnson</director>
      <actor>Nelson 'Big Head' Bighetti - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>Bertram Gilfoyle - Martin Starr</actor>
      <actor>Dinesh Chugtai - Kumail Nanjiani</actor>
      <actor>Donald 'Jared' Dunn - Zach Woods</actor>
      <actor>Gavin Belson - Matt Ross</actor>
      <actor>Jian Yang - Jimmy O. Yang</actor>
      <actor>Laurie Bream - Suzanne Cryer</actor>
      <actor>Hoover - Chris Williams</actor>
      <actor>Spiritual Advisor - Bernard White</actor>
      <actor>Garrett - Sunkrish Bala</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417171500 +0500" stop="20260417191000 +0500">
    <title>Hitch</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Alex Hitchens experienced heartbreak years ago.He decided that he would never fall in love again, but at the same time he decided to serve other men and share with them his knowledge about women's nature.Since then, he has been involved in a rather unusual profession - advising on how to seduce girls.He prides himself on the fact that he can turn every client into a reliable, self-confident pickup artist.Makes every effort to maintain anonymity.Despite this, he easily obtains subsequent lucrative orders.Hitchens' new client is a humble accountant named Albert, who has fallen in love with the beautiful heiress of a fortune, Allegra Cole.She feels that she has no chance because of her overweight and shyness.Alex meets journalist Sara, who is supposed to interview Allegra.He falls in love with her at first sight.It turns out that in this case his methods fail.As he gradually gains Sara's affection, she discovers his shameful secret...</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Andy Tennant</director>
      <actor>Alex Hitch Hitchens - Will Smith</actor>
      <actor>Albert - Kevin James</actor>
      <actor>Allegra Cole - Amber Valletta</actor>
      <actor>Sara - Eva Mendes</actor>
      <actor>Casey - Julie Ann Emery</actor>
      <actor>Cressida - Robinne Lee</actor>
      <actor>Geoff - Nathan Lee Graham</actor>
      <actor>Max - Adam Arkin</actor>
      <actor>Ben - Michael Rapaport</actor>
      <actor>Vance - Jeffrey Donovan</actor>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417191000 +0500" stop="20260417192000 +0500">
    <title>The Madagascar Penguins in a Christmas Caper</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The action of the film is set before the events of the film "Madagascar".The animals at the New York Zoo are getting ready for Christmas.When it's time to celebrate, Skipper, Kowalski and Rico notice that Private is not with them.The penguin wanted to find a gift for his friend, Ted, who was going to spend Christmas alone.Due to an unfortunate turn of events, instead of getting the gift, Private was bought itself.His friends come to his rescue.In the Polish language version, the characters were voiced by, among others:Grzegorz Pawlak, Jacek Lenartowicz, Tomasz Steciuk and Janusz Zadura.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Gary Trousdale</director>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417192000 +0500" stop="20260417210500 +0500">
    <title>What a Feeling</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Austria.Doctor Marie Theres Wallner (Caroline Peters) is 52 years old and has been married to Alexander (Heikko Deutschmann) for two decades, with whom she raises teenage Anna (Allegra Tinnefeld).Her previously successful life falls apart when her husband suddenly leaves her.Desperate, she goes to a bar where she meets a confident, independent immigrant from Iran, Fa Safir (Proschat Madani), who runs a carpentry business with her siblings.Even though the women are very different from each other, something attracts them to each other.If they want to be happy, they must free themselves from many limitations.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kat Rohrer</director>
      <actor>Dr. Marie Theres Wallner - Caroline Peters</actor>
      <actor>Fa Safir - Proschat Madani</actor>
      <actor>Djamshid Safir - Anton Noori</actor>
      <actor>Samira - Nicole Ansari-Cox</actor>
      <actor>Ms. Safir - Gohar Nurbachsch</actor>
      <actor>Samira - Nicole Ansari</actor>
      <actor>Anna Wallner - Allegra Tinnefeld</actor>
      <actor>Alexander Wallner - Heikko Deutschmann</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Rafael Haider</actor>
      <actor>Bigi - Barbara Spitz</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417210500 +0500" stop="20260417223000 +0500">
    <title>IO</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A donkey working in a circus performs with a young artist (Sandra Drzymalska).When he regains freedom thanks to activists, his wandering begins.During his journey, he experiences joy and pain.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jerzy Skolimowski</director>
      <actor>Kasandra - Sandra Drzymalska</actor>
      <actor>Vito - Lorenzo Zurzolo</actor>
      <actor>Mateo - Mateusz Kościukiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Księżna - Isabelle Huppert</actor>
      <actor>Ziom - Tomasz Organek</actor>
      <actor>Dora - Lolita Chammah</actor>
      <actor>Kaja - Agata Sasinowska</actor>
      <actor>Dorota - Anna Rokita</actor>
      <actor>Zenek - Michał Przybysławski</actor>
      <actor>Zea - Gloria Iradukunda</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417223000 +0500" stop="20260417235500 +0500">
    <title>The Addams Family</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Gomez and Morticia Addams are looking for a safe place to live and raise their children.Therefore, they move to a dark, abandoned mansion in New Jersey.The estate is surrounded by swamps and hidden on top of a mountain amidst thick fog.13 years have passed.Gomez teaches the family's traditional saber fighting to Pugslay's son.Meanwhile, Morticia must face daughter Wednesday's questions about life outside the mansion gates.Soon, TV star Margaux Needler appears in the area and starts building a modern housing estate.Her plans are hindered by the fact that the Addams residence does not fit the modernist vision of the theme park.The woman decides to get rid of the strange family.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Conrad Vernon</director>
      <director>Greg Tiernan</director>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417235500 +0500" stop="20260418012500 +0500">
    <title>The Fountain</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Three stories about man's pursuit of immortality.16th century.In the forests of South America, Spanish conquistador Tomas Creo (Hugh Jackman), head over heels in love with Queen Isabella I of Castile (Rachel Weisz), is looking for the legendary tree of life for her.The ruler wants to use them to finally solve the problem of the power struggle with a certain high-ranking cardinal.In the 20th century, scientist Tom Creo (Hugh Jackman) tries to find a cure that will save his seriously ill wife Izzi (Rachel Weisz).A man cannot come to terms with the fact that his beloved is dying.He decides to devote himself to finding a way to overcome death.Six centuries later, astronaut Tommy (Hugh Jackman) travels through space in a glass ball.He wants to reach the golden nebula, hoping to bring Izzi back to life.A science-fiction drama by Darren Aronofsky, author of "Requiem for a Dream", "Black Swan" and "The Wrestler".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Darren Aronofsky</director>
      <actor>Tomas - Hugh Jackman</actor>
      <actor>Isabel - Rachel Weisz</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Lillian Guzetti - Ellen Burstyn</actor>
      <actor>Father Avila - Mark Margolis</actor>
      <actor>Grand Inquisitor Silecio - Stephen McHattie</actor>
      <actor>Lord of Xibalba - Fernando Hernandez</actor>
      <actor>Captain Ariel - Cliff Curtis</actor>
      <actor>Antonio - Sean Patrick Thomas</actor>
      <actor>Betty - Donna Murphy</actor>
      <actor>Manny - Ethan Suplee</actor>
    </credits><date>2006</date>
    <category lang="en">Psychological Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>