<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO2-PL">
    <display-name>HBO2</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO2-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420042500 +0500" stop="20260420070000 +0500">
    <title>Battle After Another</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Pat (Leonardo DiCaprio) hides under a changed name as Bob Ferguson with his daughter Willa in a town in the desert.No one knows that in the past, this inconspicuous man was the leader of a group of revolutionaries that committed numerous acts of sabotage: his accomplices freed refugees, robbed banks and blew up government buildings.Sixteen years after the attack on the prison, the leader of the elusive gang is tracked down by his old enemy, Colonel Steven Lockjaw (Sean Penn), who was obsessed with Bob's beloved, Willy's mother.When the girl is kidnapped, her desperate father asks her former mentor (Benicio Del Toro) for help.Together they set off to search for the hostage.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Paul Thomas Anderson</director>
      <actor>Bob Ferguson - Leonardo DiCaprio</actor>
      <actor>Sensei Sergio - Benicio Del Toro</actor>
      <actor>Steven Lockjaw - Sean Penn</actor>
      <actor>Perfidia - Teyana Taylor</actor>
      <actor>Deandra - Regina Hall</actor>
      <actor>Laredo - Wood Harris</actor>
      <actor>Willa - Chase Infiniti</actor>
      <actor>Mae West - Alana Haim</actor>
      <actor>Bill Desmond - D.W. Moffett</actor>
      <actor>Tim Smith - John Hoogenakker</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420070000 +0500" stop="20260420090000 +0500">
    <title>Macbeth</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Macbeth returns from his war expedition.The witches predict a great future for him.The man's ambition and lust for power awaken, additionally fueled by his wife.However, his path to the throne will be bloody.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Justin Kurzel</director>
      <actor>Makbet - Michael Fassbender</actor>
      <actor>Lady Makbet - Marion Cotillard</actor>
      <actor>Banquo - Paddy Considine</actor>
      <actor>Fleance - Lochlann Harris</actor>
      <actor>Young Witch - Kayla Fallon</actor>
      <actor>Middle-Aged Witch - Lynn Kennedy</actor>
      <actor>Older Witch - Seylan Mhairi Baxter</actor>
      <actor>Child Witch - Amber Rissmann</actor>
      <actor>Young Boy Soldier - Scot Greenan</actor>
      <actor>Macdonwald - Hilton McRae</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420090000 +0500" stop="20260420103500 +0500">
    <title>Long Good Thursday</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Finland.A widowed farmer becomes a model for the eccentric artist Saimi.A feeling develops between them.This does not please the man's adult sons, who are afraid of losing their property.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mika Kaurismäki</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420103500 +0500" stop="20260420124500 +0500">
    <title>Monsieur Aznavour</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Paris, 1930s. The son of immigrants takes part in a theater performance.This is how he discovers his vocal talent and decides to become a singer.A breakthrough in his career was his meeting with Edith Piaf.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mehdi Idir</director>
      <director>Grand Corps Malade</director>
      <actor>Charles Aznavour - Tahar Rahim</actor>
      <actor>Pierre Roche - Bastien Bouillon</actor>
      <actor>Edith Piaf - Marie-Julie Baup</actor>
      <actor>Aida Aznavour - Camille Moutawakil</actor>
      <actor>Micheline Rugel - Ella Pellegrini</actor>
      <actor>Knar Aznavourian - Narine Grigoryan</actor>
      <actor>Mischa Aznavourian - Hovnatan Avédikian</actor>
      <actor>Ulla Thorsell - Petra Silander</actor>
      <actor>Raoul Breton - Luc Antoni</actor>
      <actor>Jean-Louis Marquet - Nicolas Chupin</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420124500 +0500" stop="20260420145500 +0500">
    <title>Noah: Chosen by God</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The distant past.Due to the wickedness of Cain's descendants, the inhabitants of large cities, the world is falling into decline.Only representatives of the House of Set still carry out the will of the Creator.One night, former warrior and healer Noah (Russell Crowe) has a terrible dream.He sees it as a gigantic flood that destroys the world.Along with his wife Naameh (Jennifer Connelly) and three sons, he visits his grandfather Methuselah (Anthony Hopkins) to seek his advice.He discovers that his dream is actually a prediction of the great flood.Noah becomes aware that he has been chosen by the Creator to save the lives of innocents.With the help of stone giants called Guardians, he begins work on an ark that will be a shelter for various animal species.Years later, when the specter of disaster becomes more and more real, the huge ship is almost ready.Then the descendant of the first murderer, the self-proclaimed ruler Tubal-kain (Ray Winstone), demands a place in the ark for himself and his subjects.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Darren Aronofsky</director>
      <actor>Noah - Russell Crowe</actor>
      <actor>Naameh - Jennifer Connelly</actor>
      <actor>Tubal-cain - Ray Winstone</actor>
      <actor>Methuselah - Anthony Hopkins</actor>
      <actor>Ila - Emma Watson</actor>
      <actor>Ham - Logan Lerman</actor>
      <actor>Shem - Douglas Booth</actor>
      <actor>Samyaza - Nick Nolte</actor>
      <actor>Magog - Mark Margolis</actor>
      <actor>Rameel - Kevin Durand</actor>
    </credits><date>2014</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420145500 +0500" stop="20260420162000 +0500">
    <title>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The ninja turtles defeated their eternal enemy Shredder and each of them found a different job.Michaelangelo makes money at children's parties as a mascot.Donatello works as a telephone operator, and Leonardo exercises his character in solitude.Only Raphael remained faithful to his old ideals and fights hooligans at night.Meanwhile, Master Splinter begins to see signs of impending danger.Immortal entrepreneur, Maximilian J. Winters decides to take control of New York, and later the entire world.To do this, he summons his four stone generals and tries to open the gate to another dimension.Only a team of Teenage Mutant Turtles can stop him.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kevin Munroe</director>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420162000 +0500" stop="20260420165000 +0500">
    <title>Silicon Valley 6</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Maximizing Alphaness</sub-title>
    <desc>The unusual adventures of exceptionally bright new technology specialists living in Silicon Valley in California.They are no strangers to start-ups or running online companies.Programmer Richard Hendricks and his friends dream of a career like Mark Zuckerberg, the creator of Facebook.The men are extremely intelligent, they have great ideas, but at the same time they are young people lost in life and quite unpredictable in interpersonal relationships.Director Mike Judge based the script on his personal experiences when he worked as an engineer at a company near Palo Alto.Viewers will see the Satellite Award nominee Thomas Middleditch ("The Wolf of Wall Street") and Josh Brener ("The Extras") in the main roles.The series "Silicon Valley" received two Golden Globe nominations for best comedy series.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S6E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Liza Johnson</director>
      <actor>Nelson 'Big Head' Bighetti - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>Bertram Gilfoyle - Martin Starr</actor>
      <actor>Dinesh Chugtai - Kumail Nanjiani</actor>
      <actor>Donald 'Jared' Dunn - Zach Woods</actor>
      <actor>Gavin Belson - Matt Ross</actor>
      <actor>Jian Yang - Jimmy O. Yang</actor>
      <actor>Laurie Bream - Suzanne Cryer</actor>
      <actor>Hoover - Chris Williams</actor>
      <actor>Spiritual Advisor - Bernard White</actor>
      <actor>Garrett - Sunkrish Bala</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420165000 +0500" stop="20260420183000 +0500">
    <title>The Jane Austen Book Club</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Sacramento, California.The husband leaves Sylvia (Amy Brenneman) for another woman.Two friends of the broken woman, Bernadette (Kathy Baker) and Jocelyn (Maria Bello), decide to help her regain balance in an original way.They establish a literary club bringing together people who share the same passion - literature by Jane Austen.For half a year, Sylvia, her friends, daughter Allegra (Maggie Grace), young teacher Prudie (Emily Blunt) and science-fiction lover Grigg (Hugh Dancy), meet and discuss six more novels by their favorite author.Together they discover that the stories created by the English writer are timeless.Regular meetings also allow club members to look at their own lives from a distance and deal with the problems that concern them.Based on the best-selling book by Karen Joy Fowler, the film was well received by audiences and critics.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Robin Swicord</director>
      <actor>Jocelyn - Maria Bello</actor>
      <actor>Prudie Drummond - Emily Blunt</actor>
      <actor>Bernadette - Kathy Baker</actor>
      <actor>Sylvia Avila - Amy Brenneman</actor>
      <actor>Allegra Avila - Maggie Grace</actor>
      <actor>Grigg Harris - Hugh Dancy</actor>
      <actor>Daniel Avila - Jimmy Smits</actor>
      <actor>Pastor - Ed Brigadier</actor>
      <actor>Trey - Kevin Zegers</actor>
      <actor>Dean Drummond - Marc Blucas</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420183000 +0500" stop="20260420191500 +0500">
    <title>Doc Ii.</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dr. Amy Larsen, former chief of internal medicine, is rebuilding her life after a tragic accident that left her with no memory.Now she is an intern.Her past still haunts me.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E11</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Russell Lee Fine</director>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420191500 +0500" stop="20260420205500 +0500">
    <title>Robot Dreams</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A lonely and timid Dog lives in colorful, bustling New York.Distrustful, he barricades himself in his apartment and looks at the noisy city with regret.The cure for his fears turns out to be a Robot, which the pet orders under the influence of an advertisement.When the parcel arrives, the dog assembles the sent model.It comes to life and immediately becomes the dog's best friend.From then on, the friends spend fun-filled days together.They go roller skating, eat hot dogs, listen to music and walk the streets of the metropolis.They are inseparable.However, their happy life together ends with a trip to the beach.Bathing in the sea has a tragic ending for Robot - he cannot move and has to stay in a sandy, closed area.The distraught Dog is unable to move it himself.However, she does everything to get him out of there.Once again he must overcome his fear of the world.His immobilized friend also dreams of the day when they will finally meet again.An Oscar-nominated animation based on a comic book by Sara Varon.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Pablo Berger</director>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420205500 +0500" stop="20260420223000 +0500">
    <title>Marmalade</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The quiet Baron (Joe Keery) is sent to prison.She shares a cell with Otis (Aldis Hodge), who has escaped several times from prisons.Initially reluctant, the boy agrees to help him get released when the boy offers him $250,000.When asked where he got the money, Baron tells his story.He lived in a small town with his bedridden mother, Eda (Amy Warner).He supported her and himself by working at the post office.However, he lost his job when he refused to cut his hair.Baron's life was changed by the arrival of the hit Marmalade (Camila Morrone), traumatized by her childhood spent in a foster family, in town.Gradually their relationship became closer.Fascinated by the girl, the simple-minded Baron agreed to rob a bank with her, especially since he lacked money to pay for his mother's medicines.Unfortunately, the plan failed because Marmalade started the jump impulsively.In addition, her actions led to a series of tragic events.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Keir O'Donnell</director>
      <actor>Detective Gray - Ozioma Akagha</actor>
      <actor>Don - Wayne Duvall</actor>
      <actor>Officer Cambio - Hans Christopher</actor>
      <actor>Mama Eda - Amy Warner</actor>
      <actor>Ms. Jenkins - Susan Brava</actor>
      <actor>Sandy - Jane Hammill</actor>
      <actor>Teen Employee - Phoenicia Gamble</actor>
      <actor>Gary - Jim Lichtscheidl</actor>
      <actor>Chief Dixon - Andrew Wheeler</actor>
      <actor>Checkpoint Officer - Toussaint Morrison</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260420223000 +0500" stop="20260421004000 +0500">
    <title>Mickey 17</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 2050. Mickey Barnes (Robert Pattinson) takes out a loan on usurious terms.Wanting to escape from an aggressive debt collector, together with his friend Timo (Steven Yeun), he joins the crew of a spaceship that is to colonize the ice planet Niflheim.However, while the second of them becomes a shuttle pilot, Mickey - not entirely consciously - becomes the person assigned to the most dangerous tasks.When he dies, in a process called reprinting, a clone of himself is created, which retains his memories.The situation of the version of man number 17 becomes even more complicated when, contrary to expectations, he is not killed during one of the missions, and when he returns to the ship, he finds Mickey 18 there. In these circumstances, the commander of the expedition, Hieronymous Marshall (Mark Ruffalo), decides to eliminate both of them.A surprising, fast-paced and humorous picture by the Oscar-winning writer and director of "Parasite", Bong Joon Ho.The production is an adaptation of the novel by Edward Ashton.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Joon-ho Bong</director>
      <actor>Mickey Barnes - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Gwen Johansen - Toni Collette</actor>
      <actor>Hieronymous Marshall - Mark Ruffalo</actor>
      <actor>Timo - Steven Yeun</actor>
      <actor>Nasha Adjaya - Naomi Ackie</actor>
      <actor>Kai Katz - Anamaria Vartolomei</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Cameron Britton</actor>
      <actor>Shrimp Eyes - Angus Imrie</actor>
      <actor>Preston - Daniel Henshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Fantasy Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421004000 +0500" stop="20260421022000 +0500">
    <title>Until Dawn</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Clover and her friends go to the valley where her sister disappeared.They become the target of a murderer.Their story repeats itself every morning.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David F. Sandberg</director>
      <actor>Clover - Ella Rubin</actor>
      <actor>Max - Michael Cimino</actor>
      <actor>Nina - Odessa A'zion</actor>
      <actor>Megan - Ji-young Yoo</actor>
      <actor>Abe - Belmont Cameli</actor>
      <actor>Melanie - Maia Mitchell</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Hill - Peter Stormare</actor>
      <actor>Psycho - Tibor Szauerwein</actor>
      <actor>Reporter - Lotta Losten</actor>
      <actor>Glore Witch - Mariann Hermányi</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421022000 +0500" stop="20260421040500 +0500">
    <title>Good Guy With A Gun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the violent death of his father, teenage Will (Beck Nolan) and his mother, Tessa Greenwood (Tiffany Bedwell), move to a small town in Illinois.There is a house they inherited from an ancestor, which the woman intends to sell.There, Will meets boys his own age and quickly becomes friends with them.The new friends are fascinated by the weapons each of them has and spend time practicing their shooting skills.Will begins to share their passion, which even worsens his already not good relationship with his mother, complicates the mourning for his father, and even puts the boy's life in danger.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>John Mossman</director>
      <actor>Duke - Dan Waller</actor>
      <actor>Jerry - Ian Barford</actor>
      <actor>Auggie - Morgan Allen</actor>
      <actor>Donelle - Liv Shine</actor>
      <actor>Tom Greenwood - Joe Swanberg</actor>
      <actor>Officer Osborne - John LaFlamboy</actor>
      <actor>Philip - David Pasquesi</actor>
      <actor>Anna - Jennifer Jelsema</actor>
      <actor>Marilyn - Elizabeth Laidlaw</actor>
      <actor>Noreen - Skye Shrum</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421040500 +0500" stop="20260421061000 +0500">
    <title>Bastarden</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Year 1755, Denmark.The impoverished Captain Ludvig (Mads Mikkelsen) asks the king for permission to establish a colony on his behalf on the barren moors famous for their infertility.If successful, he expects to be awarded a knighthood and property.The aristocrats are outraged by his arrogance and assume defeat, but he receives consent.From then on, every day for Ludvig and his relatives is spent on hard, physical work beyond their strength, which will allow them to prepare the land for cultivation.They also hire people to help them - two runaway servants: Ann Barbara (Amanda Collin) and her husband.Months pass and the first buildings are built when the ruthless Frederik de Schinkel (Simon Bennebjerg), the land lord, tries to take over the moors.When Ludvig rejects his offer, he decides to destroy it.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nikolaj Arcel</director>
      <actor>Ludvig Kahlen - Mads Mikkelsen</actor>
      <actor>Ann Barbara - Amanda Collin</actor>
      <actor>Frederik De Schinkel - Simon Bennebjerg</actor>
      <actor>Anmai Mus - Melina Hagberg</actor>
      <actor>Edel Helene - Kristine Kujath Thorp</actor>
      <actor>Anton Eklund - Gustav Lindh</actor>
      <actor>Johannes Eriksen - Morten Hee Andersen</actor>
      <actor>Bondo - Thomas W. Gabrielsson</actor>
      <actor>Trappaud - Jacob Lohmann</actor>
      <actor>Hector - Magnus Krepper</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421061000 +0500" stop="20260421063500 +0500">
    <title>Hollywood On Set 23</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E16</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421063500 +0500" stop="20260421090000 +0500">
    <title>Mickey 17</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 2050. Mickey Barnes (Robert Pattinson) takes out a loan on usurious terms.Wanting to escape from an aggressive debt collector, together with his friend Timo (Steven Yeun), he joins the crew of a spaceship that is to colonize the ice planet Niflheim.However, while the second of them becomes a shuttle pilot, Mickey - not entirely consciously - becomes the person assigned to the most dangerous tasks.When he dies, in a process called reprinting, a clone of himself is created, which retains his memories.The situation of the version of man number 17 becomes even more complicated when, contrary to expectations, he is not killed during one of the missions, and when he returns to the ship, he finds Mickey 18 there. In these circumstances, the commander of the expedition, Hieronymous Marshall (Mark Ruffalo), decides to eliminate both of them.A surprising, fast-paced and humorous picture by the Oscar-winning writer and director of "Parasite", Bong Joon Ho.The production is an adaptation of the novel by Edward Ashton.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Joon-ho Bong</director>
      <actor>Mickey Barnes - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Gwen Johansen - Toni Collette</actor>
      <actor>Hieronymous Marshall - Mark Ruffalo</actor>
      <actor>Timo - Steven Yeun</actor>
      <actor>Nasha Adjaya - Naomi Ackie</actor>
      <actor>Kai Katz - Anamaria Vartolomei</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Cameron Britton</actor>
      <actor>Shrimp Eyes - Angus Imrie</actor>
      <actor>Preston - Daniel Henshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Fantasy Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421090000 +0500" stop="20260421103500 +0500">
    <title>Robot Dreams</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A lonely and timid Dog lives in colorful, bustling New York.Distrustful, he barricades himself in his apartment and looks at the noisy city with regret.The cure for his fears turns out to be a Robot, which the pet orders under the influence of an advertisement.When the parcel arrives, the dog assembles the sent model.It comes to life and immediately becomes the dog's best friend.From then on, the friends spend fun-filled days together.They go roller skating, eat hot dogs, listen to music and walk the streets of the metropolis.They are inseparable.However, their happy life together ends with a trip to the beach.Bathing in the sea has a tragic ending for Robot - he cannot move and has to stay in a sandy, closed area.The distraught Dog is unable to move it himself.However, she does everything to get him out of there.Once again he must overcome his fear of the world.His immobilized friend also dreams of the day when they will finally meet again.An Oscar-nominated animation based on a comic book by Sara Varon.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Pablo Berger</director>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421103500 +0500" stop="20260421121000 +0500">
    <title>Marmalade</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The quiet Baron (Joe Keery) is sent to prison.She shares a cell with Otis (Aldis Hodge), who has escaped several times from prisons.Initially reluctant, the boy agrees to help him get released when the boy offers him $250,000.When asked where he got the money, Baron tells his story.He lived in a small town with his bedridden mother, Eda (Amy Warner).He supported her and himself by working at the post office.However, he lost his job when he refused to cut his hair.Baron's life was changed by the arrival of the hit Marmalade (Camila Morrone), traumatized by her childhood spent in a foster family, in town.Gradually their relationship became closer.Fascinated by the girl, the simple-minded Baron agreed to rob a bank with her, especially since he lacked money to pay for his mother's medicines.Unfortunately, the plan failed because Marmalade started the jump impulsively.In addition, her actions led to a series of tragic events.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Keir O'Donnell</director>
      <actor>Detective Gray - Ozioma Akagha</actor>
      <actor>Don - Wayne Duvall</actor>
      <actor>Officer Cambio - Hans Christopher</actor>
      <actor>Mama Eda - Amy Warner</actor>
      <actor>Ms. Jenkins - Susan Brava</actor>
      <actor>Sandy - Jane Hammill</actor>
      <actor>Teen Employee - Phoenicia Gamble</actor>
      <actor>Gary - Jim Lichtscheidl</actor>
      <actor>Chief Dixon - Andrew Wheeler</actor>
      <actor>Checkpoint Officer - Toussaint Morrison</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421121000 +0500" stop="20260421134500 +0500">
    <title>El bus de la vida</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Music teacher Andrés (Dani Rovira) lives in the Basque Country.He is soon diagnosed with cancer, which forces him to often visit the hospital in Bilbao.To get to the facility for treatment, he regularly uses an old bus driven by Mai (Susana Abaitua), who transports him and other cancer patients free of charge.Thanks to conversations with other passengers, the teacher manages to control his fear and look to the future with hope.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ibon Cormenzana</director>
      <actor>Clara - Miriam Rubio</actor>
      <actor>David - Julen Castillo</actor>
      <actor>Unai - Pablo Scapigliati</actor>
      <actor>Doctor Orduna - Javier Tolosa</actor>
      <actor>Manuela - Elena Irureta</actor>
      <actor>Santi - Antonio Durán Morris</actor>
      <actor>Itziar - Amancay Gaztanaga</actor>
      <actor>Luna - Araia Díaz</actor>
      <actor>Antxon - Anartz Zuazua</actor>
      <actor>Txaran - Inigo de la Iglesia</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421134500 +0500" stop="20260421153500 +0500">
    <title>What a Feeling</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Austria.Doctor Marie Theres Wallner (Caroline Peters) is 52 years old and has been married to Alexander (Heikko Deutschmann) for two decades, with whom she raises teenage Anna (Allegra Tinnefeld).Her previously successful life falls apart when her husband suddenly leaves her.Desperate, she goes to a bar where she meets a confident, independent immigrant from Iran, Fa Safir (Proschat Madani), who runs a carpentry business with her siblings.Even though the women are very different from each other, something attracts them to each other.If they want to be happy, they must free themselves from many limitations.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kat Rohrer</director>
      <actor>Dr. Marie Theres Wallner - Caroline Peters</actor>
      <actor>Fa Safir - Proschat Madani</actor>
      <actor>Djamshid Safir - Anton Noori</actor>
      <actor>Samira - Nicole Ansari-Cox</actor>
      <actor>Ms. Safir - Gohar Nurbachsch</actor>
      <actor>Samira - Nicole Ansari</actor>
      <actor>Anna Wallner - Allegra Tinnefeld</actor>
      <actor>Alexander Wallner - Heikko Deutschmann</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Rafael Haider</actor>
      <actor>Bigi - Barbara Spitz</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421153500 +0500" stop="20260421160500 +0500">
    <title>Silicon Valley 6</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Tethics</sub-title>
    <desc>The unusual adventures of exceptionally bright new technology specialists living in Silicon Valley in California.They are no strangers to start-ups or running online companies.Programmer Richard Hendricks and his friends dream of a career like Mark Zuckerberg, the creator of Facebook.The men are extremely intelligent, they have great ideas, but at the same time they are young people lost in life and quite unpredictable in interpersonal relationships.Director Mike Judge based the script on his personal experiences when he worked as an engineer at a company near Palo Alto.Viewers will see the Satellite Award nominee Thomas Middleditch ("The Wolf of Wall Street") and Josh Brener ("The Extras") in the main roles.The series "Silicon Valley" received two Golden Globe nominations for best comedy series.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S6E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Pete Chatmon</director>
      <actor>Nelson 'Big Head' Bighetti - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>Bertram Gilfoyle - Martin Starr</actor>
      <actor>Dinesh Chugtai - Kumail Nanjiani</actor>
      <actor>Donald 'Jared' Dunn - Zach Woods</actor>
      <actor>Gavin Belson - Matt Ross</actor>
      <actor>Jian Yang - Jimmy O. Yang</actor>
      <actor>Laurie Bream - Suzanne Cryer</actor>
      <actor>Hoover - Chris Williams</actor>
      <actor>Spiritual Advisor - Bernard White</actor>
      <actor>Garrett - Sunkrish Bala</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421160500 +0500" stop="20260421174500 +0500">
    <title>Maid in Manhattan</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>New York.Divorcee Marisa Ventura (Jennifer Lopez) raises her son alone.She works as a maid at the luxurious Beresford Hotel in Manhattan.While cleaning the apartment of aristocrat Caroline Lane (Natasha Richardson), the woman tries on her elegant outfit, in which she looks exceptionally nice.Another hotel guest sees her so changed.He is lawyer Christopher Matthew (Ralph Fiennes), running for parliament.He takes Marisa as a person of a similar social status to himself.They go for a walk together and then eat dinner together.The woman cannot bring herself to correct the mistake, especially since she likes Christopher.However, it is not known how the future senator will react to the fact that his chosen one is an ordinary girl from the Bronx... The luxurious Beresford hotel, where the main character of the film works, is in fact the famous Waldorf-Astoria on Park Avenue.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Wayne Wang</director>
      <actor>Marisa Ventura - Jennifer Lopez</actor>
      <actor>Christopher 'Chris' Marshall, N.Y. Assemblyman - Ralph Fiennes</actor>
      <actor>Caroline Lane - Natasha Richardson</actor>
      <actor>Jerry Siegel - Stanley Tucci</actor>
      <actor>Ty Ventura - Tyler Posey</actor>
      <actor>Paula Burns - Frances Conroy</actor>
      <actor>John Bextrum, Personnel Manager - Chris Eigeman</actor>
      <actor>Rachel Hoffberg - Amy Sedaris</actor>
      <actor>Stephanie Kehoe, Maid - Marissa Matrone</actor>
      <actor>Veronica Ventura - Priscilla Lopez</actor>
    </credits><date>2002</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421174500 +0500" stop="20260421190500 +0500">
    <title>A Royal Christmas Tail</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Riley runs a shelter for homeless animals.Fate puts in her path... a prince.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Fred Olen Ray</director>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421190500 +0500" stop="20260421205500 +0500">
    <title>The Huntsman: Winter's War</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Many years before Snow White's birth, Queen Ravenna (Charlize Theron) observes the actions of her sister, Freya (Emily Blunt), who is in love with a man named Andrew.Soon their daughter is born.Shortly thereafter, the child is murdered.At the same time, Freya discovers that she has the power to control ice.The woman leaves Ravenna's lands with a broken heart.He creates his own kingdom and an army of deadly hunters.There is only one rule in their ranks: never to love.It is broken by two warriors - Eric (Chris Hemsworth) and Sara (Jessica Chastain).Freya decides to separate them.Seven years later, after Ravenna's death, Snow White decides to get rid of the evil queen's mirror, moving it to the sanctuary.Some time later, William informs Eric that the soldiers who were responsible for the expedition have gone missing.The hunter suspects Freya - the mirror could significantly increase her power.He agrees to complete the mission, with the help of the dwarves.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Cedric Nicolas-Troyan</director>
      <actor>The Huntsman - Chris Hemsworth</actor>
      <actor>Ravenna - Charlize Theron</actor>
      <actor>Sara - Jessica Chastain</actor>
      <actor>Queen Freya - Emily Blunt</actor>
      <actor>Nion - Nick Frost</actor>
      <actor>Gryff - Rob Brydon</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Bromwyn - Sheridan Smith</actor>
      <actor>Doreena - Alexandra Roach</actor>
      <actor>Tull - Sope Dirisu</actor>
      <actor>Leifr - Sam Hazeldine</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421205500 +0500" stop="20260421223000 +0500">
    <title>Detective Monk: One last thing</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brilliant detective Adrian Monk (Tony Shalhoub) is going through difficult times.The contract to publish his autobiography was canceled, and the coronavirus pandemic intensified his fears and phobias.All this makes the master of deduction start thinking about ending his life and joining his beloved Truda.He is jolted out of his torpor by the tragedy that befalls his stepdaughter Molly (Caitlin McGee).The girl is getting ready to marry journalist Griffin Briggs (Austin Scott).However, her fiancé dies while bungee jumping.Molly is convinced that it was not an accident, but a carefully planned murder.The trail leads to the influential billionaire Rick Eden (James Purefoy).Retired Captain Stottlemeyer (Ted Levine) now works for the rich man as his security chief.Monk is assisted in the investigation by former assistant and now real estate agent Natalie Teeger (Traylor Howard) and Randy Disher (Jason Gray-Stanford), now the New Jersey police commissioner.Continuation of the cult series.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Randy Zisk</director>
      <actor>Adrian Monk - Tony Shalhoub</actor>
      <actor>Natalie Teeger - Traylor Howard</actor>
      <actor>Randy Disher - Jason Gray-Stanford</actor>
      <actor>Trudy Monk - Melora Hardin</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Neven Bell - Hector Elizondo</actor>
      <actor>Stottlemeyer - Ted Levine</actor>
      <actor>Rick Eden - James Purefoy</actor>
      <actor>Molly Evans - Caitlin McGee</actor>
      <actor>Griffin Briggs - Austin Scott</actor>
      <actor>Skyler - Emma Ishta</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260421223000 +0500" stop="20260422001500 +0500">
    <title>Towards the sun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 2057. People are increasingly concerned about what is happening to the Sun.It seems to be losing power, and the Earth dependent on it is gradually becoming covered with ice.Scientists are sending an expedition towards the Sun whose task is to place a powerful nuclear charge on its surface.Experts predict that such an explosion will stimulate the star's activity and thus save the world from destruction.After some time, however, it turns out that a similar mission had already taken place seven years earlier, but then none of the crew managed to return to Earth.This time, eight people are sent into space, commanded by the experienced Captain Kaneda.The Icarus II board includes, among others:Cassie, Capa, Corazon and Mace.It quickly turns out that someone is making every effort to prevent the expedition members from reaching their goal.Soon, one of the pilots makes a fatal mistake and deprives the crew of oxygen supplies.In addition, unexpectedly, the ship begins to receive warning signals from its predecessor.The situation is becoming more and more dramatic.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Danny Boyle</director>
      <actor>Kaneda - Hiroyuki Sanada</actor>
      <actor>Cassie - Rose Byrne</actor>
      <actor>Corazon - Michelle Yeoh</actor>
      <actor>Mace - Chris Evans</actor>
      <actor>Capa - Cillian Murphy</actor>
      <actor>Searle - Cliff Curtis</actor>
      <actor>Harvey - Troy Garity</actor>
      <actor>Pinbacker - Mark Strong</actor>
      <actor>Trey - Benedict Wong</actor>
      <actor>Icarus - Chipo Chung</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>