<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO2-PL">
    <display-name>HBO2</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO2-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417002500 +0500" stop="20260417023500 +0500">
    <title>Mickey 17</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year 2050. Mickey Barnes (Robert Pattinson) takes out a loan on usurious terms.Wanting to escape from an aggressive debt collector, together with his friend Timo (Steven Yeun), he joins the crew of a spaceship that is to colonize the ice planet Niflheim.However, when the second of them becomes a shuttle pilot, Mickey - not entirely consciously - becomes the person assigned to the most dangerous tasks.When he dies, in a process called reprinting, a clone of himself is created, which retains his memories.The situation of the version of man number 17 becomes even more complicated when, contrary to expectations, he is not killed during one of the missions, and when he returns to the ship, he finds Mickey 18 there. In these circumstances, the commander of the expedition, Hieronymous Marshall (Mark Ruffalo), decides to eliminate both of them.A surprising, fast-paced and humorous picture by the Oscar-winning writer and director of "Parasite", Bong Joon Ho.The production is an adaptation of the novel by Edward Ashton.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Joon-ho Bong</director>
      <actor>Mickey Barnes - Robert Pattinson</actor>
      <actor>Gwen Johansen - Toni Collette</actor>
      <actor>Hieronymous Marshall - Mark Ruffalo</actor>
      <actor>Timo - Steven Yeun</actor>
      <actor>Nasha Adjaya - Naomi Ackie</actor>
      <actor>Kai Katz - Anamaria Vartolomei</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Cameron Britton</actor>
      <actor>Shrimp Eyes - Angus Imrie</actor>
      <actor>Preston - Daniel Henshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Fantasy Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417023500 +0500" stop="20260417032000 +0500">
    <title>Heated Rivalry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two ice hockey players, Shane Hollander (Hudson Williams) and Ilya Rozanov (Connor Storrie), are united not only by ambition and the need for competition, but also by a magnetic attraction that neither of them fully understands.What begins as a secret romance between two debutants turns into an extraordinary love journey.Athletes spend eight years chasing fame on the ice rink while trying to deal with their feelings off it.They must decide whether there is room for something as fragile as love in a world of brutal competition.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Jacob Tierney</director>
      <actor>Shane Hollander - Hudson Williams</actor>
      <actor>Ilya Rozanov - Connor Storrie</actor>
      <actor>Scott Hunter - François Arnaud</actor>
      <actor>Yuna Hollander - Christina Chang</actor>
      <actor>Cliff Marleau - Franco Lo Presti</actor>
      <actor>Hayden Pike - Callan Potter</actor>
      <actor>Svetlana - Ksenia Daniela Kharlamova</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #2 - Shaun Starr</actor>
      <actor>Man in the Crease Host #1 - Conor McKenna</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417032000 +0500" stop="20260417042000 +0500">
    <title>Ród smoka</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The history of House Targaryen.Its leader, Viserys I (Paddy Considine), ruler of the Seven Kingdoms, decides to break with tradition.The king appoints his daughter, Princess Rhaenyra (Milly Alcock and Emma D'Arcy), as heir to the Iron Throne.This step leads to the initiation of a conflict within the family, called the Dance of Dragons.After the ruler's death, the fratricidal fight breaks out with renewed force.Also taking part in it are:Rhaenyra's brother, Aegon (Tom Glynn-Carney), and Alicent Hightower (Emily Carey and Olivia Cooke), the second wife of Viserys I. The events told in the series precede the action of "Game of Thrones" by 200 years.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E9</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Clare Kilner</director>
      <actor>King Viserys Targaryen - Paddy Considine</actor>
      <actor>Prince Daemon Targaryen - Matt Smith</actor>
      <actor>Lord Corlys Velaryon - Steve Toussaint</actor>
      <actor>Princess Rhaenys Velaryon - Eve Best</actor>
      <actor>Otto Hightower - Rhys Ifans</actor>
      <actor>Mysaria - Sonoya Mizuno</actor>
      <actor>Ser Criston Cole - Fabien Frankel</actor>
      <actor>Ser Harwin 'Breakbones' Strong - Ryan Corr</actor>
      <actor>Lord Jason Lannister - Jefferson Hall</actor>
      <actor>Grand Maester Mellos - David Horovitch</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Serial Fantasy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417042000 +0500" stop="20260417045500 +0500">
    <title>Peacemaker 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Two years have passed since the last events.Chris Smith (John Cena) considers himself a real hero.However, he must earn the recognition of other heroes.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Christopher Smith - John Cena</actor>
      <actor>Leota Adebayo - Danielle Brooks</actor>
      <actor>Adrian Chase - Freddie Stroma</actor>
      <actor>Agent Emilia Harcourt - Jennifer Holland</actor>
      <actor>John Economos - Steve Agee</actor>
      <actor>Eagly - Dee Bradley Baker</actor>
      <actor>Clemson Murn - Chukwudi Iwuji</actor>
      <actor>Auggie Smith - Robert Patrick</actor>
      <actor>Detective Sophie Song - Annie Chang</actor>
      <actor>Detective Larry Fitzgibbon - Lochlyn Munro</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Action-Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417045500 +0500" stop="20260417065500 +0500">
    <title>P.S. I Love You</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After the death of her husband Gerry (Gerard Butler), Holly (Hilary Swank) falls into a deep depression.On her 30th birthday, a woman receives a mysterious parcel.The cake comes with a tape with a recorded message from... Gerry.He encourages his beloved to go out and have fun with friends.After this event, new letters regularly arrived to the young widow, each ending with a declaration of love.Gerry knew how much his wife would suffer from losing him.In letters written before her death, he encourages her to take on various challenges.Thanks to her extraordinary sense of connection with the deceased, a woman in despair undergoes specific therapy and tries to start her life anew.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Richard LaGravenese</director>
      <actor>Holly - Hilary Swank</actor>
      <actor>Gerry - Gerard Butler</actor>
      <actor>Denise - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Sharon - Gina Gershon</actor>
      <actor>John - James Marsters</actor>
      <actor>Patricia - Kathy Bates</actor>
      <actor>Daniel - Harry Connick Jr.</actor>
      <actor>Ciara - Nellie McKay</actor>
      <actor>William - Jeffrey Dean Morgan</actor>
      <actor>George - Christopher Whalen</actor>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417065500 +0500" stop="20260417090000 +0500">
    <title>Insomnia</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>It's a polar summer in northern Alaska.Police officer Will Dormer (Al Pacino) arrives in the town of Nightmute with his partner Hap Eckhart (Martin Donovan).The men are to find the perpetrator of the murder of a seventeen-year-old girl.Will doesn't feel comfortable up north.The polar summer deepens his insomnia.The trail leads to writer Walter Finch (Robin Williams), who was friends with the victim.While chasing him in the thick fog, Will shoots his partner.Hap dies.In his last words, he accuses Will of doing it to prevent an internal investigation.Dormer covers his tracks by directing suspicions at Finch.A writer who witnessed Hap's murder begins to blackmail Will.Meanwhile, local policewoman Ellie Burr (Hilary Swank) is getting closer to discovering the truth behind Hap's death.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Christopher Nolan</director>
      <actor>detektyw Will Dormer - Al Pacino</actor>
      <actor>detektyw Hap Eckhart - Martin Donovan</actor>
      <actor>Walter Finch - Robin Williams</actor>
      <actor>detektyw Ellie Burr - Hilary Swank</actor>
      <actor>Pilot - Oliver Ole Zemen</actor>
      <actor>Chief Charlie Nyback - Paul Dooley</actor>
      <actor>Fred Duggar - Nicky Katt</actor>
      <actor>Farrell - Larry Holden</actor>
      <actor>Francis - Jay Brazeau</actor>
      <actor>Rich - Lorne Cardinal</actor>
    </credits><date>2002</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417090000 +0500" stop="20260417105000 +0500">
    <title>Esperando a Dalí</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Barcelona, ​​1974, a period of intense opposition to Franco's dictatorship.Brothers Fernando (Ivan Massagué), a chef, and Alberto (Pol López), an activist, must hide from the authorities.They find shelter in Cadaqués, a picturesque seaside village that is also the home of the famous artist Salvador Dalí (Gal Soler).In this setting, the brothers meet Lola (Clara Ponsot), who helps them find work.Fernando, influenced by Dalí's works and his infatuation with women, finds a passion for creating unique dishes.The man's ambitions grow, especially when Jules (José Garcia), Lola's eccentric father, dreams of organizing a dinner for Dalí himself.Despite the difficulties, Fernando creates a culinary masterpiece that inspires a revolution in the world of taste, which leads to the creation of the famous Surreal restaurant.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Pujol</director>
      <actor>Jules - José Garcia</actor>
      <actor>Fernando - Ivan Massagué</actor>
      <actor>Lola - Clara Ponsot</actor>
      <actor>Alberto - Pol López</actor>
      <actor>François - Nicolas Cazalé</actor>
      <actor>Luis - Alberto Lozano</actor>
      <actor>Lesya - Varvara Borodina</actor>
      <actor>Tonet - Francesc Ferrer</actor>
      <actor>Gala - Vicky Pena</actor>
      <actor>Teniente Garrido - Paco Tous</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417105000 +0500" stop="20260417123500 +0500">
    <title>The Front Runner</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Senator Gary Hart (Hugh Jackman) is extremely popular, especially among younger voters.In 1988, he decided to run for the presidency of the United States for the second time.He is considered by many to be the favorite.However, unexpectedly, his extramarital relationship with Donna Rice (Sara Paxton) comes to light.The media is publicizing this case, and Hart's career is in question... The director and screenwriter of the film, Jason Reitman, was nominated for the Festival Award at the Toronto International Film Festival.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jason Reitman</director>
      <actor>Gary Hart - Hugh Jackman</actor>
      <actor>Lee Hart - Vera Farmiga</actor>
      <actor>Bill Dixon - J.K. Simmons</actor>
      <actor>Ben Bradlee - Alfred Molina</actor>
      <actor>Irene Kelly - Molly Ephraim</actor>
      <actor>Billy Shore - Mark O'Brien</actor>
      <actor>Kevin Sweeney - Chris Coy</actor>
      <actor>Mike Stratton - Alex Karpovsky</actor>
      <actor>Doug Wilson - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>John Emerson - Tommy Dewey</actor>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417123500 +0500" stop="20260417145000 +0500">
    <title>Eat Pray Love</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Thirty-something Elizabeth Gilbert (Julia Roberts) living in New York seems to have everything she needs to be happy - a husband, a beautiful house and a good job.Still, she feels unhappy.One day he decides to change his life.He gets a divorce and goes on a long journey to rediscover himself.In Italy, people realize that good food, wine and time spent in the company of friends can give a lot of satisfaction.In India, she learns the power of true prayer, which allows her to find inner peace.In Bali, she discovers the joys of meditation and meets the handsome Felipe (Javier Bardem).Over time, the man becomes the love of her life.The film's script was based on Elizabeth Gilbert's autobiographical novel of the same title.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ryan Murphy</director>
      <actor>Liz Gilbert - Julia Roberts</actor>
      <actor>Felipe - Javier Bardem</actor>
      <actor>Nyomo - I. Gusti Ayu Puspawati</actor>
      <actor>Ketut Liyer - Hadi Subiyanto</actor>
      <actor>Stephen - Billy Crudup</actor>
      <actor>Delia Shiraz - Viola Davis</actor>
      <actor>Andre - A. Jay Radcliff</actor>
      <actor>Andy Shiraz - Mike O'Malley</actor>
      <actor>Bookstore Girl - Ashlie Atkinson</actor>
      <actor>David Piccolo - James Franco</actor>
    </credits><date>2010</date>
    <category lang="en">Melodrama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417145000 +0500" stop="20260417164500 +0500">
    <title>Sound of Metal</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Drummer Ruben (Riz Ahmed) and vocalist Lu go on tour.A passionate musician realizes that he is losing his hearing.The life he loved begins to fall apart and the future is uncertain.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Darius Marder</director>
      <actor>Ruben Stone - Riz Ahmed</actor>
      <actor>Lou - Olivia Cooke</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Paul Raci</actor>
      <actor>Diane - Lauren Ridloff</actor>
      <actor>Richard Berger - Mathieu Amalric</actor>
      <actor>Michael - Domenico Toledo</actor>
      <actor>Jenn - Chelsea Lee</actor>
      <actor>Shaheem - Shaheem Sanchez</actor>
      <actor>Harlan - Chris Perfetti</actor>
      <actor>The Man - Bill Thorpe</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417164500 +0500" stop="20260417171500 +0500">
    <title>Silicon Valley 6</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The unusual adventures of exceptionally bright new technology specialists living in Silicon Valley in California.They are no strangers to start-ups or running online companies.Programmer Richard Hendricks and his friends dream of a career like Mark Zuckerberg, the creator of Facebook.The men are extremely intelligent, they have great ideas, but at the same time they are young people lost in life and quite unpredictable in interpersonal relationships.Director Mike Judge based the script on his personal experiences when he worked as an engineer at a company near Palo Alto.Viewers will see the Satellite Award nominee Thomas Middleditch ("The Wolf of Wall Street") and Josh Brener ("The Extras") in the main roles.The series "Silicon Valley" received two Golden Globe nominations for best comedy series.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S6E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Liza Johnson</director>
      <actor>Nelson 'Big Head' Bighetti - Josh Brener</actor>
      <actor>Bertram Gilfoyle - Martin Starr</actor>
      <actor>Dinesh Chugtai - Kumail Nanjiani</actor>
      <actor>Donald 'Jared' Dunn - Zach Woods</actor>
      <actor>Gavin Belson - Matt Ross</actor>
      <actor>Jian Yang - Jimmy O. Yang</actor>
      <actor>Laurie Bream - Suzanne Cryer</actor>
      <actor>Hoover - Chris Williams</actor>
      <actor>Spiritual Advisor - Bernard White</actor>
      <actor>Garrett - Sunkrish Bala</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417171500 +0500" stop="20260417191000 +0500">
    <title>Hitch</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Alex Hitchens experienced heartbreak years ago.He decided that he would never fall in love again, but at the same time he decided to serve other men and share with them his knowledge about women's nature.Since then, he has been involved in a rather unusual profession - advising on how to seduce girls.He prides himself on the fact that he can turn every client into a reliable, self-confident pickup artist.Makes every effort to maintain anonymity.Despite this, he easily obtains subsequent lucrative orders.Hitchens' new client is a humble accountant named Albert, who has fallen in love with the beautiful heiress of a fortune, Allegra Cole.She feels that she has no chance because of her overweight and shyness.Alex meets journalist Sara, who is supposed to interview Allegra.He falls in love with her at first sight.It turns out that in this case his methods fail.As he gradually gains Sara's affection, she discovers his shameful secret...</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Andy Tennant</director>
      <actor>Alex Hitch Hitchens - Will Smith</actor>
      <actor>Albert - Kevin James</actor>
      <actor>Allegra Cole - Amber Valletta</actor>
      <actor>Sara - Eva Mendes</actor>
      <actor>Casey - Julie Ann Emery</actor>
      <actor>Cressida - Robinne Lee</actor>
      <actor>Geoff - Nathan Lee Graham</actor>
      <actor>Max - Adam Arkin</actor>
      <actor>Ben - Michael Rapaport</actor>
      <actor>Vance - Jeffrey Donovan</actor>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417191000 +0500" stop="20260417192000 +0500">
    <title>The Madagascar Penguins in a Christmas Caper</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The action of the film is set before the events of the film "Madagascar".The animals at the New York Zoo are getting ready for Christmas.When it's time to celebrate, Skipper, Kowalski and Rico notice that Private is not with them.The penguin wanted to find a gift for his friend, Ted, who was going to spend Christmas alone.Due to an unfortunate turn of events, instead of getting the gift, Private was bought itself.His friends come to his rescue.In the Polish language version, the characters were voiced by, among others:Grzegorz Pawlak, Jacek Lenartowicz, Tomasz Steciuk and Janusz Zadura.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Gary Trousdale</director>
    </credits><date>2005</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417192000 +0500" stop="20260417210500 +0500">
    <title>What a Feeling</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Austria.Doctor Marie Theres Wallner (Caroline Peters) is 52 years old and has been married to Alexander (Heikko Deutschmann) for two decades, with whom she raises teenage Anna (Allegra Tinnefeld).Her previously successful life falls apart when her husband suddenly leaves her.Desperate, she goes to a bar where she meets a confident, independent immigrant from Iran, Fa Safir (Proschat Madani), who runs a carpentry business with her siblings.Even though the women are very different from each other, something attracts them to each other.If they want to be happy, they must free themselves from many limitations.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kat Rohrer</director>
      <actor>Dr. Marie Theres Wallner - Caroline Peters</actor>
      <actor>Fa Safir - Proschat Madani</actor>
      <actor>Djamshid Safir - Anton Noori</actor>
      <actor>Samira - Nicole Ansari-Cox</actor>
      <actor>Ms. Safir - Gohar Nurbachsch</actor>
      <actor>Samira - Nicole Ansari</actor>
      <actor>Anna Wallner - Allegra Tinnefeld</actor>
      <actor>Alexander Wallner - Heikko Deutschmann</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Rafael Haider</actor>
      <actor>Bigi - Barbara Spitz</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417210500 +0500" stop="20260417223000 +0500">
    <title>IO</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A donkey working in a circus performs with a young artist (Sandra Drzymalska).When he regains freedom thanks to activists, his wandering begins.During his journey, he experiences joy and pain.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jerzy Skolimowski</director>
      <actor>Kasandra - Sandra Drzymalska</actor>
      <actor>Vito - Lorenzo Zurzolo</actor>
      <actor>Mateo - Mateusz Kościukiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Księżna - Isabelle Huppert</actor>
      <actor>Ziom - Tomasz Organek</actor>
      <actor>Dora - Lolita Chammah</actor>
      <actor>Kaja - Agata Sasinowska</actor>
      <actor>Dorota - Anna Rokita</actor>
      <actor>Zenek - Michał Przybysławski</actor>
      <actor>Zea - Gloria Iradukunda</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417223000 +0500" stop="20260417235500 +0500">
    <title>The Addams Family</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Gomez and Morticia Addams are looking for a safe place to live and raise their children.Therefore, they move to a dark, abandoned mansion in New Jersey.The estate is surrounded by swamps and hidden on top of a mountain amidst thick fog.13 years have passed.Gomez teaches the family's traditional saber fighting to Pugslay's son.Meanwhile, Morticia must face daughter Wednesday's questions about life outside the mansion gates.Soon, TV star Margaux Needler appears in the area and starts building a modern housing estate.Her plans are hindered by the fact that the Addams residence does not fit the modernist vision of the theme park.The woman decides to get rid of the strange family.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Conrad Vernon</director>
      <director>Greg Tiernan</director>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260417235500 +0500" stop="20260418012500 +0500">
    <title>The Fountain</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Three stories about man's pursuit of immortality.16th century.In the forests of South America, Spanish conquistador Tomas Creo (Hugh Jackman), head over heels in love with Queen Isabella I of Castile (Rachel Weisz), is looking for the legendary tree of life for her.The ruler wants to use them to finally solve the problem of the power struggle with a certain high-ranking cardinal.In the 20th century, scientist Tom Creo (Hugh Jackman) tries to find a cure that will save his seriously ill wife Izzi (Rachel Weisz).A man cannot come to terms with the fact that his beloved is dying.He decides to devote himself to finding a way to overcome death.Six centuries later, astronaut Tommy (Hugh Jackman) travels through space in a glass ball.He wants to reach the golden nebula, hoping to bring Izzi back to life.A science-fiction drama by Darren Aronofsky, author of "Requiem for a Dream", "Black Swan" and "The Wrestler".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Darren Aronofsky</director>
      <actor>Tomas - Hugh Jackman</actor>
      <actor>Isabel - Rachel Weisz</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Lillian Guzetti - Ellen Burstyn</actor>
      <actor>Father Avila - Mark Margolis</actor>
      <actor>Grand Inquisitor Silecio - Stephen McHattie</actor>
      <actor>Lord of Xibalba - Fernando Hernandez</actor>
      <actor>Captain Ariel - Cliff Curtis</actor>
      <actor>Antonio - Sean Patrick Thomas</actor>
      <actor>Betty - Donna Murphy</actor>
      <actor>Manny - Ethan Suplee</actor>
    </credits><date>2006</date>
    <category lang="en">Psychological Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418012500 +0500" stop="20260418021000 +0500">
    <title>An Update on Our Family</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Fans and the media, concerned about Huxley's fate, are increasingly expressing their concerns, and the discussion on online forums quickly turns into a wave of criticism.Commentators analyze archival materials published by the Stauffers, paying attention to their lifestyle and the way they presented their adopted son.When the family finally makes an official statement, sponsors withdraw their cooperation and public pressure mounts.Consequently, Myka disappears from the Internet, leaving behind an avalanche of unanswered questions and unexplained controversies.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Rachel Mason</director>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418021000 +0500" stop="20260418044500 +0500">
    <title>Blade Runner 2049</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The future, a world dominated by machines created to perform various dangerous tasks.Hunter Rick Deckard was tasked with tracking down and then eliminating the androids from Los Angeles three decades ago.Now the roles are reversed and he is the one who has to hide.At the same time, a new blade runner enters the game.Officer K from a special police unit tracks down humanoid robots hiding in society.When he returns home, his computer-generated companion, Joi, is always waiting for him.During the next task, the investigator comes across a shocking discovery proving that replicators can reproduce, which was previously considered impossible.Officer K's superior, Lieutenant Joshi, fears that the discovery will shock society and lead to war.So he orders the matter to be hushed up.Intrigued, K begins a private investigation.The help of the experienced Deckard turns out to be indispensable.Finding it is a difficult task in itself.Moreover, his enemies are hot on his heels.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Denis Villeneuve</director>
      <actor>'K' - Ryan Gosling</actor>
      <actor>Rick Deckard - Harrison Ford</actor>
      <actor>Joi - Ana de Armas</actor>
      <actor>Luv - Sylvia Hoeks</actor>
      <actor>Lieutenant Joshi - Robin Wright</actor>
      <actor>Sapper Morton - Dave Bautista</actor>
      <actor>Interviewer - Mark Arnold</actor>
      <actor>Angry Old Lady - Vilma Szécsi</actor>
      <actor>Nandez - Wood Harris</actor>
      <actor>Coco - David Dastmalchian</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418044500 +0500" stop="20260418063500 +0500">
    <title>The Order</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>1983, Idaho.FBI agent Terry Husk (Jude Law) with the help of local policeman Jamie Bowen (Tye Sheridan) takes down a far-right terrorist group.The criminals are led by Bob Mathews (Nicholas Hoult), who, together with his men, commits daring robberies.Neo-Nazis intend to use the looted funds to start a revolution and overthrow the US government.They draw inspiration from the apocalyptic novel "The Turner Diaries" about race war.In 1984, they kill liberal journalist Alan Berg (Marc Maron).Finally, there is a bloody confrontation between law enforcement officers and bandits.Scenario based on facts.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Justin Kurzel</director>
      <actor>Terry Husk - Jude Law</actor>
      <actor>Jamie Bowen - Tye Sheridan</actor>
      <actor>Bob Mathews - Nicholas Hoult</actor>
      <actor>Alan Berg - Marc Maron</actor>
      <actor>Gary Yarbrough - George Tchortov</actor>
      <actor>Engineer - Daniel Yip</actor>
      <actor>Walter West - Daniel Doheny</actor>
      <actor>Bruce Pierce - Sebastian Pigott</actor>
      <actor>Hotel Receptionist - John Warkentin</actor>
      <actor>David Lane - Phillip Forest Lewitski</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418063500 +0500" stop="20260418083000 +0500">
    <title>Ghostlight</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Grieving construction worker Dan (Keith Kupferer) joins a local theater group working on a production of Romeo and Juliet.There are changes in his life.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kelly O'Sullivan</director>
      <director>Alex Thompson</director>
      <actor>Dan - Keith Kupferer</actor>
      <actor>Sharon - Tara Mallen</actor>
      <actor>Rita - Dolly De Leon</actor>
      <actor>Lanora - Hanna Dworkin</actor>
      <actor>Daisy - Katherine Kupferer</actor>
      <actor>Greg - Dexter Zollicoffer</actor>
      <actor>Jonah - H.B. Ward</actor>
      <actor>Lucian - Tommy Rivera-Vega</actor>
      <actor>Moira - Alma Washington</actor>
      <actor>Mikey - Matthew C. Yee</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418083000 +0500" stop="20260418090000 +0500">
    <title>Hollywood On Set 23</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E16</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418090000 +0500" stop="20260418104500 +0500">
    <title>What a Feeling</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Austria.Doctor Marie Theres Wallner (Caroline Peters) is 52 years old and has been married to Alexander (Heikko Deutschmann) for two decades, with whom she raises teenage Anna (Allegra Tinnefeld).Her previously successful life falls apart when her husband suddenly leaves her.Desperate, she goes to a bar where she meets a confident, independent immigrant from Iran, Fa Safir (Proschat Madani), who runs a carpentry business with her siblings.Even though the women are very different from each other, something attracts them to each other.If they want to be happy, they must free themselves from many limitations.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Kat Rohrer</director>
      <actor>Dr. Marie Theres Wallner - Caroline Peters</actor>
      <actor>Fa Safir - Proschat Madani</actor>
      <actor>Djamshid Safir - Anton Noori</actor>
      <actor>Samira - Nicole Ansari-Cox</actor>
      <actor>Ms. Safir - Gohar Nurbachsch</actor>
      <actor>Samira - Nicole Ansari</actor>
      <actor>Anna Wallner - Allegra Tinnefeld</actor>
      <actor>Alexander Wallner - Heikko Deutschmann</actor>
      <actor>Tom - Rafael Haider</actor>
      <actor>Bigi - Barbara Spitz</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418104500 +0500" stop="20260418121000 +0500">
    <title>IO</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A donkey working in a circus performs with a young artist (Sandra Drzymalska).When he regains freedom thanks to activists, his wandering begins.During his journey, he experiences joy and pain.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jerzy Skolimowski</director>
      <actor>Kasandra - Sandra Drzymalska</actor>
      <actor>Vito - Lorenzo Zurzolo</actor>
      <actor>Mateo - Mateusz Kościukiewicz</actor>
      <actor>Księżna - Isabelle Huppert</actor>
      <actor>Ziom - Tomasz Organek</actor>
      <actor>Dora - Lolita Chammah</actor>
      <actor>Kaja - Agata Sasinowska</actor>
      <actor>Dorota - Anna Rokita</actor>
      <actor>Zenek - Michał Przybysławski</actor>
      <actor>Zea - Gloria Iradukunda</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418121000 +0500" stop="20260418133500 +0500">
    <title>The Addams Family</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Gomez and Morticia Addams are looking for a safe place to live and raise their children.Therefore, they move to a dark, abandoned mansion in New Jersey.The estate is surrounded by swamps and hidden on top of a mountain amidst thick fog.13 years have passed.Gomez teaches the family's traditional saber fighting to Pugslay's son.Meanwhile, Morticia must face daughter Wednesday's questions about life outside the mansion gates.Soon, TV star Margaux Needler appears in the area and starts building a modern housing estate.Her plans are hindered by the fact that the Addams residence does not fit the modernist vision of the theme park.The woman decides to get rid of the strange family.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Conrad Vernon</director>
      <director>Greg Tiernan</director>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418133500 +0500" stop="20260418144000 +0500">
    <title>Christmas Carole</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Carole Mackay sells holiday-themed trinkets online.Unfortunately, her success made her even more ruthless, but the upcoming Christmas is about to change everything.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ian Fitzgibbon</director>
      <actor>Carole - Suranne Jones</actor>
      <actor>Ghost of Christmas Present - Jo Brand</actor>
      <actor>Leon - Mark Benton</actor>
      <actor>Jackie - Rosie Cavaliero</actor>
      <actor>Eric Morecambe - Jonty Stephens</actor>
      <actor>Ernie Wise - Ian Ashpitel</actor>
      <actor>Bobbie - Taj Atwal</actor>
      <actor>Ghost of Christmas Yet To Come - Nish Kumar</actor>
      <actor>Ade - Alex Carter</actor>
      <actor>Rita - Kirsty Averton</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418144000 +0500" stop="20260418165000 +0500">
    <title>Niesamowity Spider-Man</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Teenage Peter Parker is raised by his uncle Ben and his wife May.The boy has a crush on his schoolmate, Gwen.He tries at all costs to find out what happened to his parents.The folder his father Richard left him leads him to Dr. Curt Connors.This former colleague of Richard's doesn't want to tell Peter a secret about his family.Soon the teenager is bitten by a spider with modified DNA.In an instant, he turns into Spider-Man with supernatural abilities.Then Connors reveals his other side.As the Lizard, he becomes Spider Man's greatest enemy.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Marc Webb</director>
      <actor>Spider-Man - Andrew Garfield</actor>
      <actor>Gwen Stacy - Emma Stone</actor>
      <actor>The Lizard - Rhys Ifans</actor>
      <actor>Aunt May - Sally Field</actor>
      <actor>Uncle Ben - Martin Sheen</actor>
      <actor>Mary Parker - Embeth Davidtz</actor>
      <actor>Richard Parker - Campbell Scott</actor>
      <actor>Jack's Father - C. Thomas Howell</actor>
      <actor>School Librarian - Stan Lee</actor>
      <actor>Flash Thompson - Chris Zylka</actor>
    </credits><date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418165000 +0500" stop="20260418183500 +0500">
    <title>Completement cramé</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A widowed, wealthy Englishman, Andrew Blake (John Malkovich), goes to France, the homeland of his beloved wife.When he arrives at the stately mansion with a suitcase, to his surprise he is not mistaken for a guest, but a candidate for a butler.To stay as long as possible in the place where he met the love of his life years ago, he accepts a job offer and does not reveal the real destination of his trip to anyone.He meets the owner of the historic mansion, the widow Nathalie Beauvillier (Fanny Ardant), the housekeeper and cook Odile (Émilie Dequenne), the maid Manon (Eugénie Anselin) and the estate manager Philippe.Over time, he becomes friends with the residents and helps them look at their lives from a different perspective.Thanks to this, he also finds his lost joy and motivation to act.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Gilles Legardinier</director>
      <actor>Andrew Blake - John Malkovich</actor>
      <actor>Nathalie Beauvillier - Fanny Ardant</actor>
      <actor>Odile - Émilie Dequenne</actor>
      <actor>Magnier - Philippe Bas</actor>
      <actor>Manon - Eugenie Anselin</actor>
      <actor>Mme Berliner - Christel Henon</actor>
      <actor>Passer-by - Daniel Kovacs</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418183500 +0500" stop="20260418201500 +0500">
    <title>Broke</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Former rodeo champion True is not coming to terms with the end of his career.He is surprised by a violent blizzard.He fights for survival.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Carlyle Eubank</director>
      <actor>True Brandywine - Wyatt Russell</actor>
      <actor>Ali - Auden Thornton</actor>
      <actor>George Brandywine - Dennis Quaid</actor>
      <actor>Kathy Brandywine - Mary McDonnell</actor>
      <actor>Caleb Brandywine - Johnny Berchtold</actor>
      <actor>Cliff - Tom Skerritt</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418201500 +0500" stop="20260418223000 +0500">
    <title>A Royal Affair</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>18th century.The young English aristocrat Caroline Matilda of Hanover (Alicia Vikander) marries the Danish king Christian VII (Mikkel Boe Folsgaard) as part of a political alliance.A smart, well-read and beautiful girl tries to cope with her new role.However, she finds no happiness with her exalted husband who shows signs of mental illness.When the German doctor Johann Friedrich Struensee (Mads Mikkelsen), whom the monarch has absolute trust in, appears at the court, the royal wife treats him with reluctance.Over time, however, she discovers how much she has in common with a progressive doctor, a follower of the ideas of the Enlightenment and a liberal who read the books of Voltaire, Rousseau and Locke.The two begin a passionate affair.Struensee gains more and more power and, with the support of Karolina Matilda, carries out innovative reforms.He makes many enemies.The court dignitaries, who have so far manipulated the king, do not intend to accept the loss of influence.They plot to get rid of the queen's lover.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nikolaj Arcel</director>
      <actor>Caroline Mathilde - Alicia Vikander</actor>
      <actor>Johann Friedrich Struensee - Mads Mikkelsen</actor>
      <actor>Christian VII - Mikkel Boe Folsgaard</actor>
      <actor>Juliane Marie - Trine Dyrholm</actor>
      <actor>Ove Hoegh-Guldberg - David Dencik</actor>
      <actor>Schack Carl Rantzau - Thomas W. Gabrielsson</actor>
      <actor>Enevold Brandt - Cyron Melville</actor>
      <actor>J. H. E. Bernstoff - Bent Mejding</actor>
      <actor>Augusta - Princess of Wales - Harriet Walter</actor>
      <actor>Louise von Plessen - Laura Bro</actor>
    </credits><date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO2-PL" start="20260418223000 +0500" stop="20260419003500 +0500">
    <title>Drużyna AA</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Four cross-dependent alcoholics, Leszek (Michał Żurawski), Wiola (Danuta Stenka), Dominik (Mikołaj Kubacki) and Karolina (Maria Sobocińska), participate, together with others, in therapy conducted by Wojtek (Łukasz Simlat).One day they learn that their center is to be closed due to financial problems.To raise money to save it, his friends undertake to illegally transport two tankers of spirit across Poland.Additionally, realizing their problems, they kidnap the therapist for their own safety.Following them - or rather the illegal alcohol they are transporting - follows the customs officer Klementyna (Magdalena Cielecka).However, the woman is not the person she claims to be.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Daniel Jaroszek</director>
      <actor>Wiola - Danuta Stenka</actor>
      <actor>Leszek - Michał Żurawski</actor>
      <actor>Karolina - Maria Sobocińska</actor>
      <actor>Wojtek - Łukasz Simlat</actor>
      <actor>Dominik - Mikołaj Kubacki</actor>
      <actor>Klementyna Celniczka - Magdalena Cielecka</actor>
      <actor>Bruno - Leszek Lichota</actor>
      <actor>Misia - Izabela Gwizdak</actor>
      <actor>doktor Jan Tyroszek - Piotr Trojan</actor>
      <actor>matka Dominika - Maria Pakulnis</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>