<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO3-PL">
    <display-name>HBO3</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO3-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416000000 +0500" stop="20260416013000 +0500">
    <title>Gerta Schnirch</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brno, the night of May 30-31, 1945. Gerta Schnirch (Barbora Váchová), the daughter of a Nazi and a Czech mother, together with her several-month-old child, is - like almost all Germans - expelled from the city.The exhausting procession, marked by violence and humiliation, later called the death march, ends near the border with Austria.From the temporary camp, Gerta goes to work in the Moravian countryside.She manages to save her own life and that of her daughter.After five years he returns to Brno.No one is waiting for her in the city, but she still can't leave it.She becomes entangled in a vortex of further turbulent changes.A film adaptation of Kateřina Tučková's debut novel, "The Expulsion of Greta Schnirch", touching on the difficult topic of Czech and German guilt, revenge, forgiveness and national identity.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Tomáš Mašín</director>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416013000 +0500" stop="20260416021500 +0500">
    <title>Doc Ii.</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Dr. Amy Larsen, former chief of internal medicine, is rebuilding her life after a tragic accident that left her with no memory.Now she is an intern.Her past still haunts me.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E11</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Russell Lee Fine</director>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416021500 +0500" stop="20260416041000 +0500">
    <title>28 Years Later</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>There is still a bloody fight for survival on Earth.The survivors of the epidemic protect themselves from zombies in a closely guarded stronghold on the island.The world forces twelve-year-old Spike (Alfie Williams), the son of Jamie (Aaron Taylor-Johnson) and Isla (Jodie Comer), to grow up in inhumane conditions.He will be hunting for the infected on the mainland under his father's supervision.Despite his young age, the boy must be prepared for a ruthless fight to the death.The expedition shows him the terrible consequences of being infected with a mysterious virus.It soon comes to light that not only the undead have mutated, but also those who survived.The trail leads to the doctor, Dr. Kelson (Ralph Fiennes)... The last part of the trilogy after "28 Days Later" and "28 Weeks Later" by Danny Boyle and Alex Garland, showing a world overrun by zombies.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Danny Boyle</director>
      <actor>Sir Jimmy Crystal - Jack O'Connell</actor>
      <actor>Jamie - Aaron Taylor-Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Spike - Alfie Williams</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Kelson - Ralph Fiennes</actor>
      <actor>Isla - Jodie Comer</actor>
      <actor>Jimmy Ink - Erin Kellyman</actor>
      <actor>E. Sundqvist - Edvin Ryding</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416041000 +0500" stop="20260416060500 +0500">
    <title>The Outrun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A young woman named Rona (Saoirse Ronan), who has recently left an addiction treatment center, returns from London to her native Scotland, to one of the islands of the Orkney archipelago.Because her parents are separated, she lives alternately with her mother, where she meets with her religious friends, and with her father, whom she helps on the farm.At the same time, she is still trying to cope with difficult memories - the beginning of her stay in London, where she started studying biology and often went to clubs with her boyfriend Daynin (Paapa Essiedu).She didn't even notice when she fell into alcoholism, which led to problems in her relationship and began to destroy her life.Meanwhile, while staying on the island, Rona decides to return to London.However, already on the ferry he feels that he is unable to control the urge to drink alcohol.He must re-plan his life.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nora Fingscheidt</director>
      <actor>Rona - Saoirse Ronan</actor>
      <actor>Young Rona - Freya Evans</actor>
      <actor>Daynin - Paapa Essiedu</actor>
      <actor>Barman James - Seamus Dillane</actor>
      <actor>Bouncer Dave - David Garrick</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Rasamalar - Aniya Sekkanu</actor>
      <actor>Andrew - Stephen Dillane</actor>
      <actor>Annie - Saskia Reeves</actor>
      <actor>Young Orcadian Man - Liam Smith</actor>
      <actor>Bible Group Evie - Eilidh Fisher</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Psychological Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416060500 +0500" stop="20260416073500 +0500">
    <title>Gerta Schnirch</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Brno, the night of May 30-31, 1945. Gerta Schnirch (Barbora Váchová), the daughter of a Nazi and a Czech mother, together with her several-month-old child, is - like almost all Germans - expelled from the city.The exhausting procession, marked by violence and humiliation, later called the death march, ends near the border with Austria.From the temporary camp, Gerta goes to work in the Moravian countryside.She manages to save her own life and that of her daughter.After five years he returns to Brno.No one is waiting for her in the city, but she still can't leave it.She becomes entangled in a vortex of further turbulent changes.A film adaptation of Kateřina Tučková's debut novel, "The Expulsion of Greta Schnirch", touching on the difficult topic of Czech and German guilt, revenge, forgiveness and national identity.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Tomáš Mašín</director>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Historical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416073500 +0500" stop="20260416090000 +0500">
    <title>Some Other Woman</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Thanks to his job, Peter Simmons (Tom Felton) has the opportunity to move to a tropical island for a few months.He takes his wife, Eva (Amanda Crew), with him there.The couple feels like they are in paradise and enjoys the charms of this beautiful place.However, duties keep Peter on the island longer, so the months turn into years and Eva is forced to abandon her plans.In addition, she begins to be haunted by a mysterious woman, Renata (Ashley Greene), who looks very much like her.When Eva realizes that she is taking over her life, piece by piece, she panics.He's not going to let that happen.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Joel David Moore</director>
      <actor>Eve Simmons - Amanda Crew</actor>
      <actor>Peter Simmons - Tom Felton</actor>
      <actor>Renata Cordova - Ashley Greene</actor>
      <actor>Chelsea Ranza - Brooke Lyons</actor>
      <actor>Salvador Ranza - Rick Fox</actor>
      <actor>Caro - Caroline Raynaud</actor>
      <actor>Fisherman - Darvin Ebanks</actor>
      <actor>Mendo - Matt Fox Seales</actor>
      <actor>Abarena - Nasaria Suckoo-Cholette</actor>
      <actor>Psychologist - Samantha Kaine</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416090000 +0500" stop="20260416103000 +0500">
    <title>Benchwarmers 2: Breaking Balls</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ben McGrath (Chris Klein) has great potential and a chance for a career in a professional baseball league.Unfortunately, his hopes for the game are ruined by an unfortunate accident.So the would-be athlete becomes a lawyer and gets a job at the Schmood &amp; Associates law firm.One day, however, he gets a chance to return to the field.His unconventional boss, Mel Carmichael (Jon Lovitz), convinces him to form a softball team of his co-workers.Ben undertakes this task, although he realizes that creating an effective team from a group of eccentric lawyers is quite a challenge.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jonathan A. Rosenbaum</director>
      <actor>Ben McGrath - Chris Klein</actor>
      <actor>Mel Carmichael - Jon Lovitz</actor>
      <actor>Annie - Chelsey Reist</actor>
      <actor>Stenhouse - Lochlyn Munro</actor>
      <actor>Dopkins - Garfield Wilson</actor>
      <actor>Dana - Lisa Durupt</actor>
      <actor>Krinsky - Chris Gauthier</actor>
      <actor>Howard - Peter Graham-Gaudreau</actor>
      <actor>Arthur Wilde - Zachary Gulka</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416103000 +0500" stop="20260416122000 +0500">
    <title>Force of Nature: The Dry 2</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Australia.Federal agent Aaron Falk (Eric Bana) unsuccessfully tries to extort information from Alice Russell (Anna Torv) regarding money laundering at her company.The next day, the woman goes on a team-building trip with her colleagues, including:boss Jill Bailey (Deborra-Lee Furness), childhood friend Lauren (Robin McLeavy) and sisters Brianna (Lucy Ansell) and Bethany (Sisi Stringer).Three days later, he calls a policeman, but the call quickly ends.Soon, Aaron's friend, agent Carmen Cooper (Jacqueline McKenzie), informs him that the woman's companions returned from the trip injured and she is missing.They both go to one of the regions of the Australian Alps to take part in the search.They also interrogate the other participants of the expedition, but their testimonies do not coincide.Moreover, it turns out that these people have a lot on their conscience.A continuation of the 2020 crime story, in which Eric Bana also played the role of Agent Falk.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Robert Connolly</director>
      <actor>Falk - Eric Bana</actor>
      <actor>Alice - Anna Torv</actor>
      <actor>Jill Bailey - Deborra-Lee Furness</actor>
      <actor>Lauren - Robin McLeavy</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Sisi Stringer</actor>
      <actor>Bree - Lucy Ansell</actor>
      <actor>Carmen - Jacqueline McKenzie</actor>
      <actor>Eric Falk - Jeremy Lindsay Taylor</actor>
      <actor>Daniel Bailey - Richard Roxburgh</actor>
      <actor>Ian Chase - Tony Briggs</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416122000 +0500" stop="20260416135000 +0500">
    <title>The Pirates! Band of Misfits</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A certain inept captain of a pirate ship firmly believes that he will soon become the terror of the seas and oceans.Unfortunately, for now, these ambitious plans have no chance of being implemented, and his subsequent crazy ideas end in failure.The buccaneer, who wants to prove his bravery at all costs, intends to defeat his greatest enemies - Black Bellamy and Cutlass Liz - in the competition for the title of Pirate of the Year.His faithful, although slightly crazy crew will help him achieve his goal.The captain and his companions face quite a challenge.What stands in their way is, among others:young Charles Darwin and the privateers of the cruel Queen Victoria.An adventurous family film directed by Peter Lord, who received his third Oscar nomination for this picture.The plot of the film was taken from a series of books by Gideon Defoe.In the Polish language version, the voices of the characters were provided by, among others:Waldemar Barwiński, Grzegorz Kwiecień, Karol Wróblewski and Izabella Bukowska.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Lord</director>
      <director>Jeff Newitt</director>
    </credits><date>2012</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416135000 +0500" stop="20260416141500 +0500">
    <title>Ballers 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Legendary American football player, Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson), ends his football career and starts working as a sports consultant.A comedy series that reveals the behind-the-scenes life of players of one of the most popular sports in the USA.On the one hand, the heroes live at a high standard, but on the other hand, they have to struggle with enormous pressure.The main roles were played by: Dwayne Johnson ("The Scorpion King", "Barbell and Cash"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"), Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow", "Forever Alive") and Taylor Cole ("Surrogates", the series "The Event").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Julian Farino</director>
      <actor>Spencer Strasmore - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Ricky Jerret - John David Washington</actor>
      <actor>Charles Greane - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Vernon Littlefield - Donovan W. Carter</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Rob Corddry</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416141500 +0500" stop="20260416145000 +0500">
    <title>Ballers 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Legendary American football player, Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson), ends his football career and starts working as a sports consultant.A comedy series that reveals the behind-the-scenes life of players of one of the most popular sports in the USA.On the one hand, the heroes live at a high standard, but on the other hand, they have to struggle with enormous pressure.The main roles were played by: Dwayne Johnson ("The Scorpion King", "Barbell and Cash"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"), Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow", "Forever Alive") and Taylor Cole ("Surrogates", the series "The Event").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>David Katzenberg</director>
      <actor>Spencer Strasmore - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Ricky Jerret - John David Washington</actor>
      <actor>Charles Greane - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Vernon Littlefield - Donovan W. Carter</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Rob Corddry</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416145000 +0500" stop="20260416165500 +0500">
    <title>Big Fish</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Edward Bloom (Albert Finney), a brilliant storyteller and favorite of the neighborhood, is dying.His son Will (Billy Crudup) left home long ago, not wanting to live forever in the shadow of his father's fantastic stories.Now she returns to accompany him in his last moments.Listening to Edward's stories again, Will tries to put them together to make sense.The picture that emerges is surprisingly coherent and shows the father's life in a new light.The son realizes who his father really was.Tim Burton, one of the most eccentric creators of American cinema, created a film that captivates with its warmth, fairy-tale atmosphere and surreal poetics.The script is based on the novel "Big Fish: A Story of Mythic Proportions" by Daniel Wallace.We will see Ewan McGregor as young Edward.The atmospheric music received an Oscar nomination.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Tim Burton</director>
      <actor>młody Ed Bloom - Ewan McGregor</actor>
      <actor>stary Ed Bloom - Albert Finney</actor>
      <actor>Will Bloom - Billy Crudup</actor>
      <actor>stara Sandra Bloom - Jessica Lange</actor>
      <actor>młoda Sandra Bloom - Alison Lohman</actor>
      <actor>Jenny - Helena Bonham Carter</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Bennett - Robert Guillaume</actor>
      <actor>Josephine - Marion Cotillard</actor>
      <actor>Karl the Giant - Matthew McGrory</actor>
      <actor>Don Price - David Denman</actor>
    </credits><date>2003</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416165500 +0500" stop="20260416183000 +0500">
    <title>Karate Kid: Legends</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Li Fong's friend needs help.He decided to take part in a karate tournament, but his skills are insufficient.Teacher Han turns to the legendary Daniel LaRusso for help.</desc>
    <credits>
      <actor>Mr. Han - Jackie Chan</actor>
      <actor>Li Fong - Ben Wang</actor>
      <actor>Victor Lipani - Joshua Jackson</actor>
      <actor>Mia Lipani - Sadie Stanley</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Fong - Ming-Na</actor>
      <actor>Alan - Wyatt Oleff</actor>
      <actor>Conor - Aramis Knight</actor>
      <actor>Daniel LaRusso - Ralph Macchio</actor>
      <actor>Young Girl - Olivia Yang Avis</actor>
      <actor>Young Student - Aaron Wang</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416183000 +0500" stop="20260416201500 +0500">
    <title>Jojo Rabbit</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Set in Germany during World War II, the story of Jojo (Roman Griffin Davis), a member of the Hitler Youth.His best friend is an imaginary friend - Adolf Hitler (Taika Waititi).The boy asks him for advice on key issues, such as how to be the best little Nazi or how to recognize a Jew.One day, Jojo discovers that a Jewish teenager (Thomasin McKenzie) is hiding in his house with the consent of his single mother (Scarlett Johansson).His world turns upside down, and his current views clash with his sympathy for the girl he just met.A moving but also funny story about a young German coming of age during the Holocaust.The director, screenwriter and actor of the role of Hitler is Taika Waititi.The film won an Oscar in the best adapted screenplay category.He also received five nominations for this prestigious award.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Taika Waititi</director>
      <actor>Jojo - Roman Griffin Davis</actor>
      <actor>Elsa - Thomasin McKenzie</actor>
      <actor>Rosie - Scarlett Johansson</actor>
      <actor>Adolf - Taika Waititi</actor>
      <actor>Captain Klenzendorf - Sam Rockwell</actor>
      <actor>Fraulein Rahm - Rebel Wilson</actor>
      <actor>Finkel - Alfie Allen</actor>
      <actor>Deertz - Stephen Merchant</actor>
      <actor>Yorki - Archie Yates</actor>
      <actor>Christoph - Luke Brandon Field</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416201500 +0500" stop="20260416214000 +0500">
    <title>A Picture Of Her</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Beth (Rhiannon Fish) works as first mate on a fishing vessel.He goes ashore for a while to take care of his aunt (Samantha Ferris), who has broken her leg.During her daily shopping, photographer Jake (Tyler Hynes) secretly takes a photo of her choosing flowers.A freelancer sends a photo of a stranger to a newspaper under a pseudonym.Some time later, Beth and Jake meet in person.They both turn out to be dog lovers, and over time they discover that they have a lot in common.The lovers' relationship is getting closer.Then Beth's photo appears on the cover of a magazine and goes viral, making her very popular.The woman wants to find the author, meanwhile Jake does not have the courage to confess the truth.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Robinson</director>
      <director>Michael Robison</director>
      <actor>Jake - Tyler Hynes</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Rhiannon Fish</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Dody - Samantha Ferris</actor>
      <actor>Captain Mark - Robert Wisden</actor>
      <actor>Candace - Alison Araya</actor>
      <actor>Janice - Aadila Dosani</actor>
      <actor>Richie Rosebrook - Gavin Langelo</actor>
      <actor>Jaypeg - Seth Whittaker</actor>
      <actor>Cool Rocker - Mark James</actor>
      <actor>Date Woman - Felicia Chiappetta</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416214000 +0500" stop="20260416221500 +0500">
    <title>The Righteous Gemstones 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The last installment of the famous production, mockingly telling the story of a family of televangelists.Eli Gemstone and his adult children continue to enjoy life, which is enabled by his enormous fortune.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E8</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Eli Gemstone - John Goodman</actor>
      <actor>Abraham Gemstone - Gavin Munn</actor>
      <actor>Prayer Group Goon - Thomas W Wolf</actor>
      <actor>Church Attendee - LaChelle Walker</actor>
      <actor>Winston - Jackson Kelly</actor>
      <actor>Thaddeus - Alex Saxon</actor>
      <actor>Union Soldier Stephens - Charles Ambrose</actor>
      <actor>Parishioner - Stacey Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Kelvin Gemstone's Chauffeur - Justin N. Bailey</actor>
      <actor>Rural Church Member - David Michael-Smith</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416221500 +0500" stop="20260416231000 +0500">
    <title>The Righteous Gemstones 4</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The last installment of the famous production, mockingly telling the story of a family of televangelists.Eli Gemstone and his adult children continue to enjoy life, which is enabled by his enormous fortune.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S4E9</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Eli Gemstone - John Goodman</actor>
      <actor>Abraham Gemstone - Gavin Munn</actor>
      <actor>Prayer Group Goon - Thomas W Wolf</actor>
      <actor>Church Attendee - LaChelle Walker</actor>
      <actor>Winston - Jackson Kelly</actor>
      <actor>Thaddeus - Alex Saxon</actor>
      <actor>Union Soldier Stephens - Charles Ambrose</actor>
      <actor>Parishioner - Stacey Stewart</actor>
      <actor>Kelvin Gemstone's Chauffeur - Justin N. Bailey</actor>
      <actor>Rural Church Member - David Michael-Smith</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260416231000 +0500" stop="20260417000000 +0500">
    <title>The Great</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Catherine manages to dethrone her husband.However, he quickly learns that taking the throne is just the beginning.Now she faces a real fight to introduce significant changes in Russia.In fact, it means struggling with his own court, as well as his loved ones, including his mother (Gillian Anderson).In addition, Katarzyna will also experience love suffering.She will have to sort out her relationship with Piotr.Only all these adventures lead the powerful woman to reflect that in order to change the country, she must allow herself to be changed.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E9</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Colin Bucksey</director>
      <actor>Peter - Nicholas Hoult</actor>
      <actor>Catherine - Elle Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Tartar Nick - Christophe Tek</actor>
      <actor>Ivan - Charlie Price</actor>
      <actor>Soldier - Michael Odin Cartwright</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Bayo Gbadamosi</actor>
      <actor>Tatyana - Florence Keith-Roach</actor>
      <actor>Captain - Anthony J. Abraham</actor>
      <actor>Chef Louis - Asheq Akhtar</actor>
      <actor>Unknown Lady - Komal Amin</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417000000 +0500" stop="20260417004000 +0500">
    <title>Last Week Tonight With John Oliver 13</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Another season of a show full of irony and sarcasm, hosted by John Oliver.In each episode, the host summarizes the events from the world of politics from the last week.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E2</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Talk-Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417004000 +0500" stop="20260417013500 +0500">
    <title>The Pitt</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>John Wells</director>
      <actor>Dr. Michael Robinavitch - Noah Wyle</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Cassie McKay - Fiona Dourif</actor>
      <actor>Dana Evans - Katherine LaNasa</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Dennis Whitaker - Gerran Howell</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Trinity Santos - Isa Briones</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Heather Collins - Tracy Ifeachor</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Melissa King - Taylor Dearden</actor>
      <actor>Mateo Diaz - Jalen Thomas Brooks</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Victoria Javadi - Shabana Azeez</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Samira Mohan - Supriya Ganesh</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417013500 +0500" stop="20260417023500 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417023500 +0500" stop="20260417033500 +0500">
    <title>DTF St. Louis</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Clark - Jason Bateman</actor>
      <actor>Floyd - David Harbour</actor>
      <actor>Carol - Linda Cardellini</actor>
      <actor>Homer - Richard Jenkins</actor>
      <actor>Jodie Plumb - Joy Sunday</actor>
      <actor>Eimy - Wynn Everett</actor>
      <actor>Stephen Queece - Asher Miles Fallica</actor>
      <actor>Clara Gilchrist - Chastity Dotson</actor>
      <actor>Chicago Reporter - Mallory Hoff</actor>
      <actor>Value Inn Manager - Arischa Conner</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417033500 +0500" stop="20260417040500 +0500">
    <title>Rooster</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Greg Russo (Steve Carell) has written a best-selling series of books, and readers identify him with his literary hero nicknamed Rooster.A famous writer comes to the university campus to support his daughter (Charly Clive) who is going through a marital crisis in a difficult moment.Her partner has just left her for a student, which everyone knows perfectly well.The situation is further complicated by scandals involving a woman who are the subject of gossip in the academic community.The father declares help, but his presence quickly reveals old conflicts and uncomfortable topics, instead of bringing the expected solution.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Bill Lawrence</director>
      <director>Matt Tarses</director>
      <actor>Greg Russo - Steve Carell</actor>
      <actor>Walter Mann - John C. McGinley</actor>
      <actor>Cristle - Annie Mumolo</actor>
      <actor>Tommy - Maximo Salas</actor>
      <actor>Spooner - Evan Jachelski</actor>
      <actor>George - Xavier Beloved</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417040500 +0500" stop="20260417044000 +0500">
    <title>Comeback 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Valerie Cherish, a once popular television actress, rose to fame as a sitcom star.After many years, he wants to return to the small screen at all costs.He decides to take part in a new reality show.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Patrick King</director>
      <actor>Valerie Cherish - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Jane Benson - Laura Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mark Berman - Damian Young</actor>
      <actor>Billy Stanton - Dan Bucatinsky</actor>
      <actor>Juna Millken - Malin Akerman</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417044000 +0500" stop="20260417062500 +0500">
    <title>The Killer's Game</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Joe Flood, one of the best contract killers, learns about an incurable disease and places a contract on himself.However, the murderess is targeting his ex-girlfriend.Joe decides to save her.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>J.J. Perry</director>
      <actor>Maize Arnaud - Sofia Boutella</actor>
      <actor>Joe Flood - Dave Bautista</actor>
      <actor>Angus Mackenzie - Scott Adkins</actor>
      <actor>Zvi Rabinowitz - Ben Kingsley</actor>
      <actor>Radovan - Daniel Bernhardt</actor>
      <actor>Aimee - Antonia Desplat</actor>
      <actor>Emilio 'El Botas' - Marko Zaror</actor>
      <actor>Rory Mckenzie - Drew McIntyre</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417062500 +0500" stop="20260417070500 +0500">
    <title>Last Week Tonight With John Oliver 13</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Another season of a show full of irony and sarcasm, hosted by John Oliver.In each episode, the host summarizes the events from the world of politics from the last week.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E2</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Talk-Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417070500 +0500" stop="20260417090000 +0500">
    <title>The Forgiven</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Wealthy Londoners David (Ralph Fiennes) and Jo (Jessica Chastain) Henninger, whose marriage is in serious crisis, go to Morocco for the weekend, where they are to attend a lavish party hosted by an old friend.A man driving very fast and under the influence of alcohol fatally hits a teenager in the desert.The couple takes the body to a friend's house, where they try to cover up the incident in cooperation with the local police.However, soon the boy's father appears in the villa, demanding not only the body, but also justice.There is a violent clash of cultures, after which David will have to face the consequences of his actions.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>John Michael McDonagh</director>
      <actor>Jo Henninger - Jessica Chastain</actor>
      <actor>David Henninger - Ralph Fiennes</actor>
      <actor>Cody - Abbey Lee</actor>
      <actor>Richard Galloway - Matt Smith</actor>
      <actor>Dally Margolis - Caleb Landry Jones</actor>
      <actor>Tom Day - Christopher Abbott</actor>
      <actor>Isabelle - Marie-Josée Croze</actor>
      <actor>Lord Swanthorne - Alex Jennings</actor>
      <actor>Anouar - Said Taghmaoui</actor>
      <actor>Maisy Joyce - Fiona O'Shaughnessy</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417090000 +0500" stop="20260417093000 +0500">
    <title>Shrek the Halls</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After many dramatic adventures, Shrek dreams only of resting in the comfort of his home.However, he is not given peace.Christmas is approaching.Everyone, without exception, succumbs to the Christmas euphoria of preparing for the magical days of the year.Meanwhile, the ogre cannot surrender to the overwhelmingly solemn atmosphere because he hates holidays.However, he does not want to disappoint Fiona and the children, so he decides to get involved in the ceremonial preparations.His miserable struggles are watched by his faithful friends - Donkey, Puss in Boots and Biscuit.Embarrassed by the ogre's clumsiness and lack of good taste, they decide to help him.Soon, thanks to their efforts, Shrek's house is thrown into chaos.This promises to be the most terrifying Christmas in the life of an ogre, a lover of peace and quiet... The next adventure of Shrek in a special TV version.In the Polish language version, famous actors provided their voices, including:Jerzy Stuhr and Zbigniew Zamachowski.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Gary Trousdale</director>
    </credits><date>2007</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417093000 +0500" stop="20260417110000 +0500">
    <title>Karate Kid: Legends</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Li Fong's friend needs help.He decided to take part in a karate tournament, but his skills are insufficient.Teacher Han turns to the legendary Daniel LaRusso for help.</desc>
    <credits>
      <actor>Mr. Han - Jackie Chan</actor>
      <actor>Li Fong - Ben Wang</actor>
      <actor>Victor Lipani - Joshua Jackson</actor>
      <actor>Mia Lipani - Sadie Stanley</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Fong - Ming-Na</actor>
      <actor>Alan - Wyatt Oleff</actor>
      <actor>Conor - Aramis Knight</actor>
      <actor>Daniel LaRusso - Ralph Macchio</actor>
      <actor>Young Girl - Olivia Yang Avis</actor>
      <actor>Young Student - Aaron Wang</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417110000 +0500" stop="20260417125000 +0500">
    <title>Alles Fifty Fifty</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Despite the divorce, Marion (Laura Tonke) and Andi (Moritz Bleibtreu) consider themselves exemplary parents of eleven-year-old Milan (Valentin Thatenhorst).They share custody of their son and care for him.So they are surprised when they are called to an interview at the school, during which they learn that the boy is causing a lot of problems.In this situation, they decide to take him on a holiday together to Italy.Marion's new boyfriend, Robin (David Kross), also accompanies them on the trip.Both parents quickly notice that Milan often acts like a spoiled only child, and they come to the conclusion that they need to work on raising him.The time they spend together and their shared efforts make them grow closer again.At the same time, their son falls in love for the first time.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Alireza Golafshan</director>
      <actor>Marion - Laura Tonke</actor>
      <actor>Andi - Moritz Bleibtreu</actor>
      <actor>Milan - Valentin Thatenhorst</actor>
      <actor>Robin - David Kross</actor>
      <actor>Jens - Axel Stein</actor>
      <actor>Paris - Jasin Challah</actor>
      <actor>Mila - Aennie Lade</actor>
      <actor>Elke - Ramona Kunze-Libnow</actor>
      <actor>Giando Kellner - Ricardo Angelini</actor>
      <actor>Herr Accapatoio - Günther Brenner</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417125000 +0500" stop="20260417143500 +0500">
    <title>Rise of the Planet of the Apes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>San Francisco.Will Rodman is a scientist employed by a pharmaceutical company.She is developing a formula for a drug that regenerates brain tissue that could cure his father, who suffers from Alzheimer's disease.A little chimpanzee named Caesar comes under the care of a scientist.This is where Will conducts his research.Over time, he begins to achieve success and is on the verge of a big breakthrough.He meets Caroline Aranha, who has devoted her entire life to monkeys and knows the capabilities of this species perfectly.It quickly turns out that the new drug also has side effects - it increases intelligence.Gifted with increasingly greater cognitive abilities, the chimpanzee realizes that his life means nothing to scientists.Outraged, he decides to oppose people.Caesar takes advantage of the ignorance of the facility's guards and gives samples of the drug to other chimpanzees.In a short time, all the monkeys escape from the building and start wreaking destruction in the city.The fight between intelligent monkeys for domination over humans begins.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Rupert Wyatt</director>
      <actor>Will Rodman - James Franco</actor>
      <actor>Charles Rodman - John Lithgow</actor>
      <actor>Caesar - Andy Serkis</actor>
      <actor>Caroline - Freida Pinto</actor>
      <actor>Dodge Landon - Tom Felton</actor>
      <actor>John Landon - Brian Cox</actor>
      <actor>Franklin - Tyler Labine</actor>
      <actor>Hunsiker - David Hewlett</actor>
      <actor>Woman on Street - Sonja Bennett</actor>
      <actor>Irena - Chelah Horsdal</actor>
    </credits><date>2011</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417143500 +0500" stop="20260417150000 +0500">
    <title>Ballers 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Legendary American football player, Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson), ends his football career and starts working as a sports consultant.A comedy series that reveals the behind-the-scenes life of players of one of the most popular sports in the USA.On the one hand, the heroes live at a high standard, but on the other hand, they have to struggle with enormous pressure.The main roles were played by: Dwayne Johnson ("The Scorpion King", "Barbell and Cash"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"), Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow", "Forever Alive") and Taylor Cole ("Surrogates", the series "The Event").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>David Katzenberg</director>
      <actor>Spencer Strasmore - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Ricky Jerret - John David Washington</actor>
      <actor>Charles Greane - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Vernon Littlefield - Donovan W. Carter</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Rob Corddry</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417150000 +0500" stop="20260417153000 +0500">
    <title>Ballers 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Legendary American football player, Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson), ends his football career and starts working as a sports consultant.A comedy series that reveals the behind-the-scenes life of players of one of the most popular sports in the USA.On the one hand, the heroes live at a high standard, but on the other hand, they have to struggle with enormous pressure.The main roles were played by: Dwayne Johnson ("The Scorpion King", "Barbell and Cash"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"), Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow", "Forever Alive") and Taylor Cole ("Surrogates", the series "The Event").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E4</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>David Katzenberg</director>
      <actor>Spencer Strasmore - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Ricky Jerret - John David Washington</actor>
      <actor>Charles Greane - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Vernon Littlefield - Donovan W. Carter</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Rob Corddry</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417153000 +0500" stop="20260417173500 +0500">
    <title>Green Book</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>USA, 1960s. Tony Vallelonga, a simple resident of the Bronx who has a wife and a group of children to support, agrees to accompany, as a chauffeur and bodyguard, a black musician - the luxurious erudite Donald Shirley - on a concert tour across the United States.Not only does he have to defend his protégé from troubles in the Deep South, but he also has to combat prejudiced views.During their journey, they both follow the instructions from the "Green Book" guide for African Americans traveling around the country.It includes, among others:suggestions on where to sleep and eat to avoid unpleasant incidents.The time spent together and overcoming mounting problems cause a surprising, lasting bond to emerge between men from different worlds.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Peter Farrelly</director>
      <actor>Tony Lip - Viggo Mortensen</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Donald Shirley - Mahershala Ali</actor>
      <actor>Dolores - Linda Cardellini</actor>
      <actor>Johnny Venere - Sebastian Maniscalco</actor>
      <actor>Oleg - Dimiter D. Marinov</actor>
      <actor>George Dyer - the Cellist - Mike Hatton</actor>
      <actor>Record Exec - P.J. Byrne</actor>
      <actor>Gio Loscudo - Joe Cortese</actor>
      <actor>Copa Coat Check Girl - Maggie Nixon</actor>
      <actor>Bobby Rydell - Von Lewis</actor>
    </credits><date>2018</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417173500 +0500" stop="20260417181500 +0500">
    <title>Last Week Tonight With John Oliver 13</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Another season of a show full of irony and sarcasm, hosted by John Oliver.In each episode, the host summarizes the events from the world of politics from the last week.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E2</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Talk-Show</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417181500 +0500" stop="20260417204500 +0500">
    <title>Ford v Ferrari</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The victory in the prestigious race goes to the Ferrari team every year.Henry Ford II intends to dethrone the full-time champion.He thinks about building a car that will leave the competition behind.For this purpose, he asks for help from two specialists.One of them is the temperamental fast driving enthusiast Ken Miles.The second one is Carroll Shelby, who can boast of winning Le Mans, and some time ago, due to health problems, he gave up his driving career and took up car design.They both immediately take up the challenge, even though they know that there is a long way to achieve their goal.They quickly encounter resistance from officials.It turns out that they must immerse themselves in the world of ruthless bureaucracy to take part in the twenty-four-hour race.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>James Mangold</director>
      <actor>Carroll Shelby - Matt Damon</actor>
      <actor>Ken Miles - Christian Bale</actor>
      <actor>Lee Iacocca - Jon Bernthal</actor>
      <actor>Mollie Miles - Caitríona Balfe</actor>
      <actor>Leo Beebe - Josh Lucas</actor>
      <actor>Peter Miles - Noah Jupe</actor>
      <actor>Henry Ford II - Tracy Letts</actor>
      <actor>Enzo Ferrari - Remo Girone</actor>
      <actor>Phil Remington - Ray McKinnon</actor>
      <actor>Roy Lunn - JJ Feild</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Biographical Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417204500 +0500" stop="20260417221000 +0500">
    <title>Killing the Competition</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Bossy Elizabeth Fenwick (Melissa Joan Hart) was once the star of the cheerleading squad.Currently, the woman is very keen for her teenage daughter, Grace (Lily Brooks O'Briant), to follow in her footsteps.Unfortunately, although the girl performs very well in the team selection committee, other candidates turn out to be better and she is rejected.Elizabeth can't come to terms with it.Unable to forgive his daughter for this failure, he begins to harass her, lowering her self-esteem.Gradually, the woman's actions take the form of obsession.Finally, to ensure Grace's place in the band, she decides to expel another student from her high school, an excellent dancer named Hannah (Valerie Loo).To do this, he intends to kidnap the girl and her mother, Nicole (Anzu Lawson).Inspired by true events, the film tells the story of the obsession that a parent's unfulfilled ambition can turn into.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Lee Gabiana</director>
      <actor>Elizabeth Fenwick - Melissa Joan Hart</actor>
      <actor>Grace Fenwick - Lily Brooks O'Briant</actor>
      <actor>Hannah Li - Valerie Loo</actor>
      <actor>Steve Fenwick - Eddie Mills</actor>
      <actor>Nicole Li - Anzu Lawson</actor>
      <actor>Jackson Fenwick - Cyrus McReynolds</actor>
      <actor>Tyler Tulsey - Lucas Randazzo</actor>
      <actor>Kath - Anmalya Delva</actor>
      <actor>Jeanie - Kate McCarty</actor>
      <actor>Bekka - Lola Raie</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417221000 +0500" stop="20260417230000 +0500">
    <title>Industry</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Harper Stern (Myha'la Herrold) moves to London from a small town in upstate New York.He takes up a job at a major international bank, Pierpoint &amp; Co.She really wants to prove herself to her superiors and do better than her peers.However, he quickly comes face to face with the brutal reality.He discovers that in the fight for a job it is not only competence that counts, but also origin.People from privileged families have much greater opportunities.However, this does not take away from her enthusiasm and motivates her even more to try to get her dream job.Together with other graduates from his age group, he learns about the hierarchical realities of the industry.Young people fall into the ruthless corporate machine where no one trusts anyone, and everyone, regardless of ethical issues, tries to take the place of their colleagues in a better position.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Lena Dunham</director>
      <actor>Gus - David Jonsson</actor>
      <actor>Hari - Nabhaan Rizwan</actor>
      <actor>Harper - Myha'la Herrold</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Kilblane - Conor MacNeill</actor>
      <actor>Yasmin - Marisa Abela</actor>
      <actor>Sara Dhadwal - Priyanga Burford</actor>
      <actor>Tate Connelley - Trader - Charlotte Callaghan</actor>
      <actor>Graduate - Clemmie France Hayhurst</actor>
      <actor>Robert - Harry Lawtey</actor>
    </credits><date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260417230000 +0500" stop="20260418000000 +0500">
    <title>The Great</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Catherine manages to dethrone her husband.However, he quickly learns that taking the throne is just the beginning.Now she faces a real fight to introduce significant changes in Russia.In fact, it means struggling with his own court, as well as his loved ones, including his mother (Gillian Anderson).In addition, Katarzyna will also experience love suffering.She will have to sort out her relationship with Piotr.Only all these adventures lead the powerful woman to reflect that in order to change the country, she must allow herself to be changed.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S2E10</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Colin Bucksey</director>
      <actor>Peter - Nicholas Hoult</actor>
      <actor>Catherine - Elle Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Tartar Nick - Christophe Tek</actor>
      <actor>Ivan - Charlie Price</actor>
      <actor>Soldier - Michael Odin Cartwright</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Bayo Gbadamosi</actor>
      <actor>Tatyana - Florence Keith-Roach</actor>
      <actor>Captain - Anthony J. Abraham</actor>
      <actor>Chef Louis - Asheq Akhtar</actor>
      <actor>Unknown Lady - Komal Amin</actor>
    </credits><date>2021</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>