<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="HBO3-PL">
    <display-name>HBO3</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/HBO3-PL.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420064000 +0500" stop="20260420083500 +0500">
    <title>The Outrun</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A young woman named Rona (Saoirse Ronan), who has recently left an addiction treatment center, returns from London to her native Scotland, to one of the islands of the Orkney archipelago.Because her parents are separated, she lives alternately with her mother, where she meets with her religious friends, and with her father, whom she helps on the farm.At the same time, she is still trying to cope with difficult memories - the beginning of her stay in London, where she started studying biology and often went to clubs with her boyfriend Daynin (Paapa Essiedu).She didn't even notice when she fell into alcoholism, which led to problems in her relationship and began to destroy her life.Meanwhile, while staying on the island, Rona decides to return to London.However, already on the ferry he feels that he is unable to control the urge to drink alcohol.He must re-plan his life.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nora Fingscheidt</director>
      <actor>Rona - Saoirse Ronan</actor>
      <actor>Young Rona - Freya Evans</actor>
      <actor>Daynin - Paapa Essiedu</actor>
      <actor>Barman James - Seamus Dillane</actor>
      <actor>Bouncer Dave - David Garrick</actor>
      <actor>Dr. Rasamalar - Aniya Sekkanu</actor>
      <actor>Andrew - Stephen Dillane</actor>
      <actor>Annie - Saskia Reeves</actor>
      <actor>Young Orcadian Man - Liam Smith</actor>
      <actor>Bible Group Evie - Eilidh Fisher</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Psychological Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420083500 +0500" stop="20260420090000 +0500">
    <title>Kung Fu Panda: Secret of the Scroll</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The helpless inhabitants of the villages in the Valley of Tranquility are terrorized by a powerful Boar.Shifu, who has just fallen ill, asks Tigress to bring four trained warriors to help him.During the journey, however, the envoy does not use the list prepared by the master, but a scroll created by Po.He has no idea that the notes concern... professions in which the young panda could pursue in the future.As a result of a mistake, Tigress brings to the Jade Palace: the cleaner Crane, the comedian Monkey, the dancer Viper and the doctor Mantis.Soon, the inconspicuous chosen ones become the Mighty Five.A short story about Po's adventures before he became the Dragon Warrior.It features characters known from the next three full-length parts of the famous animated series.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Rodolphe Guenoden</director>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420090000 +0500" stop="20260420113500 +0500">
    <title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>A new school year begins at Hogwarts, the famous wizarding school.Harry Potter and his friend Ron Weasley have been unlucky from the beginning.They miss their train, so they take a flying car to get there.Unfortunately, they cause a crash, which angers Prof.Snape.It turns out that last year's feat, neutralizing Lord Voldemort, made Harry a hero.The young wizard is not happy about his sudden popularity.It does not help him concentrate on his studies and even makes enemies, including among teachers.Meanwhile, prof.Dumbledore warns that evil lurks within the walls of the academy.An ominous writing appears on the wall, declaring that the Chamber of Secrets has been opened.Students and teachers are in danger.Potter must find out what got out of the chamber and defeat the dark forces that have taken over Hogwarts.He is helped by his friends, Ron and Hermione.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Chris Columbus</director>
      <actor>Harry Potter - Daniel Radcliffe</actor>
      <actor>Ron Weasley - Rupert Grint</actor>
      <actor>Hermione Granger - Emma Watson</actor>
      <actor>wuj Vernon - Richard Griffiths</actor>
      <actor>ciotka Petunia - Fiona Shaw</actor>
      <actor>Dudley Dursley - Harry Melling</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Mason - Jim Norton</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Mason - Veronica Clifford</actor>
      <actor>Fred Weasley - James Phelps</actor>
      <actor>George Weasley - Oliver Phelps</actor>
    </credits><date>2002</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420113500 +0500" stop="20260420132500 +0500">
    <title>Saturday Night</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>New York, October 11, 1975.Aspiring producer Lorne Michaels (Gabriel LaBelle) arrives at the NBC studios to prepare the broadcast of the first episode of "Saturday Night".The man's superior, Dick Ebersol (Cooper Hoffman), immediately informs him that executive director David Tebet (Willem Dafoe) is skeptical about the new show.Meanwhile, there are constant misunderstandings between cast members on set.Garrett Morris (Lamorne Morris) is not happy with the role he was cast in, John Belushi (Matt Wood) cannot communicate with his co-workers and causes fights, as does Chevy Chase (Cory Michael Smith), who confronts Milton Berle (J.K. Simmons) because he is hitting on his girlfriend.Even host George Carlin (Matthew Rhys) thinks what he was asked to do is embarrassing.Additionally, everyone is wondering what type of program they should create.Resigned, Michaels goes to a local bar, where he meets comedy writer Alan Zweibel (Josh Brener).After a short conversation, she hires him to cooperate.The film was inspired by real events and its action covers 90 minutes preceding the first broadcast of the famous cyclical entertainment program.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jason Reitman</director>
      <actor>Lorne Michaels - Gabriel LaBelle</actor>
      <actor>Rosie Shuster - Rachel Sennott</actor>
      <actor>Chevy Chase - Cory Michael Smith</actor>
      <actor>Gilda Radner - Ella Hunt</actor>
      <actor>Dan Aykroyd - Dylan O'Brien</actor>
      <actor>Laraine Newman - Emily Fairn</actor>
      <actor>John Belushi - Matt Wood</actor>
      <actor>Garrett Morris - Lamorne Morris</actor>
      <actor>Jane Curtin - Kimberly Matula</actor>
      <actor>NBC Page - Finn Wolfhard</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420132500 +0500" stop="20260420151500 +0500">
    <title>Jojo Rabbit</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Set in Germany during World War II, the story of Jojo (Roman Griffin Davis), a member of the Hitler Youth.His best friend is an imaginary friend - Adolf Hitler (Taika Waititi).The boy asks him for advice on key issues, such as how to be the best little Nazi or how to recognize a Jew.One day, Jojo discovers that a Jewish teenager (Thomasin McKenzie) is hiding in his house with the consent of his single mother (Scarlett Johansson).His world turns upside down, and his current views clash with his sympathy for the girl he just met.A moving but also funny story about a young German coming of age during the Holocaust.The director, screenwriter and actor of the role of Hitler is Taika Waititi.The film won an Oscar in the best adapted screenplay category.He also received five nominations for this prestigious award.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Taika Waititi</director>
      <actor>Jojo - Roman Griffin Davis</actor>
      <actor>Elsa - Thomasin McKenzie</actor>
      <actor>Rosie - Scarlett Johansson</actor>
      <actor>Adolf - Taika Waititi</actor>
      <actor>Captain Klenzendorf - Sam Rockwell</actor>
      <actor>Fraulein Rahm - Rebel Wilson</actor>
      <actor>Finkel - Alfie Allen</actor>
      <actor>Deertz - Stephen Merchant</actor>
      <actor>Yorki - Archie Yates</actor>
      <actor>Christoph - Luke Brandon Field</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420151500 +0500" stop="20260420154500 +0500">
    <title>Ballers 3</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Make Believe</sub-title>
    <desc>Legendary American football player, Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson), ends his football career and starts working as a sports consultant.A comedy series that reveals the behind-the-scenes life of competitors of one of the most popular sports in the USA.On the one hand, the heroes live at a high standard, but on the other hand, they have to struggle with enormous pressure.The main roles were played by: Dwayne Johnson ("The Scorpion King", "Barbell and Cash"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"), Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow", "Forever Alive") and Taylor Cole ("Surrogates", the series "The Event").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Spencer Strasmore - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Ricky Jerret - John David Washington</actor>
      <actor>Charles Greane - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Vernon Littlefield - Donovan W. Carter</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Rob Corddry</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420154500 +0500" stop="20260420161500 +0500">
    <title>Ballers 3</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">I Hate New York</sub-title>
    <desc>Legendary American football player, Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson), ends his football career and starts working as a sports consultant.A comedy series that reveals the behind-the-scenes life of competitors of one of the most popular sports in the USA.On the one hand, the heroes live at a high standard, but on the other hand, they have to struggle with enormous pressure.The main roles were played by: Dwayne Johnson ("The Scorpion King", "Barbell and Cash"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"), Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow", "Forever Alive") and Taylor Cole ("Surrogates", the series "The Event").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E6</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Millicent Shelton</director>
      <actor>Spencer Strasmore - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Ricky Jerret - John David Washington</actor>
      <actor>Charles Greane - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Vernon Littlefield - Donovan W. Carter</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Rob Corddry</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420161500 +0500" stop="20260420174500 +0500">
    <title>Benchwarmers 2: Breaking Balls</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Ben McGrath (Chris Klein) has great potential and a chance for a career in a professional baseball league.Unfortunately, his hopes for the game are ruined by an unfortunate accident.So the would-be athlete becomes a lawyer and gets a job at the Schmood &amp; Associates law firm.One day, however, he gets a chance to return to the field.His unconventional boss, Mel Carmichael (Jon Lovitz), convinces him to form a softball team of his co-workers.Ben undertakes this task, although he realizes that creating an effective team from a group of eccentric lawyers is quite a challenge.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jonathan A. Rosenbaum</director>
      <actor>Ben McGrath - Chris Klein</actor>
      <actor>Mel Carmichael - Jon Lovitz</actor>
      <actor>Annie - Chelsey Reist</actor>
      <actor>Stenhouse - Lochlyn Munro</actor>
      <actor>Dopkins - Garfield Wilson</actor>
      <actor>Dana - Lisa Durupt</actor>
      <actor>Krinsky - Chris Gauthier</actor>
      <actor>Howard - Peter Graham-Gaudreau</actor>
      <actor>Arthur Wilde - Zachary Gulka</actor>
    </credits><date>2019</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420174500 +0500" stop="20260420191000 +0500">
    <title>Fantastic Mr. Fox</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Since his unsuccessful attack on one of the farms, Mr. Fox has been leading a quiet, boring life.Under the influence of his wife, he settled down, gave up working on the border of the law and started writing articles for a local newspaper.However, his instincts do not allow him to sit still for long.Soon, together with his friend Szop, he comes up with a plan to attack three large farms.The friends brilliantly rob Walter Boggis, Franklin Bean and Nathan Bunce.However, people do not remain idle and quickly develop a plan for revenge.Mr. Fox must fight for the life not only of himself and his loved ones, but also of other persecuted creatures.Wes Anderson, responsible for the film, was nominated for an Oscar in 2001 for his screenplay for "Brilliant Clan"."Fantastic Mr. Fox" is his animated debut.The director's credits include the award-winning comedy "The Grand Budapest Hotel."The film received nine Oscar nominations, including:in the following categories: best film, script, music, cinematography and editing.He also won a Golden Globe statuette.The Polish language version was attended by, among others:Grzegorz Wons, Agnieszka Kunikowska, Artur Pontek, Piotr Bajtlik and Krzysztof Szczerbiński.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Wes Anderson</director>
    </credits><date>2009</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420191000 +0500" stop="20260420203500 +0500">
    <title>Ready Jet Go: Space Camp The Movie</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jet surfs the comet's tail with his pet, Sunspot.Unfortunately, it turns out that the pet is allergic to comet dust and begins to shrink.Jet and his friends must find a cure quickly.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>David Mucci Fassett</director>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Animated Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420203500 +0500" stop="20260420221500 +0500">
    <title>True Story</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Michael Finkel (Jonah Hill), a New York Times journalist, disgraced himself with an article whose hero - a slave trader in Mali - does not exist.The reporter is publicly humiliated and fired.So he returns to his hometown.He soon discovers that a man is impersonating him, accused of murdering his wife and three small children.Christian Longo (James Franco) is captured in Mexico.He agrees to meet with Finkel, who sees a chance to publish a best-selling novel and rehabilitate himself in the eyes of readers.However, it turns out that Longo has some plans for the journalist.She has been following his career for a long time.A story based on facts about the relationship between a psychopathic murderer and a disgraced journalist.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Rupert Goold</director>
      <actor>Michael Finkel - Jonah Hill</actor>
      <actor>Christian Longo - James Franco</actor>
      <actor>Jill Barker - Felicity Jones</actor>
      <actor>MaryJane Longo - Maria Dizzia</actor>
      <actor>Pat Frato - Ethan Suplee</actor>
      <actor>Zach Longo - Conor Kikot</actor>
      <actor>Sadie Longo - Charlotte Driscoll</actor>
      <actor>Madison Longo - Stella Rae Payne</actor>
      <actor>Greg Ganley - Robert John Burke</actor>
      <actor>Judge Odenkirk - Byron Jennings</actor>
    </credits><date>2015</date>
    <category lang="en">Crime Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420221500 +0500" stop="20260420230500 +0500">
    <title>Industry</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Quiet and Nice</sub-title>
    <desc>Harper Stern (Myha'la Herrold) moves to London from a small town in upstate New York.He takes up a job at a major international bank, Pierpoint &amp; Co.She really wants to prove herself to her superiors and do better than her peers.However, he quickly comes face to face with the brutal reality.He discovers that in the fight for a job it is not only competence that counts, but also origin.People from privileged families have much greater opportunities.However, this does not take away from her enthusiasm and motivates her even more to try to get her dream job.Together with other graduates from his age group, he learns about the hierarchical realities of the industry.Young people fall into the ruthless corporate machine where no one trusts anyone, and everyone, regardless of ethical issues, tries to take the place of their colleagues in a better position.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Tinge Krishnan</director>
      <actor>Gus - David Jonsson</actor>
      <actor>Hari - Nabhaan Rizwan</actor>
      <actor>Harper - Myha'la Herrold</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Kilblane - Conor MacNeill</actor>
      <actor>Yasmin - Marisa Abela</actor>
      <actor>Sara Dhadwal - Priyanga Burford</actor>
      <actor>Tate Connelley - Trader - Charlotte Callaghan</actor>
      <actor>Graduate - Clemmie France Hayhurst</actor>
      <actor>Robert - Harry Lawtey</actor>
      <actor>Eric - Ken Leung</actor>
    </credits><date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260420230500 +0500" stop="20260421000000 +0500">
    <title>The Great</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">The Bullet or the Bear</sub-title>
    <desc>A continuation of the story about Tsarina Catherine (Elle Fanning), in which facts mix with satire.After the woman recently tried to kill her husband, Piotr (Nicholas Hoult), and imprisoned all his friends, the relationship between them is not good.Meanwhile, Katarzyna also faces political problems.Wanting to solve them, the ruler becomes famous also outside Russia.During this time, Piotr tries to accept the fact that he lives in his wife's shadow.He devotes himself to fatherhood, takes part in hunting and discovers culinary novelties.Finally, they both decide to take a responsible step - they decide to save their marriage
Katarzyna feels remorse for stabbing Pukachev.The ruler also begins to notice how important it is to be familiar with politics.She decides to become her champion.She hopes that Aunt Elizabeth and Archie will help her with this.Orlo is furious that Peter is still alive.He, in turn, hesitates whether he should continue to do only what he wants or obey Katarzyna.So first he frees his friends who are waiting to be executed, but eventually he brings them back.Georgina, on the other hand, declares her loyalty to Catherine.To test this, the ruler orders her to be the first to shoot at the prisoners.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E1</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Colin Bucksey</director>
      <director>Matthew Moore</director>
      <director>Bert</director>
      <actor>Katarzyna - Elle Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Piotr - Nicholas Hoult</actor>
      <actor>Marial - Phoebe Fox</actor>
      <actor>Velementov - Douglas Hodge</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Bayo Gbadamosi</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Elizabeth - Belinda Bromilow</actor>
      <actor>Archbishop - Adam Godley</actor>
      <actor>Georgina - Charity Wakefield</actor>
      <actor>Queen Agnes - Grace Molony</actor>
      <actor>Grigor Dymov - Gwilym Lee</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421000000 +0500" stop="20260421010000 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421010000 +0500" stop="20260421013000 +0500">
    <title>Rooster</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Greg Russo (Steve Carell) has written a best-selling series of books, and readers identify him with his literary hero nicknamed Rooster.A famous writer comes to the university campus to support his daughter (Charly Clive) who is going through a marital crisis in a difficult moment.Her partner has just left her for a student, which everyone knows perfectly well.The situation is further complicated by scandals involving a woman who are the subject of gossip in the academic community.The father declares help, but his presence quickly reveals old conflicts and uncomfortable topics, instead of bringing the expected solution.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Bill Lawrence</director>
      <director>Matt Tarses</director>
      <actor>Greg Russo - Steve Carell</actor>
      <actor>Walter Mann - John C. McGinley</actor>
      <actor>Cristle - Annie Mumolo</actor>
      <actor>Tommy - Maximo Salas</actor>
      <actor>Spooner - Evan Jachelski</actor>
      <actor>George - Xavier Beloved</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421013000 +0500" stop="20260421020000 +0500">
    <title>Comeback 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Valerie Cherish, a once popular television actress, rose to fame as a sitcom star.After many years, he wants to return to the small screen at all costs.He decides to take part in a new reality show.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Patrick King</director>
      <actor>Valerie Cherish - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Jane Benson - Laura Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mark Berman - Damian Young</actor>
      <actor>Billy Stanton - Dan Bucatinsky</actor>
      <actor>Juna Millken - Malin Akerman</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421020000 +0500" stop="20260421041500 +0500">
    <title>Sinners</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The year is 1932. Twin brothers Smoke and Stack (double role of Michael B. Jordan), who have a difficult past, return from Chicago to their hometown in Mississippi.They try to escape from problems and a life of crime.They establish a music club for black people and hope for a new beginning.Their enemy, however, are dark, sinister forces that they must face.At stake is not only the lives of the brothers and their loved ones, but also their culture, history and memory.A dark cinema combining elements of action, horror and a musical drawing on the blues tradition.It is a story about an attempt at redemption and the fight against an invisible evil that symbolizes the weight of the past and past sins.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ryan Coogler</director>
      <actor>Mary - Hailee Steinfeld</actor>
      <actor>Remmick - Jack O'Connell</actor>
      <actor>Smoke - Michael B. Jordan</actor>
      <actor>Annie - Wunmi Mosaku</actor>
      <actor>Joan - Lola Kirke</actor>
      <actor>Delta Slim - Delroy Lindo</actor>
      <actor>Grace Chow - Li Jun Li</actor>
      <actor>Cornbread - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Pearline - Jayme Lawson</actor>
      <actor>Hogwood - David Maldonado</actor>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Horror</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421041500 +0500" stop="20260421054000 +0500">
    <title>Some Other Woman</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Thanks to his job, Peter Simmons (Tom Felton) has the opportunity to move to a tropical island for a few months.He takes his wife, Eva (Amanda Crew), with him there.The couple feels like they are in paradise and enjoys the charms of this beautiful place.However, duties keep Peter on the island longer, so months turn into years and Eva is forced to abandon her plans.In addition, she begins to be haunted by a mysterious woman, Renata (Ashley Greene), who looks very much like her.When Eva realizes that she is taking over her life, piece by piece, she panics.He's not going to let that happen.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Joel David Moore</director>
      <actor>Eve Simmons - Amanda Crew</actor>
      <actor>Peter Simmons - Tom Felton</actor>
      <actor>Renata Cordova - Ashley Greene</actor>
      <actor>Chelsea Ranza - Brooke Lyons</actor>
      <actor>Salvador Ranza - Rick Fox</actor>
      <actor>Caro - Caroline Raynaud</actor>
      <actor>Fisherman - Darvin Ebanks</actor>
      <actor>Mendo - Matt Fox Seales</actor>
      <actor>Abarena - Nasaria Suckoo-Cholette</actor>
      <actor>Psychologist - Samantha Kaine</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Thriller</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421054000 +0500" stop="20260421064000 +0500">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The further fate of a group of friends who left school behind and entered adulthood.The action moves forward several years.Rue (Zendaya Coleman) is no longer a lost teenager, but a person involved in the criminal world.He goes to interrogation in connection with smuggling drugs from Mexico.Cassie (Sydney Sweeney) and Maddy's (Alexa Demie) relationship has improved, but old wounds haven't healed at all.The first woman's relationship with Nate (Jacob Elordi) develops, but not towards a happy ending.The remaining characters confront their own choices, addiction and violence.They are looking for redemption and answers to the question about their place in the world.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Rue Bennett - Zendaya Coleman</actor>
      <actor>Jules Vaughn - Hunter Schafer</actor>
      <actor>Lexi Howard - Maude Apatow</actor>
      <actor>Nate Jacobs - Jacob Elordi</actor>
      <actor>Maddy Perez - Alexa Demie</actor>
      <actor>Cassie Howard - Sydney Sweeney</actor>
      <actor>Leslie Bennett - Nika King</actor>
      <actor>Cal Jacobs - Eric Dane</actor>
      <actor>Suze - Alanna Ubach</actor>
      <actor>Marsha Jacobs - Paula Marshall</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421064000 +0500" stop="20260421071000 +0500">
    <title>Rooster</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Greg Russo (Steve Carell) has written a best-selling series of books, and readers identify him with his literary hero nicknamed Rooster.A famous writer comes to the university campus to support his daughter (Charly Clive) who is going through a marital crisis in a difficult moment.Her partner has just left her for a student, which everyone knows perfectly well.The situation is further complicated by scandals involving a woman who are the subject of gossip in the academic community.The father declares help, but his presence quickly reveals old conflicts and uncomfortable topics, instead of bringing the expected solution.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Bill Lawrence</director>
      <director>Matt Tarses</director>
      <actor>Greg Russo - Steve Carell</actor>
      <actor>Walter Mann - John C. McGinley</actor>
      <actor>Cristle - Annie Mumolo</actor>
      <actor>Tommy - Maximo Salas</actor>
      <actor>Spooner - Evan Jachelski</actor>
      <actor>George - Xavier Beloved</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421071000 +0500" stop="20260421074000 +0500">
    <title>Comeback 3</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Valerie Cherish, a once popular television actress, rose to fame as a sitcom star.After many years, he wants to return to the small screen at all costs.He decides to take part in a new reality show.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E5</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Patrick King</director>
      <actor>Valerie Cherish - Lisa Kudrow</actor>
      <actor>Jane Benson - Laura Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mark Berman - Damian Young</actor>
      <actor>Billy Stanton - Dan Bucatinsky</actor>
      <actor>Juna Millken - Malin Akerman</actor>
    </credits><date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421074000 +0500" stop="20260421090000 +0500">
    <title>33 photos from the ghetto</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The story of the discovery of 33 unique photographs documenting the Warsaw Ghetto Uprising in 1943.The negatives of the secretly taken photos were found by the son of their creator after 80 years.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jan Czarlewski</director>
    </credits><date>2025</date>
    <category lang="en">Documentary Film</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421090000 +0500" stop="20260421112000 +0500">
    <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>13-year-old Harry Potter spends his next holidays with his aunt and uncle, the Dursleys.So far, he has been very obedient and has never once used magic outside his school, in accordance with the regulations in force.Eventually, however, his mischievous Aunt Marge throws him off balance.Using his magical skills, the boy causes the woman to inflate like a balloon and fly away.Harry, terrified by the prospect of the punishment his guardians would surely inflict on him, runs away from them at night.The Knight-Errant's multi-decker bus takes him to a pub where the Minister of Magic, Cornelius Fudge, is waiting for him.He offers the young wizard a place to stay.His strange behavior catches Potter's attention.It turns out that Sirius Black escaped from Azkaban.He allegedly caused the death of Harry's parents, and now he plans to kill their son.Hogwarts is guarded by Dementors, who are the guards of Azkaban.Harry feels paralyzing fear of them.He must defeat him to face the enemy.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Alfonso Cuarón</director>
      <actor>Harry Potter - Daniel Radcliffe</actor>
      <actor>Ron Weasley - Rupert Grint</actor>
      <actor>Hermiona - Emma Watson</actor>
      <actor>Uncle Vernon - Richard Griffiths</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Marge - Pam Ferris</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Petunia - Fiona Shaw</actor>
      <actor>Dudley Dursley - Harry Melling</actor>
      <actor>James Potter - Adrian Rawlins</actor>
      <actor>Lily Potter - Geraldine Somerville</actor>
      <actor>Stan Shunpike - Lee Ingleby</actor>
    </credits><date>2004</date>
    <category lang="en">Adventure Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421112000 +0500" stop="20260421124000 +0500">
    <title>The Heist Before Christmas</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The brothers meet a man dressed as Santa Claus in the forest who is running away from the police after a robbery.At the same time, they meet another stranger (Timothy Spall) who claims he fell off a sleigh...</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Edward Hall</director>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Dramas</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421124000 +0500" stop="20260421142000 +0500">
    <title>Living</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>London, 1953. Rodney Williams (Bill Nighy) has been doing the same boring bureaucratic job for years.A lonely man feels that his life has been meaningless for a long time.One day he learns from the doctor that he has been diagnosed with incurable cancer.Desperate, he goes to a seaside town to commit suicide.However, he changes his mind and spends the night wandering around bars with a writer he meets there, Sutherland (Tom Burke).Back in London, Williams doesn't go to the office.He runs into Margaret Harris (Aimee Lou Wood), a much younger and energetic woman who once worked in his department.He becomes friends with her and she infects him with her enthusiasm.When the man's condition worsens, he decides to do something important.With the help of Peter Wakeling (Alex Sharp), a young idealist from his office, he wants to build a playground, the construction of which he himself had previously blocked.A remake of "The Brand of Death", a drama by Akira Kurosawa, inspired by Leo Tolstoy's short story "The Death of Ivan Ilyich".</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Oliver Hermanus</director>
      <actor>Williams - Bill Nighy</actor>
      <actor>Margaret Harris - Aimee Lou Wood</actor>
      <actor>Peter Wakeling - Alex Sharp</actor>
      <actor>Sutherland - Tom Burke</actor>
      <actor>Middleton - Adrian Rawlins</actor>
      <actor>Rusbridger - Hubert Burton</actor>
      <actor>Hart - Oliver Chris</actor>
      <actor>Sir James - Michael Cochrane</actor>
      <actor>Singh - Anant Varman</actor>
      <actor>Mrs McMasters - Zoe Boyle</actor>
    </credits><date>2022</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421142000 +0500" stop="20260421144500 +0500">
    <title>Ballers 3</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Ricky-Leaks</sub-title>
    <desc>Legendary American football player, Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson), ends his football career and starts working as a sports consultant.A comedy series that reveals the behind-the-scenes life of competitors of one of the most popular sports in the USA.On the one hand, the heroes live at a high standard, but on the other hand, they have to struggle with enormous pressure.The main roles were played by: Dwayne Johnson ("The Scorpion King", "Barbell and Cash"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"), Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow", "Forever Alive") and Taylor Cole ("Surrogates", the series "The Event").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E7</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <actor>Spencer Strasmore - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Ricky Jerret - John David Washington</actor>
      <actor>Charles Greane - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Vernon Littlefield - Donovan W. Carter</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Rob Corddry</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421144500 +0500" stop="20260421152000 +0500">
    <title>Ballers 3</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Alley-Oops</sub-title>
    <desc>Legendary American football player, Spencer Strasmore (Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson), ends his football career and starts working as a sports consultant.A comedy series that reveals the behind-the-scenes life of competitors of one of the most popular sports in the USA.On the one hand, the heroes live at a high standard, but on the other hand, they have to struggle with enormous pressure.The main roles were played by: Dwayne Johnson ("The Scorpion King", "Barbell and Cash"), Omar Benson Miller ("8th Mile", "The Sorcerer's Apprentice"), Rob Corddry ("Fur Tomorrow", "Forever Alive") and Taylor Cole ("Surrogates", the series "The Event").</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E8</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>David Katzenberg</director>
      <actor>Spencer Strasmore - Dwayne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Ricky Jerret - John David Washington</actor>
      <actor>Charles Greane - Omar Benson Miller</actor>
      <actor>Vernon Littlefield - Donovan W. Carter</actor>
      <actor>Joe - Rob Corddry</actor>
    </credits><date>2017</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421152000 +0500" stop="20260421165500 +0500">
    <title>karina jane austin</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Jane Hayes (Keri Russell) is thirty years old, single and loves Jane Austen's novels.In men, she looks for similarities to Mr. Darcy, the hero of "Pride and Prejudice", played by Colin Firth years ago.One day, the woman decides to spend all her savings to go to Great Britain, following in the footsteps of her beloved writer.There he goes to a residence for Jane Austen enthusiasts.The woman doesn't think it will be the most beautiful trip of her life.A warm comedy intended for fans of Jane Austen's works.The film, nominated for an award at the Sundance Film Festival, was directed by Jerushy Hess.The screenplay was based on the novel of the same title by Shannon Hale.The main character was played by Golden Globe winner Keri Russell (series "Felicity", "The Magic of Ordinary Days").</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jerusha Hess</director>
      <actor>Jane Hayes - Keri Russell</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Henry Nobley - JJ Feild</actor>
      <actor>Martin - Bret McKenzie</actor>
      <actor>Miss Elizabeth Charming - Jennifer Coolidge</actor>
      <actor>Colonel Andrews - James Callis</actor>
      <actor>Lady Amelia Heartwright - Georgia King</actor>
      <actor>Mr. Wattlesbrook - Rupert Vansittart</actor>
      <actor>Captain East - Ricky Whittle</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Wattlesbrook - Jane Seymour</actor>
      <actor>Molly - Ayda Field</actor>
    </credits><date>2013</date>
    <category lang="en">Romantic Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421165500 +0500" stop="20260421172000 +0500">
    <title>Hollywood On Set 23</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc />
    <episode-num system="onscreen">E11</episode-num>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Magazine</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421172000 +0500" stop="20260421185000 +0500">
    <title>Neighbors 2: Sorority Rising</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Mac (Seth Rogen) and Kelly (Rose Byrne) Radner have decided to sell their house and move to a better neighborhood.They are thirty trial days away from finalizing the contract, during which time potential buyers can conduct an inspection and, if they don't like anything, break the contract.It's bad luck that students from the Kappa Nu sorority show up in the area.Shelby (Chloë Grace Moretz), Beth (Kiersey Clemons) and Nora (Beanie Feldstein) - just like their predecessors - love to throw parties.The Radners must enlist the help of their old enemy, Teddy Sanders (Zac Efron).The recent college star is struggling with his own issues.Lonely, he wants to be needed by someone at all costs.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nicholas Stoller</director>
      <actor>Mac Radner - Seth Rogen</actor>
      <actor>Teddy Sanders - Zac Efron</actor>
      <actor>Kelly Radner - Rose Byrne</actor>
      <actor>Shelby - Chloë Grace Moretz</actor>
      <actor>Jimmy - Ike Barinholtz</actor>
      <actor>Beth - Kiersey Clemons</actor>
      <actor>Pete - Dave Franco</actor>
      <actor>Garf - Jerrod Carmichael</actor>
      <actor>Scoonie - Christopher Mintz-Plasse</actor>
      <actor>Nora - Beanie Feldstein</actor>
    </credits><date>2016</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421185000 +0500" stop="20260421203500 +0500">
    <title>Rise of the Planet of the Apes</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>San Francisco.Will Rodman is a scientist employed by a pharmaceutical company.She is developing a formula for a drug that regenerates brain tissue that could cure his father, who suffers from Alzheimer's disease.A little chimpanzee named Caesar comes under the care of a scientist.This is where Will conducts his research.Over time, he begins to achieve success and is on the verge of a big breakthrough.He meets Caroline Aranha, who has devoted her entire life to monkeys and knows the capabilities of this species perfectly.It quickly turns out that the new drug also has side effects - it increases intelligence.Gifted with increasingly greater cognitive abilities, the chimpanzee realizes that his life means nothing to scientists.Outraged, he decides to oppose people.Caesar takes advantage of the ignorance of the facility's guards and gives samples of the drug to other chimpanzees.In a short time, all the monkeys escape from the building and start wreaking destruction in the city.The fight between intelligent monkeys for domination over humans begins.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Rupert Wyatt</director>
      <actor>Will Rodman - James Franco</actor>
      <actor>Charles Rodman - John Lithgow</actor>
      <actor>Caesar - Andy Serkis</actor>
      <actor>Caroline - Freida Pinto</actor>
      <actor>Dodge Landon - Tom Felton</actor>
      <actor>John Landon - Brian Cox</actor>
      <actor>Franklin - Tyler Labine</actor>
      <actor>Hunsiker - David Hewlett</actor>
      <actor>Woman on Street - Sonja Bennett</actor>
      <actor>Irena - Chelah Horsdal</actor>
    </credits><date>2011</date>
    <category lang="en">Film Sf</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421203500 +0500" stop="20260421221500 +0500">
    <title>Silver Star</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>African American Billie (Troy Leigh-Anne Johnson) is twenty years old and a tomboy.He comes from a military family and is missing one eye.After serving her prison sentence, she discovers that her separated parents are facing eviction.He decides to prevent this at all costs.The woman decides to rob a bank, but the action ends in failure.As a result, the young criminal takes her client hostage.Pregnant Franny (Grace Van Dien) is eighteen years old and has a head open to crazy ideas.Together they escape and set off on an adventurous journey.At one point, Franny offers Billie an unexpected deal.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Ruben Amar</director>
      <director>Lola Bessis</director>
      <actor>Franny - Grace Van Dien</actor>
      <actor>Billie - Troy Leigh-Anne Johnson</actor>
      <actor>Tyrone Sands - Johnath Davis</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Woodman - Getchie Argetsinger</actor>
      <actor>Shonda - Tamara Fruits</actor>
      <actor>Alice - Ekaterina Baker</actor>
      <actor>Dylan - Joey Giambattista</actor>
      <actor>William Bortschstoecker - Josh Silverman</actor>
      <actor>Mrs. Clark - Amy Tribbey</actor>
      <actor>Jess - Noa Fisher</actor>
    </credits><date>2024</date>
    <category lang="en">Social Drama</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421221500 +0500" stop="20260421230500 +0500">
    <title>Industry</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Notting Hill</sub-title>
    <desc>Harper Stern (Myha'la Herrold) moves to London from a small town in upstate New York.He takes up a job at a major international bank, Pierpoint &amp; Co.She really wants to prove herself to her superiors and do better than her peers.However, he quickly comes face to face with the brutal reality.He discovers that in the fight for a job it is not only competence that counts, but also origin.People from privileged families have much greater opportunities.However, this does not take away from her enthusiasm and motivates her even more to try to get her dream job.Together with other graduates from his age group, he learns about the hierarchical realities of the industry.Young people fall into the ruthless corporate machine where no one trusts anyone, and everyone, regardless of ethical issues, tries to take the place of their colleagues in a better position.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S1E3</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Tinge Krishnan</director>
      <actor>Gus - David Jonsson</actor>
      <actor>Hari - Nabhaan Rizwan</actor>
      <actor>Harper - Myha'la Herrold</actor>
      <actor>Kenny Kilblane - Conor MacNeill</actor>
      <actor>Yasmin - Marisa Abela</actor>
      <actor>Sara Dhadwal - Priyanga Burford</actor>
      <actor>Tate Connelley - Trader - Charlotte Callaghan</actor>
      <actor>Graduate - Clemmie France Hayhurst</actor>
      <actor>Robert - Harry Lawtey</actor>
      <actor>Eric - Ken Leung</actor>
    </credits><date>2020</date>
    <category lang="en">Drama Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme><programme channel="HBO3-PL" start="20260421230500 +0500" stop="20260422000000 +0500">
    <title>The Great</title>
    <sub-title lang="en">Choose Your Weapon</sub-title>
    <desc>A continuation of the story about Tsarina Catherine (Elle Fanning), in which facts mix with satire.After the woman recently tried to kill her husband, Piotr (Nicholas Hoult), and imprisoned all his friends, the relationship between them is not good.Meanwhile, Katarzyna also faces political problems.Wanting to solve them, the ruler becomes famous also outside Russia.During this time, Piotr tries to accept the fact that he lives in his wife's shadow.He devotes himself to fatherhood, takes part in hunting and discovers culinary novelties.Finally, they both decide to take a responsible step - they decide to save their marriage
The British ambassador offers Catherine an island in the Mediterranean Sea in exchange for 10,000 soldiers who would be sent to North America, where the War of Independence is taking place.The ruler promises him help, but delays it, enchanted by the American ambassador.Eventually, she even starts an affair with him, which makes Piotr jealous.Marial is upset that she is no longer Catherine's friend.Maxim, her husband, is furious that the woman flaunts her intimate relationship with Grigor and challenges the man to a duel.</desc>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S3E2</episode-num>
    <credits>
      <director>Colin Bucksey</director>
      <director>Matthew Moore</director>
      <director>Bert</director>
      <actor>Katarzyna - Elle Fanning</actor>
      <actor>Piotr - Nicholas Hoult</actor>
      <actor>Marial - Phoebe Fox</actor>
      <actor>Velementov - Douglas Hodge</actor>
      <actor>Arkady - Bayo Gbadamosi</actor>
      <actor>Aunt Elizabeth - Belinda Bromilow</actor>
      <actor>Archbishop - Adam Godley</actor>
      <actor>Georgina - Charity Wakefield</actor>
      <actor>Queen Agnes - Grace Molony</actor>
      <actor>Grigor Dymov - Gwilym Lee</actor>
    </credits><date>2023</date>
    <category lang="en">Comedy Series</category>
    <language>en</language>
  </programme>
</tv>