<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="wedo-movies-UK">
    <display-name>wedo movies</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/wedo-movies-UK.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260420041057 +0500" stop="20260420061926 +0500">
    <title>Damage</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>An older politician begins an affair with his son's fiancée, leading to a series of devastating events.</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/2/1765107-portrait.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260420061926 +0500" stop="20260420081340 +0500">
    <title>Dark Night of the Scarecrow</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In a small Southern town, four vigilantes wrongfully execute a mentally-challenged man, but after the court sets them free, they begin to mysteriously experience deadly "accidents."</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/2/2339660-portrait.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260420081340 +0500" stop="20260420100005 +0500">
    <title>Radio Rebel</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Tara (Debby Ryan) -  a painfully shy high-schooler, has a secret: she is also a confident DJ known as Radio Rebel, who lends her voice to others.</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/2/1766322-portrait.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260420100005 +0500" stop="20260420114255 +0500">
    <title>A Romance Wedding</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Zoe Davis is a successful and highly driven wedding planner in the big city. When her father asks her for help at the family café shop, she happily drives back to her cozy hometown of Romance, Oregon. Little does she know her mom has already hired Will to help, an aspiring chef and coincidentally...Zoe’s childhood sweetheart! Tensions rise between Zoe and Will, but so does the chemistry. Will they settle their differences and find lost love along the way?</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/2/1671657-portrait.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260420114255 +0500" stop="20260420140906 +0500">
    <title>A Handful of Dust</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>The wife's affair and a death in the family hasten the demise of an upper-class English marriage.</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/5/2339664-portrait_textless.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260420140906 +0500" stop="20260420163337 +0500">
    <title>Spitfire</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>R. J. Mitchell, a patriotic aircraft designer, was concerned about the rise of German military power and dedicated himself to creating a defense against the German Messerschmidt, ultimately sacrificing his health.  AKA The First of the Few</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/2/1768487-portrait.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260420163337 +0500" stop="20260420191231 +0500">
    <title>McLintock!</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Wealthy rancher G. W. McLintock uses his power and influence in the territory to keep the peace between farmers, ranchers, land-grabbers, Indians and corrupt government officials.</desc>
    <date>19630101</date>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/2/2805668-portrait.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260420191231 +0500" stop="20260420205558 +0500">
    <title>Killer in Red</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Christa Bright is an aspiring personal stylist who has an instant connection with new client Kat Niven, a shy woman who needs help gaining confidence. But Kat's admiration for Christa turns into an all consuming obsession with Christa and her fiancé, and she will stop at nothing to get what she wants.  A.K.A My Killer Client</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/2/1671474-portrait.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260420205558 +0500" stop="20260420224055 +0500">
    <title>Kidnapped to the Island</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>When a star-struck teenager with a desire to make it as a pop star disappears, her concerned single mom sets out to rescue her from the controlling singer who lured her to a faraway island with promises of fame and fortune.</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/2/1671663-portrait.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260420224055 +0500" stop="20260421010002 +0500">
    <title>Away from Her</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After 45 years of marriage, ageing couple Fiona and Grant are struck with a devastating blow, the looming clouds of Alzheimer's disease. In a heart-breaking decision, Fiona is moved into a residential facility. But there's one more shock on the horizon as Fiona starts to transfer her affections to another man, Aubrey, who also is a patient at the nursing home. A double-Oscar-nominated, beautifully subtle exploration of a devastating disease; Julie Christie turns in a Golden Globe winning performance in this honest, life-affirming story of relationships, love and devotion.</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/2/1669915-portrait.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260421010002 +0500" stop="20260421030241 +0500">
    <title>Down With Love</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>In 1962 New York City, love blossoms between a playboy journalist and a feminist advice author.</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/2/1768420-portrait.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260421030241 +0500" stop="20260421051403 +0500">
    <title>The Exception</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Secrets are revealed, allegiances are tested, and love is defined. Set in WWII - when German soldier, Stefan (Jai Courtney: Suicide Squad), goes on a mission to investigate exiled German Monarch Kaiser Wilhelm II (Christopher Plummer: The Girl With The Dragon Tattoo), he ends up falling dangerously in love with Mieke (Lily James: Cinderella) one of the housemaids. All is fair in love and war.</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://provider-static.plex.tv/epg/cms/production/8e0c6799-af71-4c18-8a81-19ee30c4f935/wedo-movies_2000x3000_2.jpg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260421051403 +0500" stop="20260421070932 +0500">
    <title>Webcam Cheerleaders</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Maisy heads to her late sister's college to dig into the truth about what happened to her. She finds out that many of the girls on the cheer squad are also working as webcam models. But sharing what she learns could be risky.</desc>
    <category>Movie</category>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://cdn-images.watch4.com/1920/2/2034665-portrait.jpg" />
  </programme>
</tv>