<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv>
  <channel id="wedo-movies-UK">
    <display-name>wedo movies</display-name>
    <icon src="https://thefilmtuition.com/tvlogo/wedo-movies-UK.png" />
  </channel><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260417072438 +0500" stop="20260417100005 +0500">
    <title>McLintock!</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>Wealthy rancher G. W. McLintock uses his power and influence in the territory to keep the peace between farmers, ranchers, land-grabbers, Indians and corrupt government officials.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://tvpnlogopeu.samsungcloud.tv/platform/image/contents/vc/00/LINEAR/GB_USQO570425A_1761017812_0_20260408T170427256Z_43_imageprocessorclient-tvplus-linear-74d4c47476-pkcwb.jpeg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260417100005 +0500" stop="20260417114442 +0500">
    <title>A Love to Remember</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>After a year of interacting exclusively online, Tenley, an eco-conscious horticulturist, finally works up the courage to meet her online crush, Jared. When Jared doesn't show because of a bike accident, Tenley gets mistaken for his wife at the hospital. Soon, she's forced to keep the lie up with Jared's entire family and his annoyingly charming best friend, Everett in order to save Jared's company... You've Got Mail meets While You Were Sleeping!</desc>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://tvpnlogopeu.samsungcloud.tv/platform/image/contents/vc/00/LINEAR/GB_USQO570425A_1200803965_1_20250918T082851952Z_51_imageprocessorclient-tvplus-linear-5db7c6bc99-t7nzf.jpeg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260417114442 +0500" stop="20260417133301 +0500">
    <title>Wedding Wonderland</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>When family conflicts arise between happy couple Hallie and Lucas during the week before their big day, their plans for a breezy wedding in the tropics take a turn and their love is tested when they are forced to put on a small-town winter wedding in the snow.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://tvpnlogopeu.samsungcloud.tv/platform/image/contents/vc/00/LINEAR/GB_USQO570425A_1275308632_0_20251023T092934580Z_70_imageprocessorclient-tvplus-linear-5db7c6bc99-grwzd.jpeg" />
  </programme><programme channel="wedo-movies-UK" start="20260417133301 +0500" stop="20260417161922 +0500">
    <title>Death of a Salesman</title>
    <sub-title />
    <desc>During the post-war boom period of the late '40s, Willy Loman is an aging, traveling salesman, who despairs that his life his been lived in vain. Facing dispensability and insignificance in a heated, youthful economy, Willy is not ready to part with his cherished fantasies of an America that admires him for personable triumphs in the marketplace.</desc>
    <language>en</language>
    <icon src="https://tvpnlogopeu.samsungcloud.tv/platform/image/contents/vc/00/LINEAR/GB_USQO570425A_486531407_0_20231128T144134710Z_92.jpeg" />
  </programme>
</tv>